[
  {
    "id": "1",
    "question": "\u0d15\u0d47\u0d30\u0d33\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d06\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f \u0d2e\u0d41\u0d16\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d2e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d3f?",
    "answer": "\u0d07. \u0d0e\u0d02. \u0d0e\u0d38\u0d4d. \u0d28\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d42\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d3e\u0d1f\u0d4d ",
    "status": "2"
  },
  {
    "id": "2",
    "question": "\u0d15\u0d47\u0d30\u0d33\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d06\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f \u0d27\u0d28\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d2e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d3f ?\r\n",
    "answer": "\u0d38\u0d3f. \u0d05\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d24\u0d2e\u0d47\u0d28\u0d4b\u0d7b ",
    "status": "2"
  },
  {
    "id": "3",
    "question": "\u0d15\u0d47\u0d30\u0d33\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d06\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f \u0d35\u0d3f\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d2d\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d38\u0d2e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d3f ?\r\n",
    "answer": "\u0d1c\u0d4b\u0d38\u0d2b\u0d4d \u0d2e\u0d41\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d36\u0d4d\u0d36\u0d47\u0d30\u0d3f ",
    "status": "2"
  },
  {
    "id": "4",
    "question": "\u0d15\u0d47\u0d30\u0d33\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d06\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f \u0d24\u0d4a\u0d34\u0d3f\u0d7d-\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d7b\u0d38\u0d4d\u200c\u0d2a\u0d4b\u0d7c\u0d1f\u0d4d \u0d35\u0d15\u0d41\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d4d \u0d2e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d3f ?\r\n",
    "answer": "\u0d1f\u0d3f.\u0d35\u0d3f. \u0d24\u0d4b\u0d2e\u0d38\u0d4d ",
    "status": "2"
  },
  {
    "id": "5",
    "question": "\u0d15\u0d47\u0d30\u0d33\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d06\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f \u0d35\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d35\u0d38\u0d3e\u0d2f \u0d35\u0d15\u0d41\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d4d \u0d2e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d3f ?\r\n",
    "answer": "\u0d15\u0d46. \u0d2a\u0d3f. \u0d17\u0d4b\u0d2a\u0d3e\u0d32\u0d7b ",
    "status": "2"
  },
  {
    "id": "6",
    "question": "\u0d15\u0d47\u0d30\u0d33\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d06\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f \u0d28\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d2e\u0d02-\u0d35\u0d48\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d24\u0d3f \u0d35\u0d15\u0d41\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d4d \u0d2e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d3f ?\r\n",
    "answer": "\u0d35\u0d3f.\u0d06\u0d7c. \u0d15\u0d43\u0d37\u0d4d\u0d23\u0d2f\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d7c ",
    "status": "2"
  },
  {
    "id": "7",
    "question": "\u0d15\u0d47\u0d30\u0d33\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d06\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f \u0d2d\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d37\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d02-\u0d35\u0d28\u0d35\u0d15\u0d41\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d4d \u0d2e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d3f ?\r\n",
    "answer": "\u0d15\u0d46.\u0d38\u0d3f. \u0d1c\u0d4b\u0d7c\u0d1c\u0d4d ",
    "status": "2"
  },
  {
    "id": "8",
    "question": "\u0d15\u0d47\u0d30\u0d33\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d06\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f \u0d2a\u0d4a\u0d24\u0d41\u0d2e\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d2e\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d35\u0d15\u0d41\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d4d \u0d2e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d3f ?\r\n",
    "answer": "\u0d1f\u0d3f.\u0d0e. \u0d2e\u0d1c\u0d40\u0d26\u0d4d ",
    "status": "2"
  },
  {
    "id": "9",
    "question": "\u0d15\u0d47\u0d30\u0d33\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d06\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f \u0d24\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d26\u0d47\u0d36\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d35\u0d2f\u0d02\u0d2d\u0d30\u0d23 \u0d35\u0d15\u0d41\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d4d \u0d2e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d3f ?\r\n",
    "answer": "\u0d2a\u0d3f.\u0d15\u0d46. \u0d1a\u0d3e\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d7b ",
    "status": "2"
  },
  {
    "id": "10",
    "question": "\u0d15\u0d47\u0d30\u0d33\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d06\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f \u0d06\u0d30\u0d4b\u0d17\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d02 \u0d35\u0d15\u0d41\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d4d \u0d2e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d3f ?\r\n",
    "answer": "\u0d21\u0d4b. \u0d0e.\u0d06\u0d7c. \u0d2e\u0d47\u0d28\u0d4b\u0d7b ",
    "status": "2"
  },
  {
    "id": "11",
    "question": "\u0d15\u0d47\u0d30\u0d33\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d32\u0d4b\u0d15 \u0d38\u0d2d\u0d3e \u0d2e\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d21\u0d32\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d19\u0d33\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d0e\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d23\u0d02?\r\n",
    "answer": "20",
    "status": "2"
  },
  {
    "id": "12",
    "question": "\u0d15\u0d47\u0d30\u0d33\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d30\u0d3e\u0d1c\u0d4d\u0d2f \u0d38\u0d2d\u0d3e \u0d38\u0d40\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d41\u0d15\u0d33\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d0e\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d23\u0d02?\r\n",
    "answer": "9",
    "status": "2"
  },
  {
    "id": "13",
    "question": "\u0d15\u0d47\u0d30\u0d33\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d06\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f \u0d35\u0d28\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d3e \u0d2e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d3f?\r\n",
    "answer": "\u0d15\u0d46.\u0d06\u0d7c. \u0d17\u0d57\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2e \r\n",
    "status": "2"
  },
  {
    "id": "14",
    "question": "\u0d15\u0d47\u0d30\u0d33 \u0d28\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d2e\u0d38\u0d2d\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d06\u0d15\u0d46 \u0d05\u0d02\u0d17\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d19\u0d7e?",
    "answer": "141",
    "status": "2"
  },
  {
    "id": "15",
    "question": "\u0d15\u0d47\u0d30\u0d33 \u0d28\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d2e\u0d38\u0d2d\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d7d \u0d24\u0d3f\u0d30\u0d1e\u0d4d\u0d1e\u0d46\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d46\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f \u0d05\u0d02\u0d17\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d19\u0d7e?",
    "answer": "140",
    "status": "2"
  },
  {
    "id": "16",
    "question": "\u0d15\u0d47\u0d30\u0d33 \u0d28\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d2e\u0d38\u0d2d\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d0f\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d35\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d02 \u0d15\u0d41\u0d31\u0d1e\u0d4d\u0d1e \u0d38\u0d4d\u200c\u0d2a\u0d40\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d7c?\r\n",
    "answer": "\u0d38\u0d3f.\u0d0e\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d4d. \u0d2e\u0d41\u0d39\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d26\u0d4d \u0d15\u0d4b\u0d2f ",
    "status": "2"
  },
  {
    "id": "17",
    "question": "\u0d15\u0d47\u0d30\u0d33 \u0d28\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d2e\u0d38\u0d2d\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d06\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f \u0d21\u0d46\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d42\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d3f \u0d38\u0d4d\u200c\u0d2a\u0d40\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d7c?\r\n",
    "answer": "\u0d15\u0d46. \u0d13. \u0d10. \u0d37\u0d3e\u0d2d\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d3f ",
    "status": "2"
  },
  {
    "id": "18",
    "question": "\u0d15\u0d47\u0d30\u0d33\u0d02 \u0d0e\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30 \u0d24\u0d35\u0d23 \u0d30\u0d3e\u0d37\u0d4d\u200c\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d2a\u0d24\u0d3f \u0d2d\u0d30\u0d23\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d7b \u0d15\u0d40\u0d34\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d3f?",
    "answer": "7 \u0d24\u0d35\u0d23",
    "status": "2"
  },
  {
    "id": "19",
    "question": "\u0d2a\u0d42\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4b\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d42\u0d7c \u0d2f\u0d41\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d27\u0d02 \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d46\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d15\u0d32\u0d3e\u0d2a\u0d02?\r\n",
    "answer": "\u0d2e\u0d32\u0d2c\u0d3e\u0d7c \u0d32\u0d39\u0d33 ",
    "status": "2"
  },
  {
    "id": "20",
    "question": "\u0d15\u0d2f\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d42\u0d7c \u0d38\u0d2e\u0d30\u0d02 \u0d28\u0d1f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d35\u0d7c\u0d37\u0d02?",
    "answer": "1941",
    "status": "2"
  },
  {
    "id": "21",
    "question": "\u0d32\u0d4b\u0d15\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d46 \u0d0f\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d35\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d35\u0d32\u0d3f\u0d2f \u0d30\u0d3e\u0d1c\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d02?\r\n",
    "answer": "\u0d31\u0d37\u0d4d\u0d2f ",
    "status": "7"
  },
  {
    "id": "22",
    "question": "\u0d32\u0d4b\u0d15\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d46 \u0d0f\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d35\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d35\u0d32\u0d3f\u0d2f \u0d30\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d3e\u0d2e\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d46 \u0d30\u0d3e\u0d1c\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d02?\r\n",
    "answer": "\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d21 ",
    "status": "7"
  },
  {
    "id": "23",
    "question": "\u0d32\u0d4b\u0d15\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d46 \u0d0f\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d35\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d35\u0d32\u0d3f\u0d2f \u0d06\u0d2b\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d7b \u0d30\u0d3e\u0d1c\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d02?\r\n",
    "answer": "\u0d38\u0d41\u0d21\u0d3e\u0d7b ",
    "status": "7"
  },
  {
    "id": "24",
    "question": "\u0d32\u0d4b\u0d15\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d0f\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d35\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d15\u0d42\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d24\u0d7d \u0d1c\u0d28\u0d38\u0d02\u0d16\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d33\u0d4d\u0d33 \u0d30\u0d3e\u0d1c\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d02?\r\n",
    "answer": "\u0d1a\u0d48\u0d28 ",
    "status": "7"
  },
  {
    "id": "25",
    "question": "\u0d32\u0d4b\u0d15\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d0f\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d35\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d15\u0d41\u0d31\u0d35\u0d4d \u0d1c\u0d28\u0d38\u0d02\u0d16\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d33\u0d4d\u0d33 \u0d30\u0d3e\u0d1c\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d02?\r\n",
    "answer": "\u0d35\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d7b ",
    "status": "7"
  },
  {
    "id": "26",
    "question": "\u0d32\u0d4b\u0d15\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d7d \u0d06\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d3f \u0d1a\u0d32\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30 \u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d26\u0d7c\u0d36\u0d28\u0d02 \u0d28\u0d1f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d0e\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d1f\u0d46?\r\n",
    "answer": "\u0d2a\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d40\u0d38\u0d4d ",
    "status": "4"
  },
  {
    "id": "27",
    "question": "\u0d32\u0d4b\u0d15\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d7d \u0d06\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d3f \u0d1a\u0d32\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30 \u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d26\u0d7c\u0d36\u0d28\u0d02 \u0d28\u0d1f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d4d?\r\n",
    "answer": "1895 \u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d7c\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d4d 22",
    "status": "4"
  },
  {
    "id": "28",
    "question": "\u0d06\u0d27\u0d41\u0d28\u0d3f\u0d15 \u0d38\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d3f\u0d2e\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d35\u0d4d?\r\n",
    "answer": "\u0d21\u0d47\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d21\u0d4d \u0d17\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d2b\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d ",
    "status": "4"
  },
  {
    "id": "29",
    "question": "\u0d06\u0d27\u0d41\u0d28\u0d3f\u0d15 \u0d38\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d3f\u0d2e\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d09\u0d2a\u0d1c\u0d4d\u0d1e\u0d3e\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d7e ?\r\n",
    "answer": "\u0d32\u0d42\u0d2e\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d7c \u0d38\u0d39\u0d4b\u0d26\u0d30\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d7c(\u0d06\u0d17\u0d38\u0d4d\u200c\u0d24\u0d4d\u200c \u0d32\u0d42\u0d2e\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d7c, \u0d32\u0d42\u0d2f\u0d3f \u0d32\u0d42\u0d2e\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d7c)",
    "status": "4"
  },
  {
    "id": "30",
    "question": "\u0d06\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f \u0d36\u0d3e\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30 \u0d1a\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d3f \u0d05\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d46\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d24\u0d4d?\r\n",
    "answer": "\u0d0e \u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d4d \u0d1f\u0d41 \u0d2e\u0d42\u0d7a (\u0d38\u0d02\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d27\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d02-\u0d1c\u0d4b\u0d7c\u0d1c\u0d38\u0d4d \u0d2e\u0d46\u0d32\u0d4d\u0d32\u0d3f\u0d38\u0d4d ,1902 )",
    "status": "4"
  },
  {
    "id": "31",
    "question": "\u0d15\u0d25\u0d3e\u0d1a\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d19\u0d33\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d35\u0d4d?\r\n",
    "answer": "\u0d0e\u0d21\u0d4d\u200c\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d7b \u0d0e\u0d38\u0d4d. \u0d2a\u0d4b\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d7c ",
    "status": "4"
  },
  {
    "id": "32",
    "question": "\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d7c\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d42\u0d7a \u0d38\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d3f\u0d2e\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d35\u0d4d?\r\n",
    "answer": "\u0d35\u0d3e\u0d7e\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d4d \u0d21\u0d3f\u0d38\u0d4d\u200c\u0d28\u0d3f ",
    "status": "4"
  },
  {
    "id": "33",
    "question": "\u0d0e.\u0d21\u0d3f. 1000\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d7d \u0d07\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d2f\u0d46 \u0d06\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d2e\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d4d ?",
    "answer": "\u0d2e\u0d41\u0d39\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d26\u0d4d \u0d17\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f ",
    "status": "2"
  },
  {
    "id": "34",
    "question": "\u0d30\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d3e\u0d02 \u0d24\u0d31\u0d48\u0d7b \u0d2f\u0d41\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d27\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d7d \u0d06\u0d30\u0d46\u0d3e\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d \u0d0f\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d41\u0d2e\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d24\u0d4d?",
    "answer": "\u0d2a\u0d43\u0d25\u0d4d\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d1c\u0d4d \u0d1a\u0d57\u0d39\u0d3e\u0d7b, \u0d2e\u0d41\u0d39\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d26\u0d4d \u0d17\u0d4b\u0d31\u0d3f ",
    "status": "2"
  },
  {
    "id": "35",
    "question": "\u0d21\u0d7d\u0d39\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d38\u0d41\u0d7d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d7b \u0d30\u0d3e\u0d1c\u0d35\u0d02\u0d36\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d19\u0d7e \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d46\u0d32\u0d4d\u0d32\u0d3e\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d30\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d41 ?",
    "answer": "\u0d05\u0d1f\u0d3f\u0d2e\u0d35\u0d02\u0d36\u0d02 \u0d05\u0d25\u0d35\u0d3e \u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d2e\u0d32\u0d41\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4d \u0d35\u0d02\u0d36\u0d02, \u0d16\u0d3f\u0d7d\u0d1c\u0d3f \u0d35\u0d02\u0d36\u0d02, \u0d24\u0d41\u0d17\u0d4d\u0d33\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d41\u0d15\u0d7e, \u0d38\u0d2f\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d26\u0d4d \u0d35\u0d02\u0d36\u0d02, \u0d32\u0d4b\u0d27\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d7e",
    "status": "2"
  },
  {
    "id": "36",
    "question": "\u0d0f\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d35\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d12\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d3f \u0d2d\u0d30\u0d23\u0d02 \u0d28\u0d1f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d2f \u0d21\u0d7d\u0d39\u0d3f \u0d38\u0d41\u0d7d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d7b\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d7c \u0d06\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d ?",
    "answer": "\u0d32\u0d4b\u0d27\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d7e",
    "status": "2"
  },
  {
    "id": "37",
    "question": "\u0d05\u0d1f\u0d3f\u0d2e\u0d35\u0d02\u0d36\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d2d\u0d30\u0d23\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d32\u0d02 \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d30\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d41 ?",
    "answer": "\u0d0e.\u0d21\u0d3f. 1206 - 1290",
    "status": "2"
  },
  {
    "id": "38",
    "question": "\u0d38\u0d2f\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d26\u0d4d \u0d35\u0d02\u0d36\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d2d\u0d30\u0d23\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d32\u0d02 \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d30\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d41 ?",
    "answer": "1414 - 1451",
    "status": "2"
  },
  {
    "id": "39",
    "question": ". '\u0d32\u0d3e\u0d16\u0d4d \u0d2c\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d37\u0d4d\" \u0d05\u0d25\u0d35\u0d3e \u0d32\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d37\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d19\u0d7e \u0d28\u0d7d\u0d15\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d35\u0d7b \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d05\u0d2a\u0d30\u0d28\u0d3e\u0d2e\u0d2e\u0d41\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d30\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d38\u0d41\u0d7d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d4d ?",
    "answer": "\u0d15\u0d41\u0d1e\u0d4d\u0d1e\u0d2c\u0d4d\u0d26\u0d40\u0d7b \u0d10\u0d2c\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4d",
    "status": "2"
  },
  {
    "id": "40",
    "question": "\u0d15\u0d41\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d2c\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d3e\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d28\u0d3f\u0d7c\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d02 \u0d2a\u0d42\u0d7c\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d41 \u0d2d\u0d30\u0d23\u0d3e\u0d27\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d15\u0d3e\u0d32\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d ?",
    "answer": "\u0d2b\u0d3f\u0d31\u0d4b\u0d38\u0d4d \u0d37\u0d3e \u0d24\u0d41\u0d17\u0d4d\u0d33\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4d",
    "status": "2"
  },
  {
    "id": "41",
    "question": "\u0d21\u0d7d\u0d39\u0d3f \u0d38\u0d3f\u0d02\u0d39\u0d3e\u0d38\u0d28\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d47\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d2f \u0d06\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d46 \u0d38\u0d41\u0d7d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d4d ?",
    "answer": "\u0d15\u0d41\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d2c\u0d4d\u0d26\u0d40\u0d7b\u0d10\u0d2c\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4d",
    "status": "2"
  },
  {
    "id": "42",
    "question": "\u0d24\u0d32\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d02 \u0d32\u0d3e\u0d39\u0d4b\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d7d \u0d28\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d4d \u0d21\u0d7d\u0d39\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d47\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4d \u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d2f \u0d05\u0d1f\u0d3f\u0d2e\u0d35\u0d02\u0d36 \u0d38\u0d41\u0d7d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d4d ?",
    "answer": "\u0d07\u0d7d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d41\u0d2e\u0d3f\u0d37\u0d4d ",
    "status": "2"
  },
  {
    "id": "43",
    "question": "\u0d07\u0d7d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d41\u0d2e\u0d3f\u0d37\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d15\u0d3e\u0d32\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d30\u0d42\u0d2a\u0d02\u0d15\u0d46\u0d3e\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24 \u0d28\u0d3e\u0d7d\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d24\u0d02\u0d17 \u0d38\u0d02\u0d18 \u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d2d\u0d41\u0d38\u0d2e\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d3f \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d ?",
    "answer": "\u0d1a\u0d39\u0d7d\u0d17\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d3f",
    "status": "2"
  },
  {
    "id": "44",
    "question": "\u0d31\u0d38\u0d3f\u0d2f \u0d38\u0d41\u0d7d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d28 \u0d06\u0d30\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d2e\u0d15\u0d33\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d30\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d41 ?",
    "answer": "\u0d07\u0d7d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d41\u0d2e\u0d3f\u0d37\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d46",
    "status": "2"
  },
  {
    "id": "45",
    "question": "\u0d2c\u0d3e\u0d7d\u0d2c\u0d7b \u0d21\u0d7d\u0d39\u0d3f \u0d2d\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a \u0d15\u0d3e\u0d32\u0d18\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d2e\u0d47\u0d24\u0d4d",
    "answer": "1266 - 1287",
    "status": "2"
  },
  {
    "id": "46",
    "question": "'\u0d38\u0d3f\u0d7d \u0d07\u0d32\u0d3e\u0d39\u0d3f\" \u0d05\u0d25\u0d35\u0d3e \u0d26\u0d48\u0d35\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d28\u0d3f\u0d34\u0d7d \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d47\u0d30\u0d41\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d30\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d38\u0d41\u0d7d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d4d ?",
    "answer": "\u0d2c\u0d3e\u0d7d\u0d2c\u0d7b",
    "status": "2"
  },
  {
    "id": "47",
    "question": "\u0d05\u0d1f\u0d3f\u0d2e\u0d35\u0d02\u0d36\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d0f\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d35\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d12\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d46 \u0d30\u0d3e\u0d1c\u0d3e\u0d35\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d4d ?",
    "answer": "\u0d15\u0d2f\u0d42\u0d7c\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d7c\u0d38\u0d4d",
    "status": "2"
  },
  {
    "id": "48",
    "question": "\u0d36\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d41\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d33\u0d46 \u0d05\u0d2e\u0d7c\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a \u0d1a\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d7b \u0d1a\u0d4b\u0d30\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d07\u0d30\u0d41\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d28\u0d2f\u0d02 \u0d38\u0d4d\u0d35\u0d40\u0d15\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a \u0d05\u0d1f\u0d3f\u0d2e\u0d35\u0d02\u0d36\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d38\u0d41\u0d7d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d7b \u0d06\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d30\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d41 ?",
    "answer": "\u0d2c\u0d3e\u0d7d\u0d2c\u0d7b",
    "status": "2"
  },
  {
    "id": "49",
    "question": "\u0d07\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d7d \u0d06\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d3f \u0d35\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d28\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d23\u0d02 \u0d15\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d4b\u0d33 \u0d28\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d23\u0d02 \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d3f\u0d35 \u0d0f\u0d7c\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d46\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d2f \u0d2d\u0d30\u0d23\u0d3e\u0d27\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d4d ?",
    "answer": "\u0d05\u0d32\u0d3e\u0d35\u0d41\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d26\u0d40\u0d7b \u0d16\u0d3f\u0d7d\u0d1c\u0d3f ",
    "status": "2"
  },
  {
    "id": "50",
    "question": "\u0d05\u0d32\u0d3e\u0d35\u0d41\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d26\u0d40\u0d7b \u0d16\u0d3f\u0d7d\u0d1c\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d06\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d3e\u0d28 \u0d15\u0d35\u0d3f \u0d06\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d30\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d41 ?",
    "answer": "\u0d05\u0d2e\u0d40\u0d7c\u0d16\u0d41\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d41",
    "status": "2"
  },
  {
    "id": "51",
    "question": "'\u0d07\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d24\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\" \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d46\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d06\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d ?",
    "answer": "\u0d05\u0d2e\u0d40\u0d7c\u0d16\u0d41\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d41",
    "status": "2"
  },
  {
    "id": "52",
    "question": "\u0d38\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d7c, \u0d24\u0d2c\u0d32 \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d3f\u0d35 \u0d15\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d1f\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d06\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d46\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d \u0d15\u0d30\u0d41\u0d24\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d46\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d24\u0d4d ?",
    "answer": "\u0d05\u0d2e\u0d40\u0d7c\u0d16\u0d41\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d41 ",
    "status": "2"
  },
  {
    "id": "53",
    "question": "\u0d24\u0d41\u0d17\u0d4d\u0d33\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4d \u0d35\u0d02\u0d36\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d0f\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d35\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d38\u0d3f\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d27\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d2f \u0d2d\u0d30\u0d23\u0d3e\u0d27\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d4d ?",
    "answer": "\u0d2e\u0d41\u0d39\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d26\u0d4d \u0d2c\u0d40\u0d7b \u0d24\u0d41\u0d17\u0d4d\u0d33\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4d",
    "status": "2"
  },
  {
    "id": "54",
    "question": "\u0d2e\u0d24\u0d28\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d41\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d2f '\u0d1c\u0d38\u0d3f\u0d2f\" \u0d06\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d3f \u0d0f\u0d7c\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d46\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d4d ?",
    "answer": "\u0d2b\u0d3f\u0d31\u0d4b\u0d38\u0d4d \u0d37\u0d3e \u0d24\u0d41\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d32\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4d",
    "status": "2"
  },
  {
    "id": "55",
    "question": "1398 \u0d7d \u0d24\u0d3f\u0d2e\u0d4b\u0d7c \u0d07\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d2f\u0d46 \u0d06\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d2e\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d41\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d4b\u0d7e \u0d21\u0d7d\u0d39\u0d3f \u0d38\u0d41\u0d7d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d7b \u0d06\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d30\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d41 ?",
    "answer": "\u0d2e\u0d41\u0d39\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d26\u0d4d \u0d2c\u0d40\u0d7b \u0d30\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d3e\u0d2e\u0d7b ",
    "status": "2"
  },
  {
    "id": "56",
    "question": "1451\u0d7d \u0d32\u0d4b\u0d27\u0d3f\u0d35\u0d02\u0d36\u0d02 \u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d3e\u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d4d ?",
    "answer": "\u0d2c\u0d39\u0d32\u0d42\u0d7d \u0d32\u0d4b\u0d27\u0d3f ",
    "status": "2"
  },
  {
    "id": "57",
    "question": "1526 \u0d32\u0d46 \u0d12\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d3e\u0d02 \u0d2a\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d3f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d2f\u0d41\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d27\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d7d \u0d07\u0d2c\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d39\u0d3f\u0d02 \u0d32\u0d4b\u0d27\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d46 \u0d2a\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d1c\u0d2f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d46\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f \u0d2e\u0d41\u0d17\u0d7e\u0d35\u0d02\u0d36\u0d02 \u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d3e\u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d4d ?",
    "answer": "\u0d2c\u0d3e\u0d2c\u0d7c",
    "status": "2"
  },
  {
    "id": "58",
    "question": "'\u0d30\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d3e\u0d02 \u0d05\u0d32\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d38\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d7c\" \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d46\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f \u0d38\u0d41\u0d7d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d4d?",
    "answer": "\u0d05\u0d32\u0d3e\u0d35\u0d41\u0d26\u0d40\u0d7b \u0d16\u0d3f\u0d7d\u0d1c\u0d3f",
    "status": "2"
  },
  {
    "id": "59",
    "question": "'\u0d2a\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d35\u0d24\u0d4d\" \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d35\u0d3f\u0d16\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d24\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d35\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d30\u0d1a\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d35\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d4d ?",
    "answer": "\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d32\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4d \u0d2e\u0d41\u0d39\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d26\u0d4d \u0d1c\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d38\u0d3f",
    "status": "2"
  },
  {
    "id": "60",
    "question": "\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d28\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d23\u0d02 \u0d28\u0d1f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d3e\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d3f \u0d05\u0d32\u0d3e\u0d35\u0d41\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d26\u0d40\u0d7b \u0d16\u0d3f\u0d7d\u0d1c\u0d3f \u0d28\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d4b\u0d17\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a \u0d09\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d4b\u0d17\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d7c \u0d06\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d30\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d41 ?",
    "answer": "\u0d37\u0d39\u0d4d\u0d28 ",
    "status": "2"
  },
  {
    "id": "61",
    "question": "\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d \u0d07\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d3e \u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d2e\u0d47\u0d2f\u0d02 \u0d24\u0d2f\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d31\u0d3e\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d24\u0d4d ?",
    "answer": "\u0d1c\u0d35\u0d3e\u0d39\u0d7c\u0d32\u0d3e\u0d7d \u0d28\u0d46\u0d39\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d41",
    "status": "2"
  },
  {
    "id": "62",
    "question": "\u0d07\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d3f \u0d0f\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d35\u0d41\u0d2e\u0d27\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d02 \u0d05\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d7c\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d33\u0d4d\u0d33\u0d24\u0d4d ?",
    "answer": "\u0d2c\u0d02\u0d17\u0d4d\u0d33\u0d3e\u0d26\u0d47\u0d36\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d ",
    "status": "2"
  },
  {
    "id": "63",
    "question": "\u0d0f\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d35\u0d41\u0d2e\u0d27\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d02 \u0d38\u0d02\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d19\u0d33\u0d41\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d3f \u0d05\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d7c\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d33\u0d4d\u0d33 \u0d38\u0d02\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d02 ?",
    "answer": "\u0d09\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d7c\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d26\u0d47\u0d36\u0d4d",
    "status": "3"
  },
  {
    "id": "64",
    "question": "\u0d2c\u0d02\u0d17\u0d3e\u0d33\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d26\u0d41\u0d03\u0d16\u0d02 \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d46\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d24\u0d4d ?",
    "answer": "\u0d26\u0d3e\u0d2e\u0d4b\u0d26\u0d7c \u0d28\u0d26\u0d3f ",
    "status": "3"
  },
  {
    "id": "65",
    "question": "\u0d2e\u0d32\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d33\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d32\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d37\u0d23\u0d2e\u0d46\u0d3e\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24 \u0d06\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d28\u0d4b\u0d35\u0d32\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d3f \u0d17\u0d23\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d46\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d24\u0d4d ?",
    "answer": "\u0d07\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d26\u0d41\u0d32\u0d47\u0d16.",
    "status": "9"
  },
  {
    "id": "66",
    "question": "\u0d32\u0d4b\u0d15\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d0f\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d35\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d05\u0d02\u0d17\u0d2c\u0d32\u0d2e\u0d41\u0d33\u0d4d\u0d33 \u0d2a\u0d3e\u0d7c\u0d32\u0d2e\u0d46\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d30\u0d3e\u0d1c\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d47\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d ?",
    "answer": "\u0d1a\u0d48\u0d28",
    "status": "7"
  },
  {
    "id": "67",
    "question": "\u0d2a\u0d3e\u0d7c\u0d32\u0d2e\u0d46\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d41\u0d15\u0d33\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d35\u0d4d ?",
    "answer": "\u0d2c\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d7a",
    "status": "7"
  },
  {
    "id": "68",
    "question": "\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d38\u0d3f\u0d21\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d27\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d2e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d38\u0d02\u0d2d\u0d3e\u0d35\u0d28 \u0d1a\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d4d\u0d24 \u0d06\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f \u0d26\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d37\u0d3f\u0d23\u0d47\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d7b \u0d38\u0d02\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d02 ?",
    "answer": "\u0d06\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d27\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d26\u0d47\u0d36\u0d4d",
    "status": "3"
  },
  {
    "id": "69",
    "question": "\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d38\u0d3f\u0d21\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d46 \u0d38\u0d02\u0d2d\u0d3e\u0d35\u0d28 \u0d1a\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d4d\u0d24 \u0d06\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f \u0d26\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d37\u0d3f\u0d23\u0d47\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d7b \u0d38\u0d02\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d02 ?",
    "answer": "\u0d24\u0d2e\u0d3f\u0d34\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d3e\u0d1f\u0d4d",
    "status": "3"
  },
  {
    "id": "70",
    "question": "\u0d1c\u0d3e\u0d7c\u0d16\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d21\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d3f \u0d28\u0d3f\u0d7c\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d26\u0d47\u0d36\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d46\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f \u0d2e\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4a\u0d30\u0d41 \u0d2a\u0d47\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d ?",
    "answer": "\u0d35\u0d28\u0d3e\u0d1e\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d7d",
    "status": "3"
  },
  {
    "id": "71",
    "question": "\u0d09\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d16\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d21\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d2a\u0d34\u0d2f \u0d2a\u0d47\u0d30\u0d4d ?",
    "answer": "\u0d09\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d1e\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d7d",
    "status": "3"
  },
  {
    "id": "72",
    "question": "\u0d32\u0d4b\u0d15\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d06\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f \u0d06\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d3f \u0d38\u0d46\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d ______ ?",
    "answer": "\u0d2b\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4b\u0d7e",
    "status": "7"
  },
  {
    "id": "73",
    "question": "\u0d32\u0d4b\u0d15\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d06\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f \u0d06\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d2c\u0d2f\u0d4b\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d ?",
    "answer": "\u0d2a\u0d46\u0d28\u0d3f\u0d38\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d3f\u0d7b",
    "status": "7"
  },
  {
    "id": "74",
    "question": "\u0d2c\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d40\u0d37\u0d4d \u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d27\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d2e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d14\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d4b\u0d17\u0d3f\u0d15 \u0d35\u0d38\u0d24\u0d3f ?",
    "answer": "10 \u0d21\u0d57\u0d23\u0d3f\u0d19\u0d4d \u0d38\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d40\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d",
    "status": "7"
  },
  {
    "id": "75",
    "question": "\u0d2c\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d40\u0d37\u0d4d \u0d30\u0d3e\u0d1c\u0d3e\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d14\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d4b\u0d17\u0d3f\u0d15 \u0d35\u0d38\u0d24\u0d3f ?",
    "answer": "\u0d2c\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3f\u0d02\u0d17\u0d4d\u0d39\u0d3e\u0d02 \u0d15\u0d4a\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d02",
    "status": "7"
  },
  {
    "id": "76",
    "question": "\u0d0f\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d35\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d15\u0d42\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d24\u0d7d \u0d30\u0d3e\u0d1c\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d19\u0d33\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d26\u0d47\u0d36\u0d3f\u0d2f \u0d15\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d15 \u0d35\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4b\u0d26\u0d02 ?",
    "answer": "\u0d2b\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d2c\u0d4b\u0d7e",
    "status": "6"
  },
  {
    "id": "77",
    "question": "\u0d06\u0d27\u0d41\u0d28\u0d3f\u0d15 \u0d2b\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d2c\u0d4b\u0d33\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d1c\u0d7b\u0d2e\u0d28\u0d3e\u0d1f\u0d4d ?",
    "answer": "\u0d07\u0d02\u0d17\u0d4d\u0d32\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d4d",
    "status": "6"
  },
  {
    "id": "78",
    "question": "\u0d2b\u0d3f\u0d2b \u0d28\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d7d \u0d35\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d35\u0d7c\u0d37\u0d02 ?",
    "answer": "1904- \u0d38\u0d42\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d4d",
    "status": "6"
  },
  {
    "id": "79",
    "question": "\u0d2b\u0d3f\u0d2b\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d07\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d4b\u0d34\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d46 \u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d38\u0d3f\u0d21\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d ?",
    "answer": "\u0d17\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d3f \u0d07\u0d7b\u0d2b\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4b",
    "status": "6"
  },
  {
    "id": "80",
    "question": "\u0d2b\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d2c\u0d4b\u0d7e \u0d17\u0d4b\u0d7e \u0d2a\u0d4b\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d09\u0d2f\u0d30\u0d02 ?",
    "answer": "2.44 m \u0d05\u0d15\u0d32\u0d02 - 7.32 m",
    "status": "6"
  },
  {
    "id": "81",
    "question": "\u0d2b\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d2c\u0d4b\u0d33\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31 \u0d2d\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d02 ?",
    "answer": "410 to 450 g",
    "status": "6"
  },
  {
    "id": "82",
    "question": "\u0d32\u0d4b\u0d15\u0d15\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d06\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f \u0d2a\u0d47\u0d30\u0d4d ?",
    "answer": "\u0d2f\u0d42\u0d7e\u0d38\u0d4d \u0d31\u0d3f\u0d2e\u0d46 \u0d15\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d4d",
    "status": "6"
  },
  {
    "id": "83",
    "question": "\u0d06\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f \u0d32\u0d4b\u0d15\u0d15\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d4d \u0d35\u0d3f\u0d1c\u0d2f\u0d3f ?",
    "answer": "\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d31\u0d17\u0d4d\u0d35\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d4d- 1930",
    "status": "6"
  },
  {
    "id": "84",
    "question": "\u0d06\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f \u0d32\u0d4b\u0d15\u0d15\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d4d \u0d31\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d23\u0d31\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d4d ?",
    "answer": "\u0d05\u0d7c\u0d1c\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d40\u0d28",
    "status": "6"
  },
  {
    "id": "85",
    "question": "\u0d06\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f \u0d32\u0d4b\u0d15\u0d15\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d4d \u0d35\u0d47\u0d26\u0d3f ?",
    "answer": "\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d31\u0d17\u0d4d\u0d35\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d4d",
    "status": "6"
  },
  {
    "id": "86",
    "question": "\u0d06\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f \u0d32\u0d4b\u0d15\u0d15\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d4d \u0d2e\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d38\u0d30\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d7d \u0d2a\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d46\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24 \u0d30\u0d3e\u0d1c\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d19\u0d7e ?",
    "answer": "13",
    "status": "6"
  },
  {
    "id": "87",
    "question": "\u0d0e\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30 \u0d35\u0d7c\u0d37\u0d02 \u0d15\u0d42\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d4b\u0d34\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d \u0d32\u0d4b\u0d15\u0d15\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d4d \u0d2e\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d38\u0d30\u0d02 \u0d28\u0d1f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d24\u0d4d ?",
    "answer": "4",
    "status": "6"
  },
  {
    "id": "88",
    "question": "\u0d32\u0d4b\u0d15\u0d15\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d7d \u0d12\u0d30\u0d41 \u0d1f\u0d40\u0d2e\u0d3f\u0d7d \u0d0e\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30 \u0d15\u0d33\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d46 \u0d30\u0d1c\u0d3f\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d7c \u0d1a\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d02 ?",
    "answer": "23",
    "status": "6"
  },
  {
    "id": "89",
    "question": "\u0d0f\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d35\u0d7c\u0d37\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d46 \u0d32\u0d4b\u0d15\u0d15\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d4d \u0d2e\u0d41\u0d24\u0d32\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d 32 \u0d1f\u0d40\u0d2e\u0d41\u0d15\u0d7e \u0d2a\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d46\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d7b \u0d24\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d19\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d24\u0d4d ?",
    "answer": "1998 \u0d2b\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d7b\u0d38\u0d4d",
    "status": "6"
  },
  {
    "id": "90",
    "question": "\u0d31\u0d37\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d7d \u0d28\u0d1f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d0e\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d2e\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d32\u0d4b\u0d15\u0d15\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d4d \u0d06\u0d23\u0d4d ?",
    "answer": "21",
    "status": "6"
  },
  {
    "id": "91",
    "question": "88 \u0d35\u0d7c\u0d37\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d3f\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d0e\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30 \u0d30\u0d3e\u0d1c\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d19\u0d7e \u0d32\u0d4b\u0d15\u0d15\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d4d \u0d1a\u0d3e\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d7b\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d4d ?",
    "answer": "8",
    "status": "6"
  },
  {
    "id": "92",
    "question": "\u0d0f\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d35\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d15\u0d42\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d24\u0d7d \u0d24\u0d35\u0d23 \u0d32\u0d4b\u0d15\u0d15\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d4d \u0d15\u0d3f\u0d30\u0d40\u0d1f\u0d02 \u0d28\u0d47\u0d1f\u0d3f\u0d2f \u0d30\u0d3e\u0d1c\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d02 ?",
    "answer": "\u0d2c\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d38\u0d40\u0d7d (5 \u0d24\u0d35\u0d23 )",
    "status": "6"
  },
  {
    "id": "93",
    "question": " \u0d0f\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d35\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d15\u0d42\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d24\u0d7d \u0d32\u0d4b\u0d15\u0d15\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d4d \u0d15\u0d33\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a \u0d30\u0d3e\u0d1c\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d02 ?",
    "answer": "\u0d2c\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d38\u0d40\u0d7d 21(\u0d1c\u0d7c\u0d2e\u0d28\u0d3f - 19)",
    "status": "6"
  },
  {
    "id": "94",
    "question": "\u0d32\u0d4b\u0d15\u0d15\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d7d \u0d0f\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d35\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d15\u0d42\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d24\u0d7d \u0d2e\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d38\u0d30\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d19\u0d7e \u0d15\u0d33\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a \u0d1f\u0d40\u0d02 ?",
    "answer": "\u0d1c\u0d7c\u0d2e\u0d28\u0d3f (106) 2\u0d2c\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d38\u0d3f\u0d7d - 104",
    "status": "6"
  },
  {
    "id": "95",
    "question": "\u0d32\u0d4b\u0d15\u0d15\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d4d \u0d2e\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d38\u0d30\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d7d \u0d0f\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d35\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d15\u0d42\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d24\u0d7d \u0d17\u0d4b\u0d33\u0d1f\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a \u0d1f\u0d40\u0d02 ?",
    "answer": "\u0d1c\u0d7c\u0d2e\u0d28\u0d3f - 224 ( \u0d2c\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d38\u0d40\u0d7d- 211)",
    "status": "6"
  },
  {
    "id": "96",
    "question": "\u0d32\u0d4b\u0d15\u0d15\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d7d \u0d0f\u0d37\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d7d \u0d28\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d4d \u0d2a\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d46\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d30\u0d3e\u0d1c\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d19\u0d33\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d0e\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d23\u0d02 ?",
    "answer": "5",
    "status": "6"
  },
  {
    "id": "97",
    "question": "\u0d32\u0d4b\u0d15\u0d15\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d7d \u0d15\u0d33\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a \u0d06\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f \u0d0f\u0d37\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d7b \u0d30\u0d3e\u0d1c\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d02 ?",
    "answer": "\u0d07\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4b\u0d28\u0d47\u0d37\u0d4d\u0d2f (1938)",
    "status": "6"
  },
  {
    "id": "98",
    "question": "\u0d31\u0d37\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d7b \u0d32\u0d4b\u0d15\u0d15\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d2d\u0d3e\u0d17\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d1a\u0d3f\u0d39\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d02 ?",
    "answer": "\u0d38\u0d3e\u0d2c\u0d3f\u0d35\u0d3e\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15",
    "status": "6"
  },
  {
    "id": "99",
    "question": "\u0d31\u0d37\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d7d \u0d09\u0d2a\u0d2f\u0d4b\u0d17\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d2a\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d ?",
    "answer": "\u0d1f\u0d46\u0d7d\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d3e\u0d7c -18 (Adidas)",
    "status": "6"
  },
  {
    "id": "100",
    "question": "\u0d2b\u0d3f\u0d2b \u0d31\u0d3e\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3f\u0d19\u0d4d \u0d38\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d26\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d02 \u0d06\u0d30\u0d02\u0d2d\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a \u0d35\u0d7c\u0d37\u0d02 ?",
    "answer": "1992 ",
    "status": "6"
  },
  {
    "id": "101",
    "question": "\u0d2b\u0d3f\u0d2b \u0d31\u0d3e\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3f\u0d19\u0d4d \u0d38\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d26\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d02 \u0d06\u0d30\u0d02\u0d2d\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a \u0d38\u0d2e\u0d2f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d12\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d3e\u0d02 \u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d41\u0d33\u0d4d\u0d33 \u0d30\u0d3e\u0d1c\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d02 ?",
    "answer": "\u0d1c\u0d7c\u0d2e\u0d28\u0d3f",
    "status": "6"
  },
  {
    "id": "102",
    "question": "\u0d0f\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d35\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d15\u0d42\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d24\u0d7d \u0d15\u0d3e\u0d32\u0d02 \u0d12\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d3e\u0d02 \u0d31\u0d3e\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3f\u0d7d \u0d24\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d7c\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d1f\u0d40\u0d02 ?",
    "answer": "\u0d2c\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d38\u0d40\u0d7d",
    "status": "6"
  },
  {
    "id": "103",
    "question": "\u0d32\u0d4b\u0d15\u0d15\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d4d \u0d28\u0d47\u0d1f\u0d3f\u0d2f \u0d1f\u0d40\u0d2e\u0d41\u0d15\u0d33\u0d3f\u0d7d \u0d06\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d25\u0d47\u0d2f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d35\u0d02 \u0d35\u0d39\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d4d \u0d15\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d4d \u0d28\u0d47\u0d1f\u0d3e\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24 \u0d12\u0d30\u0d47 \u0d12\u0d30\u0d41 \u0d1f\u0d40\u0d02 ?",
    "answer": "\u0d2c\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d38\u0d40\u0d7d",
    "status": "6"
  },
  {
    "id": "104",
    "question": "\u0d0f\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d32\u0d4b\u0d15\u0d15\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d4d \u0d2e\u0d41\u0d24\u0d32\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d \u0d14\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d4b\u0d17\u0d3f\u0d15 \u0d17\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d02 \u0d09\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d24\u0d4d ?",
    "answer": "1962 - \u0d1a\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d3f",
    "status": "6"
  },
  {
    "id": "105",
    "question": "\u0d32\u0d4b\u0d15\u0d15\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d4d \u0d28\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d3f\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d33\u0d4d\u0d33 \u0d07\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d7b \u0d31\u0d2b\u0d31\u0d3f ?",
    "answer": "\u0d15\u0d46 \u0d36\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d7c ",
    "status": "6"
  },
  {
    "id": "106",
    "question": "\u0d0f\u0d37\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d7d \u0d06\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d3f \u0d32\u0d4b\u0d15\u0d15\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d4d \u0d28\u0d1f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d24\u0d4d ?",
    "answer": "2002(\u0d1c\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d3e\u0d7b, \u0d38\u0d57\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d15\u0d4a\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d2f)",
    "status": "6"
  },
  {
    "id": "107",
    "question": "\u0d32\u0d4b\u0d15\u0d15\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d4d \u0d15\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d2b\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d2c\u0d4b\u0d33\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d15\u0d33\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d3f\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d33\u0d4d\u0d33 \u0d0f\u0d15 \u0d2a\u0d41\u0d30\u0d41\u0d37 \u0d24\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d02 ?",
    "answer": "\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d7b \u0d31\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d3e\u0d7c\u0d21\u0d4d",
    "status": "6"
  },
  {
    "id": "108",
    "question": "\u0d06\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f \u0d35\u0d28\u0d3f\u0d24 \u0d32\u0d4b\u0d15\u0d15\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d4d \u0d28\u0d1f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d35\u0d7c\u0d37\u0d02 ?",
    "answer": "1991- \u0d1a\u0d48\u0d28",
    "status": "6"
  },
  {
    "id": "109",
    "question": "\u0d2a\u0d41\u0d30\u0d41\u0d37-\u0d35\u0d28\u0d3f\u0d24 \u0d32\u0d4b\u0d15\u0d15\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d4d \u0d2b\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d2c\u0d4b\u0d7e \u0d15\u0d3f\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d1f\u0d02 \u0d28\u0d47\u0d1f\u0d3f\u0d2f \u0d06\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f \u0d1f\u0d40\u0d02 ?",
    "answer": "\u0d1c\u0d7c\u0d2e\u0d28\u0d3f",
    "status": "6"
  },
  {
    "id": "110",
    "question": "\u0d2a\u0d46\u0d32\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d06\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d15\u0d25 ?",
    "answer": "my life and beautiful game",
    "status": "6"
  },
  {
    "id": "111",
    "question": "\u0d2e\u0d31\u0d21\u0d4b\u0d23 \u0d06\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d15\u0d25 ?",
    "answer": "I am the \r\nDiego\r\n",
    "status": "6"
  },
  {
    "id": "112",
    "question": "\u0d2a\u0d46\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d05\u0d2d\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a \u0d38\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d3f\u0d2e ?",
    "answer": "escape to victory",
    "status": "6"
  },
  {
    "id": "113",
    "question": "\u0d12\u0d33\u0d3f\u0d02\u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d38\u0d3f\u0d7d \u0d07\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d7b \u0d2b\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d2c\u0d4b\u0d7e \u0d1f\u0d40\u0d02 \u0d2a\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d46\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24 \u0d35\u0d7c\u0d37\u0d02 ?",
    "answer": "1948",
    "status": "6"
  },
  {
    "id": "114",
    "question": "\u0d2c\u0d3e\u0d32\u0d7a \u0d21\u0d3f \u0d13\u0d7c \u0d2a\u0d41\u0d30\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d02 \u0d0f\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d35\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d15\u0d42\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d24\u0d7d \u0d24\u0d35\u0d23 \u0d28\u0d47\u0d1f\u0d3f\u0d2f \u0d24\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d02 ?",
    "answer": "\u0d2e\u0d46\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d38\u0d3f (5)",
    "status": "6"
  },
  {
    "id": "115",
    "question": "2014 \u0d32\u0d4b\u0d15\u0d15\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d4d \u0d35\u0d3f\u0d1c\u0d2f\u0d3f ?",
    "answer": "\u0d1c\u0d7c\u0d2e\u0d28\u0d3f (\u0d31\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d23\u0d31\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d4d - \u0d05\u0d7c\u0d1c\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d40\u0d28 )",
    "status": "6"
  },
  {
    "id": "116",
    "question": "2022 \u0d32\u0d46 \u0d32\u0d4b\u0d15\u0d15\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d4d \u0d28\u0d1f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d30\u0d3e\u0d1c\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d02 ?",
    "answer": "\u0d16\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d7c",
    "status": "6"
  },
  {
    "id": "117",
    "question": "\u0d07\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d06\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f \u0d35\u0d28\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d3e \u0d30\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d38\u0d3e\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d37\u0d3f ?",
    "answer": "\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d40\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d24\u0d3e \u0d35\u0d21\u0d47\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d7c",
    "status": "3"
  },
  {
    "id": "118",
    "question": "\u0d07\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d7b \u0d27\u0d28 \u0d35\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d47\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d40\u0d15\u0d30\u0d23\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d35\u0d4d ?",
    "answer": "\u0d2e\u0d47\u0d2f\u0d4b \u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d2d\u0d41",
    "status": "3"
  },
  {
    "id": "119",
    "question": "\u0d07\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d7b \u0d28\u0d3e\u0d37\u0d23\u0d7d \u0d15\u0d4b\u0d7a\u0d17\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d38\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d38\u0d3f\u0d21\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d3e\u0d2f \u0d06\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f \u0d26\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d37\u0d3f\u0d23\u0d47\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d7b ?",
    "answer": "\u0d2a\u0d3f.\u0d06\u0d28\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d26\u0d1a\u0d3e\u0d7c\u0d32\u0d41",
    "status": "3"
  },
  {
    "id": "120",
    "question": "'\u0d17\u0d02\u0d17\u0d2f\u0d46 \u0d2a\u0d4b\u0d32\u0d46' \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d4d \u0d17\u0d4b\u0d16\u0d32\u0d2f\u0d46 \u0d35\u0d3f\u0d36\u0d47\u0d37\u0d3f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d4d ?",
    "answer": "\u0d17\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d27\u0d3f\u0d1c\u0d3f",
    "status": "3"
  },
  {
    "id": "121",
    "question": "\u0d2d\u0d17\u0d35\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d17\u0d40\u0d24 \u0d2c\u0d02\u0d17\u0d3e\u0d33\u0d3f \u0d2d\u0d3e\u0d37\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d47\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4d \u0d2e\u0d4a\u0d34\u0d3f\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d02 \u0d1a\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d06\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d ?",
    "answer": "\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d1c\u0d3e\u0d31\u0d3e\u0d02 \u0d2e\u0d4b\u0d39\u0d7b\u0d31\u0d4b\u0d2f\u0d4d",
    "status": "3"
  },
  {
    "id": "122",
    "question": "\u0d38\u0d02\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d3e\u0d28 \u0d2e\u0d28\u0d41\u0d37\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d35\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d36 \u0d15\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d40\u0d37\u0d7b \u0d1a\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d7c\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d05\u0d02\u0d17\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d19\u0d33\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d28\u0d40\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d02 \u0d1a\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d06\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d ?",
    "answer": "\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d37\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d2a\u0d24\u0d3f",
    "status": "3"
  },
  {
    "id": "123",
    "question": "\u0d38\u0d02\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d3e\u0d28 \u0d2e\u0d28\u0d41\u0d37\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d35\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d36 \u0d15\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d40\u0d37\u0d7b \u0d1a\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d7c\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d05\u0d02\u0d17\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d19\u0d33\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d28\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d2e\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d06\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d ?",
    "answer": "\u0d17\u0d35\u0d7c\u0d23\u0d7c",
    "status": "3"
  },
  {
    "id": "124",
    "question": "\u0d2f\u0d41.\u0d2a\u0d3f.\u0d0e\u0d38\u0d4d.\u0d38\u0d3f \u0d2f\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d06\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d02 ?",
    "answer": "\u0d26\u0d4b\u0d7e\u0d2a\u0d42\u0d7c \u0d39\u0d57\u0d38\u0d4d",
    "status": "3"
  },
  {
    "id": "125",
    "question": "\u0d28\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d41\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d33\u0d46 \u0d15\u0d41\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d4d \u0d2a\u0d20\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d3f \u0d38\u0d4d\u0d35\u0d24\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30 \u0d07\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d7d \u0d06\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d3f \u0d28\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d4b\u0d17\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d46\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f \u0d15\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d40\u0d37\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d24\u0d32\u0d35\u0d7b ?",
    "answer": "\u0d21\u0d4b.\u0d1c\u0d4b\u0d7a \u0d2e\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d3f",
    "status": "3"
  },
  {
    "id": "126",
    "question": "'\u0d07\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d30' \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d2a\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d3e\u0d2a\u0d15\u0d7b ?",
    "answer": "\u0d32\u0d46\u0d28\u0d3f\u0d7b",
    "status": "3"
  },
  {
    "id": "127",
    "question": "\u0d1f\u0d46\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d40\u0d38\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d46 \u0d2b\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d1e\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d41\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d7c \u0d35\u0d3f\u0d33\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d3f\u0d30\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d2a\u0d47\u0d30\u0d4d ?",
    "answer": "\u0d1c\u0d42\u0d21\u0d3f\u0d2a\u0d3e\u0d2e\u0d46",
    "status": "7"
  },
  {
    "id": "128",
    "question": "\u0d28\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d2f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d15\u0d33\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4d\u0d32\u0d3e\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24 \u0d30\u0d3e\u0d1c\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d02 ?",
    "answer": "\u0d2a\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d17\u0d4d\u0d35\u0d47",
    "status": "7"
  },
  {
    "id": "129",
    "question": "\u0d2a\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d2e\u0d33 \u0d26\u0d4d\u0d35\u0d40\u0d2a\u0d41\u0d15\u0d7e \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d46\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d3f\u0d30\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d24\u0d4d ?",
    "answer": "\u0d15\u0d4b\u0d2e\u0d31\u0d4b\u0d38\u0d4d",
    "status": "3"
  },
  {
    "id": "130",
    "question": "\u0d06\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d3f \u0d12\u0d30\u0d41 \u0d07\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d7b \u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d38\u0d3f\u0d21\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d \u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d38\u0d02\u0d17\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a \u0d38\u0d02\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d3e\u0d28 \u0d28\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d2e\u0d38\u0d2d ?",
    "answer": "\u0d15\u0d47\u0d30\u0d33 \u0d28\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d2e\u0d38\u0d2d",
    "status": "3"
  },
  {
    "id": "131",
    "question": "\u0d1c\u0d48\u0d28\u0d2e\u0d24 \u0d17\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d2f \u0d05\u0d02\u0d17\u0d3e\u0d38\u0d4d \u0d0e\u0d34\u0d41\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d2f \u0d24\u0d2f\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d31\u0d3e\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d24\u0d4d ?",
    "answer": "\u0d2d\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d2c\u0d3e\u0d39\u0d41",
    "status": "3"
  },
  {
    "id": "132",
    "question": "\u0d07\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d7d \u0d06\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d3f \u0d15\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d7c \u0d15\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d7d \u0d0e\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d2f \u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d32\u0d02 ?",
    "answer": "\u0d15\u0d4a\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d3f (\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d38\u0d3f\u0d21\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d \u0d1f\u0d48\u0d32\u0d7c,1973)",
    "status": "3"
  },
  {
    "id": "133",
    "question": "\u0d24\u0d2e\u0d3f\u0d34\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d3e\u0d1f\u0d4d \u0d21\u0d3f.\u0d1c\u0d3f.\u0d2a\u0d3f \u0d06\u0d2f \u0d06\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f \u0d2e\u0d32\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d33\u0d3f \u0d35\u0d28\u0d3f\u0d24 ?",
    "answer": "\u0d32\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d3e \u0d36\u0d30\u0d7a",
    "status": "3"
  },
  {
    "id": "134",
    "question": "\u0d07\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d7b \u0d15\u0d30\u0d38\u0d47\u0d28\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d35\u0d4d ?",
    "answer": "\u0d2e\u0d47\u0d1c\u0d7c \u0d38\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d19\u0d7c \u0d32\u0d4b\u0d31\u0d7b\u0d38\u0d4d",
    "status": "3"
  },
  {
    "id": "135",
    "question": "\u0d15\u0d30\u0d38\u0d47\u0d28\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d06\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f \u0d38\u0d48\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d27\u0d3f\u0d2a\u0d7b ?",
    "answer": "\u0d38\u0d7c.\u0d31\u0d4b\u0d2f\u0d4d \u0d2c\u0d41\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d7c",
    "status": "3"
  },
  {
    "id": "136",
    "question": "\u0d06\u0d30\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d1a\u0d30\u0d2e\u0d26\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d \u0d35\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d28\u0d3e\u0d26\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d3f \u0d06\u0d1a\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d24\u0d4d?",
    "answer": "\u0d2a\u0d3f .\u0d0e\u0d7b \u0d2a\u0d23\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d7c",
    "status": "9"
  },
  {
    "id": "137",
    "question": "\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d23\u0d02 \u0d0e\u0d34\u0d41\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d06\u0d30\u0d4d?",
    "answer": "\u0d35\u0d3e\u0d7d\u0d2e\u0d40\u0d15\u0d3f",
    "status": "9"
  },
  {
    "id": "138",
    "question": "\u0d30\u0d2e\u0d23\u0d7b, \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d15\u0d3e\u0d35\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d02 \u0d0e\u0d34\u0d41\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d06\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d?",
    "answer": "\u0d1a\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d19\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d41\u0d34",
    "status": "9"
  },
  {
    "id": "139",
    "question": "\u0d05\u0d7d\u0d05\u0d2e\u0d40\u0d7b, \u0d2a\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d2a\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d27\u0d3f\u0d2a\u0d7c \u0d06\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d30\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d41?",
    "answer": "\u0d2e\u0d41\u0d39\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d26\u0d4d \u0d05\u0d2c\u0d4d\u0d26\u0d41\u0d31\u0d39\u0d3f\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d7b \u0d38\u0d3e\u0d39\u0d3f\u0d2c\u0d4d ",
    "status": "9"
  },
  {
    "id": "140",
    "question": "\u0d26 \u0d39\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d26\u0d41 \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d07\u0d02\u0d17\u0d4d\u0d32\u0d40\u0d37\u0d4d \u0d2a\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d02 \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d30\u0d3e\u0d1c\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d24\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d?",
    "answer": "\u0d07\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f",
    "status": "9"
  },
  {
    "id": "141",
    "question": "\u0d15\u0d47\u0d30\u0d33\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d2d\u0d30\u0d23\u0d2d\u0d3e\u0d37?",
    "answer": "\u0d2e\u0d32\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d33\u0d02",
    "status": "9"
  },
  {
    "id": "142",
    "question": "\u0d38\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d46 \u0d1c\u0d39\u0d3e\u0d02 \u0d38\u0d46 \u0d05\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1b\u0d3e \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d26\u0d47\u0d36\u0d2d\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d17\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d02 \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d2d\u0d3e\u0d37\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d \u0d30\u0d1a\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d3f\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d33\u0d4d\u0d33\u0d24\u0d4d?",
    "answer": "\u0d09\u0d31\u0d41\u0d26\u0d41",
    "status": "9"
  },
  {
    "id": "143",
    "question": "\u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d1c\u0d40\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d38\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d26\u0d47\u0d36\u0d2e\u0d46\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d4d \u0d2a\u0d31\u0d1e\u0d4d\u0d1e \u0d2e\u0d39\u0d3e\u0d7b?",
    "answer": "\u0d17\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d27\u0d3f\u0d1c\u0d3f",
    "status": "9"
  },
  {
    "id": "144",
    "question": "e - reading \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d7d e, \u0d15\u0d4a\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d4d \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d \u0d05\u0d7c\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d24\u0d4d?",
    "answer": "electronic",
    "status": "9"
  },
  {
    "id": "145",
    "question": "\u0d2e\u0d39\u0d3e\u0d2d\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d24\u0d02 \u0d30\u0d1a\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d06\u0d30\u0d4d?\t",
    "answer": "\u0d35\u0d47\u0d26\u0d35\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d38\u0d7b",
    "status": "9"
  },
  {
    "id": "146",
    "question": "\u0d35\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d46\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d24\u0d4d ,\u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d05\u0d7c\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d41\u0d33\u0d4d\u0d33 \u0d2e\u0d41\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d32\u0d3f\u0d02\u0d15\u0d33\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d2a\u0d41\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d2f \u0d17\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d7b\u0d25\u0d02 \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d4d?",
    "answer": "\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d36\u0d41\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d27 \u0d16\u0d41\u0d7c\u0d06\u0d7b",
    "status": "9"
  },
  {
    "id": "147",
    "question": "\u0d2e\u0d39\u0d3e\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d17\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d27\u0d3f \u0d06\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d15\u0d25 \u0d30\u0d1a\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d2d\u0d3e\u0d37\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d?",
    "answer": "\u0d17\u0d41\u0d1c\u0d31\u0d3e\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f",
    "status": "9"
  },
  {
    "id": "148",
    "question": "\u0d24\u0d15\u0d34\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d1a\u0d46\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d40\u0d7b \u0d05\u0d31\u0d2c\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d47\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4d \u0d35\u0d3f\u0d35\u0d7c\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d28\u0d02 \u0d1a\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d06\u0d30\u0d4d?",
    "answer": "\u0d2e\u0d41\u0d39\u0d4d \u0d2f\u0d41\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d27\u0d40\u0d7b \u0d06\u0d32\u0d41\u0d35\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d4d",
    "status": "9"
  },
  {
    "id": "149",
    "question": "\u0d36\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d40 \u0d0e\u0d7b \u0d2a\u0d23\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d7c \u0d1c\u0d28\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d0e\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d1f\u0d47\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d?",
    "answer": "\u0d28\u0d40\u0d32\u0d02\u0d2a\u0d47\u0d30\u0d42\u0d7c (\u0d15\u0d4b\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d2f\u0d02)",
    "status": "9"
  },
  {
    "id": "150",
    "question": "\u0d06\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d46 \u0d38\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d42\u0d7c\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d23 \u0d2e\u0d32\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d33 \u0d15\u0d43\u0d24\u0d3f \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d4d?",
    "answer": "\u0d38\u0d02\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d37\u0d47\u0d2a \u0d35\u0d47\u0d26\u0d3e\u0d7c\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d02",
    "status": "9"
  },
  {
    "id": "151",
    "question": "\u0d35\u0d40\u0d23 \u0d2a\u0d42\u0d35\u0d4d \u0d0e\u0d34\u0d41\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d06\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d?",
    "answer": "\u0d15\u0d41\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d28\u0d3e\u0d36\u0d3e\u0d7b",
    "status": "9"
  },
  {
    "id": "152",
    "question": "\u0d2e\u0d32\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d33 \u0d2d\u0d3e\u0d37\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d35\u0d4d \u0d06\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d?\t",
    "answer": "\u0d0e\u0d34\u0d41\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1b\u0d7b",
    "status": "9"
  },
  {
    "id": "153",
    "question": "\u0d2d\u0d42\u0d2e\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d05\u0d35\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d36\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d7e \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d38\u0d3f\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d27 \u0d15\u0d25 \u0d0e\u0d34\u0d41\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d06\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d?",
    "answer": "\u0d35\u0d48\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d02 \u0d2e\u0d41\u0d39\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d26\u0d4d \u0d2c\u0d37\u0d40\u0d7c",
    "status": "9"
  },
  {
    "id": "154",
    "question": "\u0d2e\u0d32\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d33\u0d02 \u0d05\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d1f\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d35\u0d4d \u0d06\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d?",
    "answer": "\u0d2c\u0d46\u0d1e\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d2e\u0d3f\u0d7b \u0d2c\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d4d\u0d32\u0d3f",
    "status": "9"
  },
  {
    "id": "155",
    "question": "\u0d35\u0d46\u0d33\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d02 \u0d26\u0d41\u0d03\u0d16\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d41\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d23\u0d40 \u0d24\u0d2e\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d38\u0d32\u0d4d\u0d32\u0d4b \u0d38\u0d41\u0d16\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d26\u0d02, \u0d06\u0d30\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d35\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d7e?",
    "answer": "\u0d05\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d02 \u0d05\u0d1a\u0d41\u0d24\u0d7b \u0d28\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d42\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d30\u0d3f",
    "status": "9"
  },
  {
    "id": "156",
    "question": "\u0d1a\u0d46\u0d31\u0d41\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d1f\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d06\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d15\u0d25\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d2a\u0d47\u0d30\u0d46\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d ?",
    "answer": "\u0d1c\u0d40\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d3e\u0d24 \r\n",
    "status": "9"
  },
  {
    "id": "157",
    "question": "\u0d32\u0d4b\u0d15\u0d38\u0d2d\u0d3e\u0d02\u0d17\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d30\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d36\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d24 \u0d2e\u0d32\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d33 \u0d28\u0d4b\u0d35\u0d32\u0d3f\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d2a\u0d47\u0d30\u0d46\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d ?",
    "answer": "\u0d0e\u0d38\u0d4d \u0d15\u0d46 \u0d2a\u0d4a\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d46\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d1f\u0d4d \r\n",
    "status": "9"
  },
  {
    "id": "158",
    "question": "\u0d28\u0d4b\u0d35\u0d7d \u0d38\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d3f\u0d2e\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d15\u0d41\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d4b\u0d7e: \u0d06\u0d30\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d15\u0d43\u0d24\u0d3f ?\r\n",
    "answer": "\u0d15\u0d46.\u0d38\u0d41\u0d30\u0d47\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d7b\r\n",
    "status": "9"
  },
  {
    "id": "159",
    "question": "\u0d28\u0d4b\u0d35\u0d7d \u0d38\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d3f\u0d2e\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d15\u0d41\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d4b\u0d7e: \u0d06\u0d30\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d15\u0d43\u0d24\u0d3f ?\r\n",
    "answer": "\u0d15\u0d46.\u0d38\u0d41\u0d30\u0d47\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d7b\r\n",
    "status": "4"
  },
  {
    "id": "160",
    "question": "\u0d0e\u0d02.\u0d1f\u0d3f \u0d35\u0d3e\u0d38\u0d41\u0d26\u0d47\u0d35\u0d28\u0d4d \u0d28\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d30\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d.\u0d2a\u0d3f. \u0d2e\u0d41\u0d39\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d26\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d1a\u0d47\u0d30\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d46\u0d3e\u0d34\u0d41\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d2f \u0d28\u0d4b\u0d35\u0d32\u0d4d \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d ?\r\n",
    "answer": "\u0d05\u0d31\u0d2c\u0d3f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d4a\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d4d \r\n",
    "status": "9"
  },
  {
    "id": "161",
    "question": "\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d33\u0d3f\u0d26\u0d3e\u0d38\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d1c\u0d40\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d46 \u0d15\u0d47\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d40\u0d15\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d4d \u0d12.\u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d.\u0d35\u0d3f \u0d0e\u0d34\u0d41\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d2f \u0d26\u0d40\u0d30\u0d4d\u0d18 \u0d15\u0d3e\u0d35\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d02 ?\r\n",
    "answer": "\u0d09\u0d1c\u0d4d\u0d1c\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d3f \r\n",
    "status": "9"
  },
  {
    "id": "162",
    "question": ". \" \u0d35\u0d46\u0d33\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d02 \u0d26\u0d41\u0d16\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d41\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d23\u0d40\u0d24\u0d2e\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d38\u0d32\u0d4d\u0d32\u0d4b \u0d38\u0d41\u0d16\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d26\u0d02\" \u0d06\u0d30\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d47\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d \u0d08 \u0d35\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d33\u0d4d?\r\n",
    "answer": "\u0d05\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d02 \r\n",
    "status": "9"
  },
  {
    "id": "163",
    "question": "\u0d15\u0d47\u0d30\u0d33 \u0d38\u0d3e\u0d39\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f \u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d35\u0d30\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d15\u0d15 \u0d38\u0d39\u0d15\u0d30\u0d23 \u0d38\u0d02\u0d17\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d2a\u0d41\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d15\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d28\u0d36\u0d3e\u0d32\u0d15\u0d33\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d2a\u0d47\u0d30\u0d46\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d ?\r\n",
    "answer": "\u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d \u0d2c\u0d3f \u0d0e\u0d38\u0d4d \r\n",
    "status": "9"
  },
  {
    "id": "164",
    "question": "\"\u0d15\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4a\u0d2f\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d \" \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d15\u0d3e\u0d35\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d38\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d39\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d15\u0d30\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3e \u0d35\u0d4d \u0d06\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d ?\r\n",
    "answer": "\u0d35\u0d48\u0d32\u0d4b\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d33\u0d4d\u0d33\u0d3f \r\n",
    "status": "9"
  },
  {
    "id": "165",
    "question": "\u0d15\u0d41\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d28\u0d3e\u0d36\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d46 \"\u0d35\u0d40\u0d23\u0d2a\u0d42\u0d35\u0d4d\" \u0d06\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d02 \u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d38\u0d3f\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d27\u0d40\u0d15\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d06\u0d28\u0d41\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d32\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d30\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d41 ?\r\n",
    "answer": "\u0d2e\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d35\u0d3e\u0d26\u0d3f \r\n",
    "status": "9"
  },
  {
    "id": "166",
    "question": "\u0d0e\u0d02.\u0d1f\u0d3f. \u0d35\u0d3e\u0d38\u0d41\u0d26\u0d47\u0d35\u0d28\u0d4d \u0d28\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d30\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \"\u0d28\u0d3e\u0d32\u0d41\u0d15\u0d46\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d4d\" \u0d06\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d02 \u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d38\u0d3f\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d27\u0d40\u0d15\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d41 \u0d35\u0d30\u0d4d\u0d37\u0d3e\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d ?\r\n",
    "answer": "1958 \r\n",
    "status": "9"
  },
  {
    "id": "167",
    "question": "\u0d26\u0d47\u0d35\u0d15\u0d3f \u0d28\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d2f\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d19\u0d4b\u0d1f\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d06\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d15\u0d25\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d2a\u0d47\u0d30\u0d46\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d ?\r\n",
    "answer": "\u0d28\u0d37\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d2c\u0d4b\u0d27\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d19\u0d33\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4d\u0d32\u0d3e\u0d24\u0d46 \u0d12\u0d30\u0d41 \u0d05\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d30\u0d4d\u0d1c\u0d4d\u0d1c\u0d28\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d06\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d15\u0d25 \r\n",
    "status": "9"
  },
  {
    "id": "168",
    "question": ". \"\u0d35\u0d3e\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d41\u0d39\u0d3e\u0d30\" \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d1a\u0d46\u0d31\u0d41\u0d15\u0d25\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d15\u0d30\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d35\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d4d ?\r\n",
    "answer": "\u0d38\u0d3f \u0d35\u0d3f \u0d36\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d40\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d2e\u0d28\u0d4d \r\n",
    "status": "9"
  },
  {
    "id": "169",
    "question": "\"\u0d15\u0d4b\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d28\u0d4d\" \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d24\u0d42\u0d32\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d3e \u0d28\u0d3e\u0d2e\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4d \u0d05\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d46\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d0e\u0d34\u0d41\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d41\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d28\u0d4d \u0d06\u0d30\u0d4d ?\r\n",
    "answer": "\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d35\u0d3f \u0d05\u0d2f\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d28\u0d4d \r\n",
    "status": "9"
  },
  {
    "id": "170",
    "question": ". \"\u0d15\u0d41\u0d31\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\" \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d15\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d15\u0d30\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d35\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d4d ?\r\n",
    "answer": "\u0d15\u0d1f\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d28\u0d3f\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f \u0d30\u0d3e\u0d2e\u0d15\u0d43\u0d37\u0d4d\u0d23\u0d28\u0d4d \r\n",
    "status": "9"
  },
  {
    "id": "171",
    "question": "\"\u0d07\u0d24\u0d41 \u0d2d\u0d42\u0d2e\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d\" \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d28\u0d3e\u0d1f\u0d15\u0d02 \u0d30\u0d1a\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d4d ?\r\n",
    "answer": "\u0d15\u0d46 \u0d1f\u0d3f \u0d2e\u0d41\u0d39\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d26\u0d4d \r\n",
    "status": "9"
  },
  {
    "id": "172",
    "question": "\u0d2e\u0d39\u0d3e\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d3e \u0d17\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d27\u0d3f \u0d06\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d15\u0d25 \u0d30\u0d1a\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d2d\u0d3e\u0d37\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d ?\r\n",
    "answer": "\u0d17\u0d41\u0d1c\u0d31\u0d3e\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f \r\n",
    "status": "9"
  },
  {
    "id": "173",
    "question": "\"\u0d0e\u0d32\u0d3f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d02\" \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d1a\u0d32\u0d1a\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d38\u0d02\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d27\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d15\u0d28\u0d4d \u0d06\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d ?\r\n",
    "answer": "\u0d05\u0d1f\u0d42\u0d30\u0d4d \u0d17\u0d4b\u0d2a\u0d3e\u0d32\u0d15\u0d43\u0d37\u0d4d\u0d23\u0d28\u0d4d \r\n",
    "status": "9"
  },
  {
    "id": "174",
    "question": "\u0d0f\u0d24\u0d41 \u0d15\u0d43\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d2d\u0d3e\u0d17\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d \u0d2d\u0d17\u0d35\u0d26\u0d4d \u0d17\u0d40\u0d24 ?\r\n",
    "answer": "\u0d2e\u0d39\u0d3e\u0d2d\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d24\u0d02 \r\n",
    "status": "9"
  },
  {
    "id": "175",
    "question": "18. \r\n\r\n\"\u0d26\u0d36\u0d15\u0d41\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d30 \u0d1a\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d02\" \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d38\u0d02\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d43\u0d24 \u0d15\u0d43\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d15\u0d30\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3e \u0d35\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d ?\r\n",
    "answer": "\u0d26\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d21\u0d3f \r\n",
    "status": "9"
  },
  {
    "id": "176",
    "question": "\u0d28\u0d1f\u0d28\u0d4d \u0d17\u0d4b\u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4d \"\u0d2d\u0d30\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d05\u0d35\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d4d\u0d21\u0d4d\u0d4d\" \u0d15\u0d3f\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d1a\u0d32\u0d1a\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d05\u0d2d\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d2f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d ?\r\n",
    "answer": "\u0d15\u0d4a\u0d1f\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d47\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d02 \r\n",
    "status": "9"
  },
  {
    "id": "177",
    "question": "\u0d38\u0d3f. \u0d35\u0d3f \u0d30\u0d3e\u0d2e\u0d28\u0d4d \u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d33\u0d4d\u0d33 \u0d30\u0d1a\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a \u0d38\u0d3e\u0d2e\u0d42\u0d39\u0d3f\u0d15 \u0d28\u0d4b\u0d35\u0d32\u0d4d \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d ?\r\n",
    "answer": "\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d47\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d2e\u0d43\u0d24\u0d02 \r\n",
    "status": "9"
  },
  {
    "id": "178",
    "question": ". \"\u0d38\u0d42\u0d30\u0d3f \u0d28\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d42\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d3e\u0d1f\u0d4d\" \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d28\u0d4b\u0d35\u0d32\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d15\u0d25\u0d3e\u0d2a\u0d3e\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d ?\r\n",
    "answer": "\u0d07\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d26\u0d41\u0d32\u0d47\u0d16 \r\n",
    "status": "9"
  },
  {
    "id": "179",
    "question": "\"\u0d15\u0d47\u0d30\u0d33 \u0d15\u0d32\u0d3e\u0d2e\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d21\u0d32\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d46\" \u0d06\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d02 \u0d0e\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d1f\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d ?\r\n",
    "answer": "\u0d1a\u0d46\u0d31\u0d41\u0d24\u0d41\u0d30\u0d41\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f \r\n",
    "status": "9"
  },
  {
    "id": "180",
    "question": ". \"\u0d05\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2e\" \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d31\u0d37\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d28\u0d4d \u0d28\u0d4b\u0d35\u0d32\u0d4d \u0d0e\u0d34\u0d41\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d06\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d ?\r\n",
    "answer": "\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d15\u0d38\u0d3f\u0d02\u0d17\u0d4b\u0d30\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3f \r\n",
    "status": "9"
  },
  {
    "id": "181",
    "question": "\"\u0d39\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d38\u0d3e\u0d26\u0d4d \u0d1a\u0d4c\u0d30\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d2f\" \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d38\u0d02\u0d17\u0d40\u0d24\u0d4b\u0d2a\u0d15\u0d30\u0d23\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d \u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d35\u0d40\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d02 \u0d28\u0d47\u0d1f\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d24\u0d4d ?\r\n",
    "answer": "\u0d2a\u0d41\u0d32\u0d4d\u0d32\u0d3e\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d41\u0d34\u0d32\u0d4d \r\n",
    "status": "9"
  },
  {
    "id": "182",
    "question": "\"\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d2e\u0d34\" \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d15\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d38\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d39\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d02 \u0d06\u0d30\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d47\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d ?\r\n",
    "answer": "\u0d38\u0d41\u0d17\u0d24\u0d15\u0d41\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d3f \r\n",
    "status": "9"
  },
  {
    "id": "183",
    "question": "\"\u0d15\u0d47\u0d30\u0d33\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d2a\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d37\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d33\u0d4d\" \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d2a\u0d41\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d15\u0d02 \u0d0e\u0d34\u0d41\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d06\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d ?\r\n",
    "answer": "\u0d07\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d26\u0d41\u0d1a\u0d42\u0d21\u0d28\u0d4d (\u0d38\u0d32\u0d3f\u0d02 \u0d05\u0d32\u0d3f)\r\n",
    "status": "9"
  },
  {
    "id": "184",
    "question": ". \"\u0d06\u0d28\u0d35\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d3f \u0d30\u0d3e\u0d2e\u0d28\u0d4d \u0d28\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d30\u0d4d\" \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d15\u0d25\u0d3e\u0d2a\u0d3e\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d46 \u0d38\u0d43\u0d37\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a \u0d0e\u0d34\u0d41\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d41\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d28\u0d4d \u0d06\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d ?\r\n",
    "answer": "\u0d35\u0d48\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d02 \u0d2e\u0d41\u0d39\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d26\u0d4d \u0d2c\u0d37\u0d40\u0d30\u0d4d \r\n",
    "status": "9"
  },
  {
    "id": "185",
    "question": "\"\u0d17\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d27\u0d3f\" \u0d38\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d3f\u0d2e\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4d \u0d17\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d27\u0d3f\u0d1c\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d2d\u0d3e\u0d17\u0d02 \u0d05\u0d2d\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a \u0d28\u0d1f\u0d28\u0d4d \u0d06\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d30\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d41 ?\r\n",
    "answer": "\u0d2c\u0d46\u0d28\u0d4d \u0d15\u0d3f\u0d02\u0d17\u0d4d\u0d38\u0d32\u0d3f \r\n",
    "status": "9"
  },
  {
    "id": "186",
    "question": "\u0d06\u0d31\u0d2e\u0d41\u0d33 \u0d35\u0d33\u0d4d\u0d33\u0d02\u0d15\u0d33\u0d3f \u0d28\u0d1f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d28\u0d26\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d ?\r\n \r\n",
    "answer": "\u0d2a\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2a \r\n",
    "status": "2"
  },
  {
    "id": "187",
    "question": "\u0d0f. \u0d15\u0d46 \u0d17\u0d4b\u0d2a\u0d32\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d28\u0d47\u0d24\u0d43\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d35\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4d \u0d2e\u0d32\u0d2c\u0d3e\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4d \u0d28\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d4d \u0d2e\u0d26\u0d3f\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d36\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d47\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4d 750\u0d28\u0d3e\u0d34\u0d3f\u0d15 \u0d28\u0d1f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d4d 32 \u0d2a\u0d47\u0d30\u0d4d \u0d1a\u0d47\u0d30\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d4d \u0d28\u0d1f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d2f \u0d1c\u0d3e\u0d25 \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d41 \u0d2a\u0d47\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d \u0d05\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d46\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d24\u0d4d ?\n",
    "answer": "\u0d2a\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d3f\u0d23\u0d3f \u0d1c\u0d3e\u0d25....",
    "status": "2"
  },
  {
    "id": "188",
    "question": "\u0d06\u0d30\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d06\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d15\u0d25\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d '\u0d0f\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d2a\u0d25\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d7b \u0d1e\u0d3e\u0d7b' ?\r\n",
    "answer": "\u0d1c\u0d2f\u0d1a\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d7b\r\n",
    "status": "9"
  },
  {
    "id": "189",
    "question": "\u0d08 \u0d35\u0d7c\u0d37\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d46 \u0d15\u0d4b\u0d2e\u0d7a\u0d35\u0d46\u0d7d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d1a\u0d46\u0d31\u0d41\u0d15\u0d25\u0d3e \u0d2a\u0d41\u0d30\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d02 \u0d32\u0d2d\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a \u0d07\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d7b \u0d0e\u0d34\u0d41\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d41\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d7b?\r\n",
    "answer": "\u0d2a\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d36\u0d7c \u0d15\u0d41\u0d7d\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d7c\u0d23\u0d3f (\u0d15\u0d57 \u0d06\u0d7b\u0d21\u0d4d \u0d15\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d28\u0d3f \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d15\u0d43\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d \u0d2a\u0d41\u0d30\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d02 \u0d32\u0d2d\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d24\u0d4d)\r\n",
    "status": "9"
  },
  {
    "id": "190",
    "question": "\u0d28\u0d46\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d2e\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d3f \u0d35\u0d47\u0d23\u0d41 \u0d38\u0d02\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d27\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d02 \u0d1a\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d4d\u0d24 \u0d38\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d3f\u0d2e ?\r\n",
    "answer": "\u0d2a\u0d42\u0d30\u0d02\r\n",
    "status": "4"
  },
  {
    "id": "191",
    "question": "\u0d2e\u0d32\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d33\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d06\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f \u0d38\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d3f\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4b\u0d2a\u0d4d \u0d1a\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d02 ?\r\n",
    "answer": "\u0d24\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d4b\u0d33\u0d3f \u0d05\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d41\r\n",
    "status": "4"
  },
  {
    "id": "192",
    "question": "\u0d2a\u0d4a\u0d7b\u0d15\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d02 \u0d35\u0d7c\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3f \u0d15\u0d25\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d38\u0d02\u0d2d\u0d3e\u0d37\u0d23\u0d35\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d30\u0d1a\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a \u0d06\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f \u0d38\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d3f\u0d2e ?\r\n",
    "answer": "\u0d28\u0d35\u0d32\u0d4b\u0d15\u0d02",
    "status": "4"
  },
  {
    "id": "193",
    "question": "\u0d28\u0d3f\u0d34\u0d32\u0d3e\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d02 \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d38\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d3f\u0d2e \u0d38\u0d02\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d27\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d02 \u0d1a\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d24\u0d4d ?\r\n",
    "answer": "\u0d28\u0d1f\u0d3f \u0d37\u0d40\u0d32\r\n",
    "status": "4"
  },
  {
    "id": "194",
    "question": "\u0d15\u0d41\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d3f \u0d38\u0d02\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d27\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d02 \u0d1a\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d24\u0d4d?\r\n\r\n",
    "answer": "\u0d05\u0d30\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d26\u0d7b",
    "status": "4"
  },
  {
    "id": "195",
    "question": "\u0d2e\u0d32\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d33\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d06\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f \u0d31\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d32\u0d3f\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d \u0d38\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d3f\u0d2e\r\n",
    "answer": "\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d42\u0d38\u0d4d \u0d2a\u0d47\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d7c \u0d2c\u0d4b\u0d2f\u0d4d\r\n",
    "status": "4"
  },
  {
    "id": "196",
    "question": "\u0d2c\u0d37\u0d40\u0d7c \u0d24\u0d3f\u0d30\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d25 \u0d0e\u0d34\u0d41\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d2f \u0d06\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f \u0d38\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d3f\u0d2e\r\n",
    "answer": "\u0d2d\u0d3e\u0d7c\u0d17\u0d35\u0d40\u0d28\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d2f\u0d02\r\n",
    "status": "4"
  },
  {
    "id": "197",
    "question": "\u0d2a\u0d36\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d3e\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d32 \u0d38\u0d02\u0d17\u0d40\u0d24\u0d02 \u0d2a\u0d42\u0d7c\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d23\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d3f \u0d12\u0d34\u0d3f\u0d35\u0d3e\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3f \u0d38\u0d02\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d27\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d02 \u0d1a\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d4d\u0d24 \u0d1a\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d02?\r\n\r\n",
    "answer": "\u0d15\u0d4a\u0d1f\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d47\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d02",
    "status": "4"
  },
  {
    "id": "198",
    "question": "\u0d09\u0d7e\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d1f\u0d7d \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d38\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d3f\u0d2e\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d38\u0d02\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d27\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d15\u0d7b?\r\n",
    "answer": "\u0d15\u0d46.\u0d1c\u0d3f.\u0d1c\u0d4b\u0d7c\u0d1c\u0d4d\u0d1c\u0d4d\r\n",
    "status": "4"
  },
  {
    "id": "199",
    "question": "\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d23\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d46 \u0d05\u0d1f\u0d3f\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3f \u0d05\u0d30\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d26\u0d7b \u0d38\u0d02\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d27\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d02 \u0d1a\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d4d\u0d24 \u0d1a\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d02?\r\n\r\n",
    "answer": "\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d1e\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d28\u0d38\u0d40\u0d24",
    "status": "4"
  },
  {
    "id": "200",
    "question": "\u0d38\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d3f\u0d2e\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3f\u0d2f \u0d06\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f \u0d38\u0d3e\u0d39\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f \u0d15\u0d43\u0d24\u0d3f.?\r\n",
    "answer": "\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d7c\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d21\u0d35\u0d7c\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2e\r\n",
    "status": "4"
  },
  {
    "id": "201",
    "question": "\u0d28\u0d3f\u0d7c\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d32 \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d38\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d3f\u0d2e\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d3f \u0d17\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d30\u0d1a\u0d28 \u0d28\u0d1f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d06\u0d30\u0d4d?\r\n",
    "answer": "\u0d1c\u0d3f.\u0d36\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d30\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d41\u0d31\u0d41\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d4d\r\n",
    "status": "4"
  },
  {
    "id": "202",
    "question": "\u0d13\u0d1f\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d7d \u0d28\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d4d \u0d38\u0d02\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d27\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d02 \u0d1a\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d24\u0d4d?\r\n",
    "answer": "\u0d15\u0d46.\u0d0e\u0d38\u0d4d.\u0d38\u0d47\u0d24\u0d41\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d27\u0d35\u0d7b\r\n",
    "status": "4"
  },
  {
    "id": "203",
    "question": "\u0d38\u0d42\u0d2b\u0d3f \u0d2a\u0d31\u0d1e\u0d4d\u0d1e \u0d15\u0d25 \u0d38\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d3f\u0d2e\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3f\u0d2f \u0d38\u0d02\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d27\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d15\u0d7b?\r\n",
    "answer": "\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d28\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d26\u0d7b\r\n",
    "status": "4"
  },
  {
    "id": "204",
    "question": "\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d3e\u0d35\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d38\u0d3e\u0d39\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d02 \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d0e\u0d02.\u0d1f\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d15\u0d43\u0d24\u0d3f \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d2e\u0d47\u0d16\u0d32\u0d2f\u0d46\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d41\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d?\r\n",
    "answer": "\u0d38\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d3f\u0d2e\r\n",
    "status": "4"
  },
  {
    "id": "205",
    "question": "\u0d38\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d3f\u0d2e\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d07\u0d1f\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d19\u0d7e \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d15\u0d43\u0d24\u0d3f \u0d06\u0d30\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d47\u0d24\u0d4d?\r\n",
    "answer": "\u0d38\u0d3f.\u0d35\u0d3f.\u0d2c\u0d3e\u0d32\u0d15\u0d43\u0d37\u0d4d\u0d23\u0d7b\r\n",
    "status": "4"
  },
  {
    "id": "206",
    "question": "\u0d38\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d3f\u0d2e \u0d38\u0d02\u0d2c\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d27\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d3f \u0d05\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d2c\u0d7c \u0d15\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d3f\u0d7d \u0d30\u0d1a\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a \u0d15\u0d24\u0d3f ?\r\n",
    "answer": "\u0d07\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d19\u0d28\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d12\u0d30\u0d41 \u0d38\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d3f\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d32\u0d02\r\n",
    "status": "4"
  },
  {
    "id": "207",
    "question": "\u0d38\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d3f\u0d2e\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d30\u0d3e\u0d37\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d40\u0d2f\u0d02 \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d15\u0d43\u0d24\u0d3f \u0d30\u0d1a\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d24\u0d4d?\r\n",
    "answer": "\u0d15\u0d46.\u0d30\u0d35\u0d40\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d7b (\u0d1a\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24 \u0d30\u0d35\u0d3f )\r\n",
    "status": "4"
  },
  {
    "id": "208",
    "question": "\u0d35\u0d3f.\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d1c \u0d15\u0d43\u0d37\u0d4d\u0d23\u0d7b \u0d30\u0d1a\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a \u0d38\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d3f\u0d2e\u0d3e \u0d17\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d02?\r\n",
    "answer": "\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d34\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d05\u0d36\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\r\n",
    "status": "4"
  },
  {
    "id": "209",
    "question": "\u0d35\u0d3e\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d28\u0d4b\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d38\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d3f\u0d2e \u0d15\u0d43\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d0e\u0d21\u0d3f\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d7c?\r\n",
    "answer": "\u0d0e\u0d02.\u0d15\u0d46.\u0d38\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d41\r\n",
    "status": "4"
  },
  {
    "id": "210",
    "question": "\u0d06\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d3f \u0d2e\u0d32\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d33 \u0d38\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d3f\u0d2e\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d7d \u0d05\u0d2d\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a \u0d38\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d40?\r\n",
    "answer": "\u0d35\u0d1f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d47 \u0d15\u0d41\u0d31\u0d41\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d41 \u0d15\u0d3e\u0d35\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2e\r\n",
    "status": "4"
  },
  {
    "id": "211",
    "question": "\u0d12\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d1f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d3e \u0d38\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d3f\u0d2e\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d38\u0d02\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d27\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d15\u0d7b?\r\n",
    "answer": "\u0d05\u0d30\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d26\u0d7b \r\n",
    "status": "4"
  },
  {
    "id": "212",
    "question": "\u0d32\u0d4b\u0d15\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d46 \u0d06\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f \u0d2b\u0d40\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d7c \u0d38\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d3f\u0d2e? \r\n",
    "answer": "\u0d26\u0d3f \u0d17\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d47\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d \u0d31\u0d4b\u0d2c\u0d31\u0d3f\r\n",
    "status": "4"
  },
  {
    "id": "213",
    "question": "\u0d2e\u0d32\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d33 \u0d38\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d3f\u0d2e\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d06\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f \u0d35\u0d28\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d3e \u0d38\u0d02\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d27\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d15?\r\n",
    "answer": "\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d1c\u0d2f\u0d7c\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d32\r\n",
    "status": "4"
  },
  {
    "id": "214",
    "question": "\u0d2e\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d1f \u0d30\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d35\u0d7c\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d38\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d3f\u0d2e\u0d3e \u0d28\u0d3f\u0d30\u0d41\u0d2a\u0d23\u0d17\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d02 \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d4d?\r\n",
    "answer": "\u0d1a\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d02, \u0d1a\u0d32\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d02\r\n",
    "status": "4"
  },
  {
    "id": "215",
    "question": "\u0d38\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d3f\u0d2e\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d32\u0d4b\u0d15\u0d02 \u0d06\u0d30\u0d4d \u0d0e\u0d34\u0d41\u0d24\u0d3f?\r\n",
    "answer": "\u0d05\u0d1f\u0d42\u0d7c \u0d17\u0d4b\u0d2a\u0d3e\u0d32\u0d15\u0d43\u0d37\u0d4d\u0d23\u0d7b\r\n",
    "status": "4"
  },
  {
    "id": "216",
    "question": "\u0d1a\u0d47\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d1a\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d7d \u0d05\u0d2d\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a \u0d15\u0d35\u0d3f?\r\n\r\n",
    "answer": "\u0d35\u0d2f\u0d32\u0d3e\u0d7c",
    "status": "4"
  },
  {
    "id": "217",
    "question": "\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d7b \u0d2b\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d3f\u0d02 \u0d2b\u0d46\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d35\u0d32\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d47\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4d \u0d24\u0d3f\u0d30\u0d1e\u0d4d\u0d1e\u0d46\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d46\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f \u0d06\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d2e\u0d32\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d33 \u0d1a\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d02?\r\n",
    "answer": "\u0d37\u0d3e\u0d1c\u0d3f.\u0d0e\u0d7b.\u0d15\u0d30\u0d41\u0d23\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d38\u0d4d\u0d35\u0d02\r\n",
    "status": "4"
  },
  {
    "id": "218",
    "question": "\u0d12\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d7c \u0d2e\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d38\u0d30\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d \u0d28\u0d3f\u0d7c\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d26\u0d47\u0d36\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d46\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f \u0d06\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d2e\u0d32\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d33 \u0d1a\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d02?\r\n",
    "answer": "\u0d17\u0d41\u0d30\u0d41\r\n",
    "status": "4"
  },
  {
    "id": "219",
    "question": "\u0d2e\u0d32\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d33 \u0d38\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d3f\u0d2e\u0d2f\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4d \u0d38\u0d02\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d3e\u0d28 \u0d05\u0d35\u0d3e\u0d7c\u0d21\u0d4d \u0d0f\u0d7c\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d46\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d2f \u0d35\u0d7c\u0d37\u0d02? \u0d06\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f \u0d05\u0d35\u0d3e\u0d7c\u0d21\u0d41\u0d1a\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d02?\r\n",
    "answer": "1969, \u0d15\u0d41\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d38\u0d02\u0d2d\u0d35\u0d02\r\n",
    "status": "4"
  },
  {
    "id": "220",
    "question": "\u0d2a\u0d41\u0d32\u0d3f\u0d1c\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d02 \u0d28\u0d3e\u0d1f\u0d15 \u0d15\u0d7c\u0d24\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d35\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d4d?\r\n",
    "answer": "\u0d0e\u0d7b.\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d2d\u0d3e\u0d15\u0d30\u0d7b\r\n",
    "status": "4"
  },
  {
    "id": "221",
    "question": "\u0d07\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d19\u0d28\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d12\u0d30\u0d41 \u0d38\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d3f\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d32\u0d02\r\n",
    "answer": "\u0d05\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d2c\u0d7c \u0d15\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d3f\u0d7d\r\n",
    "status": "4"
  },
  {
    "id": "222",
    "question": "\u0d38\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d3f\u0d2e\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d07\u0d1f\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d19\u0d7e\r\n",
    "answer": "\u0d38\u0d3f \u0d35\u0d3f.\u0d2c\u0d3e\u0d32\u0d15\u0d43\u0d37\u0d4d\u0d23\u0d7b\r\n",
    "status": "4"
  },
  {
    "id": "223",
    "question": "\u0d2e\u0d32\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d33 \u0d38\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d3f\u0d2e\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d35\u0d4d -\u0d1c\u0d46 \r\n",
    "answer": "\u0d38\u0d3f \u0d26\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d47\u0d7d\r\n",
    "status": "4"
  },
  {
    "id": "224",
    "question": "\u0d06\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d46 \u0d2e\u0d32\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d33 \u0d38\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d3f\u0d2e -\r\n",
    "answer": "\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d17\u0d24\u0d15\u0d41\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d7b\r\n",
    "status": "4"
  },
  {
    "id": "225",
    "question": "\u0d38\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d3f\u0d2e \u0d06\u0d15\u0d3f\u0d2f \u0d06\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f \u0d38\u0d3e\u0d39\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f \u0d15\u0d43\u0d24\u0d3f -",
    "answer": "\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d7c\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d35\u0d7c\u0d2e(1933)\r\n",
    "status": "4"
  },
  {
    "id": "226",
    "question": "\u0d2e\u0d32\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d33\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d06\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f \u0d36\u0d2c\u0d4d\u0d26 \u0d1a\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d02 -\r\n",
    "answer": "\u0d2c\u0d3e\u0d32\u0d7b(1938)\r\n",
    "status": "4"
  },
  {
    "id": "227",
    "question": "\u0d2e\u0d32\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d33 \u0d38\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d3f\u0d2e\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d7d \u0d06\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d02\r\n\u0d38\u0d02\u0d38\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a \u0d35\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f -",
    "answer": "\u0d06\u0d32\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d3f\r\n\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d38\u0d46\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d (\u0d2c\u0d3e\u0d32\u0d7b 1938)",
    "status": "4"
  },
  {
    "id": "228",
    "question": "\u0d2e\u0d32\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d33 \u0d38\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d3f\u0d2e\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d7d \u0d06\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d02\r\n\u0d38\u0d02\u0d38\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a \u0d35\u0d3e\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4d -",
    "answer": "\u0d39\u0d32\u0d4b \u0d2e\u0d3f\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d7c\r\n",
    "status": "4"
  },
  {
    "id": "229",
    "question": "\u0d06\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d02 \u0d38\u0d02\u0d38\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a \u0d28\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d15 \u0d28\u0d1f\u0d7b -",
    "answer": "\u0d15\u0d46\r\n\u0d15\u0d46 \u0d05\u0d30\u0d42\u0d7c\r\n",
    "status": "4"
  },
  {
    "id": "230",
    "question": "\u0d06\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d02 \u0d38\u0d02\u0d38\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a \u0d28\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d3e \u0d28\u0d1f\u0d3f -\r\n",
    "answer": "\u0d0e\u0d02 \u0d15\u0d46 \u0d15\u0d2e\u0d32\u0d02\r\n",
    "status": "4"
  },
  {
    "id": "231",
    "question": "\u0d2e\u0d32\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d33\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d06\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f \u0d15\u0d33\u0d7c \u0d1a\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d02 -\r\n",
    "answer": "\u0d15\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d02 \u0d2c\u0d46\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a \u0d15\u0d4b\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d4d(1961)\r\n",
    "status": "4"
  },
  {
    "id": "232",
    "question": "\u0d2e\u0d32\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d33\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d06\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f \u0d2a\u0d41\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d23 \u0d1a\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d02 -",
    "answer": "\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d39\u0d4d\u0d32\u0d3e\u0d26 (1941)",
    "status": "4"
  },
  {
    "id": "233",
    "question": "\u0d2e\u0d32\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d33\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d06\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f \u0d2c\u0d4b\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d38\u0d4d \u0d13\u0d2b\u0d40\u0d38\u0d4d \u0d39\u0d3f\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d \u0d1a\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d02 -\r\n",
    "answer": "\u0d1c\u0d40\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d24 \u0d28\u0d57\u0d15 (1951)\r\n",
    "status": "4"
  },
  {
    "id": "234",
    "question": "\u0d2e\u0d32\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d33\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d06\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f \u0d28\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d4b \u0d31\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d32\u0d3f\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d \u0d1a\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d02 -\r\n",
    "answer": "\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d42\u0d38\u0d4d \u0d2a\u0d47\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d7c \u0d2c\u0d4b\u0d2f\u0d4d (1955)\r\n",
    "status": "4"
  },
  {
    "id": "235",
    "question": "\u0d2e\u0d32\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d33\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d06\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f \u0d38\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d3f\u0d2e \u0d38\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4b\u0d2a\u0d4d \u0d1a\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d02 -\r\n",
    "answer": "\u0d24\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d4b\u0d33\u0d3f \u0d05\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d41 (1978)\r\n",
    "status": "4"
  },
  {
    "id": "236",
    "question": "\u0d2e\u0d32\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d33\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d06\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f 70mm \u0d1a\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d02 -",
    "answer": "\u0d2a\u0d1f\u0d2f\u0d4b\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d02 (1982)",
    "status": "4"
  },
  {
    "id": "237",
    "question": "\u0d2e\u0d32\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d33\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d2a\u0d1f\u0d2f\u0d4b\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d02 \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d3e \u0d1a\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\r\n\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d47\u0d30\u0d15\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d2f \u0d2b\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d1e\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d4d \u0d28\u0d4b\u0d35\u0d7d-",
    "answer": "\u0d26\u0d3f \u0d15\u0d4c\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d4d\r\n\u0d13\u0d2b\u0d4d \u0d2e\u0d4b\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d3f \u0d15\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d4b\r\n",
    "status": "4"
  },
  {
    "id": "238",
    "question": "\u0d2e\u0d32\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d33\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d06\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f 3D \u0d1a\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d02 -\r\n",
    "answer": "\u0d2e\u0d48 \u0d21\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d7c \u0d15\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d3e\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d7b (1984)\r\n",
    "status": "4"
  },
  {
    "id": "239",
    "question": "\u0d2e\u0d32\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d33\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d06\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f \u0d21\u0d4b\u0d7e\u0d2c\u0d3f \u0d38\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d40\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d4a \u0d1a\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d02 -\r\n",
    "answer": "\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d32\u0d3e\u0d2a\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d3f (1996)\r\n",
    "status": "4"
  },
  {
    "id": "240",
    "question": "\u0d2e\u0d32\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d33\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d06\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f \u0d21\u0d3f \u0d1f\u0d3f \u0d0e\u0d38\u0d4d \u0d1a\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d02 -\r\n",
    "answer": "\u0d2e\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4d\u0d32\u0d47\u0d28\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d02 \u0d38\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d3e\u0d7c\u0d38\u0d4d(2000)\r\n",
    "status": "4"
  },
  {
    "id": "241",
    "question": "\u0d2e\u0d32\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d33\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d06\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f \u0d1c\u0d28\u0d15\u0d40\u0d2f \u0d38\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d3f\u0d2e -",
    "answer": "\u0d05\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2e \u0d05\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d7b\r\n( 1986)\r\n",
    "status": "4"
  },
  {
    "id": "242",
    "question": "\u0d2e\u0d32\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d33\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d06\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f sponsered \u0d38\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d3f\u0d2e -",
    "answer": "\u0d2e\u0d15\u0d7e\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d4d\r\n(2005)\r\n",
    "status": "4"
  },
  {
    "id": "243",
    "question": "\u0d2e\u0d32\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d33\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d06\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f \u0d21\u0d3f\u0d1c\u0d3f\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d7d \u0d38\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d3f\u0d2e -\r\n",
    "answer": "\u0d2e\u0d42\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d3e\u0d2e\u0d24\u0d4a\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d7e (2006)\r\n",
    "status": "4"
  },
  {
    "id": "244",
    "question": "\u0d2a\u0d42\u0d30\u0d4d\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d23\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d14\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d21\u0d4b\u0d7c \u0d7d\r\n\u0d1a\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d40\u0d15\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a \u0d06\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f \u0d2e\u0d32\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d33 \u0d38\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d3f\u0d2e-",
    "answer": "\u0d13\u0d33\u0d35\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d24\u0d40\u0d30\u0d35\u0d41\u0d02 (1970)\r\n",
    "status": "4"
  },
  {
    "id": "245",
    "question": "\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d38\u0d3f\u0d21\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d35\u0d46\u0d33\u0d4d\u0d33\u0d3f\u0d2e\u0d46\u0d21\u0d7d\r\n\u0d28\u0d47\u0d1f\u0d3f\u0d2f \u0d06\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f \u0d2e\u0d32\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d33 \u0d1a\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d02 -\r\n",
    "answer": "\u0d28\u0d40\u0d32\u0d15\u0d41\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d7d (1954)\r\n",
    "status": "4"
  },
  {
    "id": "246",
    "question": "\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d38\u0d3f\u0d21\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d38\u0d4d\u0d35\u0d7c\u0d23 \u0d2e\u0d46\u0d21\u0d7d\r\n\u0d28\u0d47\u0d1f\u0d3f\u0d2f \u0d06\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f \u0d2e\u0d32\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d33 \u0d1a\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d02 -",
    "answer": "\u0d1a\u0d46\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d40\u0d7b\r\n",
    "status": "4"
  },
  {
    "id": "247",
    "question": "\u0d17\u0d3e\u0d28 \u0d30\u0d1a\u0d28\u0d2f\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4d \u0d26\u0d47\u0d36\u0d40\u0d2f \u0d05\u0d35\u0d3e\u0d7c\u0d21\u0d4d \u0d28\u0d47\u0d1f\u0d3f\u0d2f\r\n\u0d06\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f \u0d2e\u0d32\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d33\u0d3f -",
    "answer": "\u0d35\u0d2f\u0d32\u0d3e\u0d7c\r\n",
    "status": "4"
  },
  {
    "id": "248",
    "question": "\u0d13\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d7c \u0d2a\u0d41\u0d30\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\r\n\u0d28\u0d3f\u0d30\u0d4d\u0d26\u0d47\u0d36\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d2a\u0d46\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f \u0d06\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f \u0d2e\u0d32\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d33\r\n\u0d1a\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d02-",
    "answer": "\u0d17\u0d41\u0d30\u0d41 (1997)\r\n",
    "status": "4"
  },
  {
    "id": "249",
    "question": "\u0d2e\u0d32\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d33\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d06\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f \u0d2b\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d3f\u0d02 \u0d38\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d41\u0d21\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d4b -",
    "answer": "\u0d09\u0d26\u0d2f (1948)",
    "status": "4"
  },
  {
    "id": "250",
    "question": "\u0d2e\u0d32\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d33\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d06\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f \u0d2b\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d3f\u0d02 \u0d38\u0d4a\u0d38\u0d48\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d3f -\r\n",
    "answer": "\u0d1a\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d32\u0d47\u0d16 (1964)\r\n",
    "status": "4"
  },
  {
    "id": "251",
    "question": "\u0d2a\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d36\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d40 \u0d28\u0d47\u0d1f\u0d3f\u0d2f \u0d06\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f \u0d2e\u0d32\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d33 \u0d28\u0d1f\u0d7b -\r\n",
    "answer": "\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d41\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d36\u0d3f \u0d38\u0d41\u0d15\u0d41\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d7b \u0d28\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d7c(1973)\r\n",
    "status": "4"
  },
  {
    "id": "252",
    "question": "\u0d2e\u0d32\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d33\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d06\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f \u0d1c\u0d46 \u0d38\u0d3f \u0d21\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d47\u0d7d \u0d05\u0d35\u0d3e\u0d7c\u0d21\u0d4d -\r\n",
    "answer": "\u0d1f\u0d3f \u0d07 \u0d35\u0d3e\u0d38\u0d41\u0d26\u0d47\u0d35\u0d7b (1992)",
    "status": "4"
  },
  {
    "id": "253",
    "question": "\u0d26\u0d3e\u0d26 \u0d38\u0d3e\u0d39\u0d46\u0d2c\u0d4d \u0d2b\u0d32\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d46 \u0d05\u0d35\u0d3e\u0d7c\u0d21\u0d4d \u0d28\u0d47\u0d1f\u0d3f\u0d2f\r\n\u0d06\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f \u0d2e\u0d32\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d33\u0d3f _",
    "answer": "\u0d05\u0d1f\u0d42\u0d30\u0d4d \u0d17\u0d4b\u0d2a\u0d3e\u0d32 \u0d15\u0d43\u0d37\u0d4d\u0d23\u0d7b\r\n",
    "status": "4"
  },
  {
    "id": "254",
    "question": "\u0d2e\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d1a\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d41\u0d33\u0d4d\u0d33 \u0d06\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f \u0d26\u0d47\u0d36\u0d40\u0d2f\r\n\u0d05\u0d35\u0d3e\u0d7c\u0d21\u0d4d -",
    "answer": "\u0d1a\u0d46\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d40\u0d7b (1965)\r\n",
    "status": "4"
  },
  {
    "id": "255",
    "question": "\u0d1a\u0d3e\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a \u0d06\u0d30\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d38\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d3f\u0d2e?\r\n",
    "answer": "\u0d2a\u0d3f.\u0d0e.\u0d2c\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d7c\r\n",
    "status": "4"
  },
  {
    "id": "256",
    "question": "\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d27\u0d47\u0d2f\u0d7b \u0d38\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d2e\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d15\u0d25 \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d?\r\n",
    "answer": "\u0d2d\u0d3e\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d30\u0d2a\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d47\u0d32\u0d30\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d1c\u0d40\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d35\u0d41\u0d02\r\n",
    "status": "4"
  },
  {
    "id": "257",
    "question": "\u0d36\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d27\u0d02 \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d38\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d3f\u0d2e \u0d38\u0d02\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d27\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d02 \u0d1a\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d4d\u0d24 \u0d38\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d3f\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d3f\u0d30\u0d41\u0d2a\u0d15\u0d7b \u0d06\u0d30\u0d4d?\r\n",
    "answer": "\u0d35\u0d3f.\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d1c\u0d15\u0d43\u0d37\u0d4d\u0d23\u0d7b\r\n",
    "status": "4"
  },
  {
    "id": "258",
    "question": "\u0d2e\u0d4a\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d3e\u0d37\u0d4d \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d38\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d32\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d02 \u0d05\u0d35\u0d24\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d4d?\r\n",
    "answer": "\u0d10\u0d38\u0d7b\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d7b\r\n",
    "status": "4"
  },
  {
    "id": "259",
    "question": "\u0d2e\u0d34 \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d38\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d3f\u0d2e\u0d2f\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4d \u0d15\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d23\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d2f \u0d15\u0d25?\r\n",
    "answer": "\u0d28\u0d37\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d46\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f \u0d28\u0d40\u0d32\u0d3e\u0d02\u0d2c\u0d30\u0d3f, \u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d27\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d3f\r\n",
    "status": "4"
  },
  {
    "id": "260",
    "question": "\u0d15\u0d41\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d28\u0d3e\u0d36\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d15\u0d30\u0d41\u0d23 \u0d38\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d3f\u0d2e \u0d06\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d4d?\r\n",
    "answer": "\u0d24\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d7b\r\n",
    "status": "4"
  },
  {
    "id": "261",
    "question": "\u0d2a\u0d3e\u0d32\u0d47\u0d30\u0d3f \u0d2e\u0d23\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d02 \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d38\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d3f\u0d2e\u0d2f\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4d \u0d15\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d23\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d2f \u0d28\u0d4b\u0d35\u0d7d \u0d0e\u0d34\u0d41\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d?\r\n",
    "answer": "\u0d1f\u0d3f.\u0d2a\u0d3f \u0d30\u0d3e\u0d1c\u0d40\u0d35\u0d7b\r\n",
    "status": "4"
  },
  {
    "id": "262",
    "question": "\u0d26\u0d48\u0d35\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d35\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d43\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d7e \u0d38\u0d02\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d27\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d02 ?",
    "answer": "\u0d32\u0d46\u0d28\u0d3f\u0d7b \u0d30\u0d3e\u0d1c\u0d47\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d7b",
    "status": "4"
  },
  {
    "id": "263",
    "question": "\u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d4d \u0d38\u0d4d\u0d35\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d02 \u0d1c\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d15\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d3f \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d38\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d3f\u0d2e\u0d2f\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4d \u0d06\u0d27\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d2f \u0d15\u0d25 ?",
    "answer": "\u0d15\u0d4a\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d41 \u0d15\u0d4a\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d41 \u0d2d\u0d42\u0d15\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d19\u0d7e",
    "status": "4"
  },
  {
    "id": "264",
    "question": "\u0d2a\u0d4b\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d7b\u0d38\u0d4d \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d1a\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d2b\u0d4b\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d4b \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d38\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d3f\u0d2e\u0d2f\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4d \u0d06\u0d27\u0d3e\u0d30 \u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d2f \u0d15\u0d25?",
    "answer": "\u0d2e\u0d41\u0d15\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d26\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d2b\u0d4b\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d4b \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d15\u0d25.",
    "status": "4"
  },
  {
    "id": "265",
    "question": "\u0d2a\u0d36\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d3e\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d32 \u0d38\u0d02\u0d17\u0d40\u0d24\u0d02 \u0d2a\u0d42\u0d7c\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d23\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d05\u0d34\u0d3f\u0d35\u0d3e\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3f\u0d2f \u0d1a\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d02?",
    "answer": "\u0d15\u0d4a\u0d1f\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d47\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d02",
    "status": "4"
  },
  {
    "id": "266",
    "question": "\u0d36\u0d36\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d41\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d15\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d3e \u0d24\u0d30\u0d7a \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d1a\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d24\u0d24\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d2e\u0d42\u0d32\u0d15\u0d25 \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d4d ?",
    "answer": "\u0d35\u0d7b\u0d2e\u0d30\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d19\u0d7e \u0d35\u0d40\u0d34\u0d41\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d4b\u0d7e - \u0d0e\u0d7b.\u0d0e\u0d38\u0d4d.\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d27\u0d35\u0d7b",
    "status": "4"
  },
  {
    "id": "267",
    "question": "\u0d2a\u0d41\u0d32\u0d3f\u0d1c\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d02 \u0d38\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d3f\u0d2e \u0d38\u0d02\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d27\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d02 \u0d1a\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d4d ?",
    "answer": "\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d26\u0d7b",
    "status": "4"
  },
  {
    "id": "268",
    "question": "\u0d2d\u0d3e\u0d7c\u0d17\u0d4d\u0d17\u0d35\u0d40 \u0d28\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d2f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d \u0d15\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d23\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d2f \u0d2c\u0d37\u0d40\u0d7c \u0d15\u0d25 ?",
    "answer": "\u0d28\u0d40\u0d32\u0d35\u0d46\u0d33\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d02",
    "status": "4"
  },
  {
    "id": "269",
    "question": "\u0d2e\u0d32\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d33\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d06\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f 70mm \u0d1a\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d02?",
    "answer": "\u0d2a\u0d1f\u0d2f\u0d4b\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d02",
    "status": "4"
  },
  {
    "id": "270",
    "question": "in which Annie gives it those \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d38\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d3f\u0d2e\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d28\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d2f \u0d38\u0d3e\u0d39\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d3f ?",
    "answer": "\u0d05\u0d30\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d27\u0d24\u0d3f \u0d31\u0d4b\u0d2f\u0d4d",
    "status": "4"
  },
  {
    "id": "271",
    "question": "\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d35\u0d3e\u0d32\u0d02 \u0d30\u0d1a\u0d28 \u0d28\u0d3f\u0d7c\u0d35\u0d39\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a \u0d38\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d3f\u0d2e ?",
    "answer": "\u0d15\u0d41\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d3f",
    "status": "4"
  },
  {
    "id": "272",
    "question": "\u0d2e\u0d32\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d33\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d06\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f \u0d30\u0d3e\u0d37\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d40\u0d2f \u0d38\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d3f\u0d2e ?",
    "answer": "\u0d15\u0d2c\u0d28\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d26\u0d3f \u0d1a\u0d41\u0d35\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d4b\u0d7e",
    "status": "4"
  },
  {
    "id": "273",
    "question": "\u0d1e\u0d3e\u0d7b \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d38\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d3f\u0d2e \u0d06\u0d27\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3f\u0d2f \u0d15\u0d25 ?",
    "answer": "\u0d1f\u0d3f.\u0d2a\u0d3f \u0d30\u0d3e\u0d1c\u0d40\u0d35\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d15\u0d46.\u0d1f\u0d3f \u0d0e\u0d7b \u0d15\u0d4b\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d42\u0d7c \u0d0e\u0d34\u0d41\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d1c\u0d40\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d35\u0d41\u0d02",
    "status": "4"
  },
  {
    "id": "274",
    "question": "\u0d1c\u0d3f \u0d05\u0d30\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d26\u0d7b \u0d28\u0d3f\u0d7c\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a \u0d07\u0d02\u0d17\u0d4d\u0d32\u0d40\u0d37\u0d4d \u0d1a\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d02 ?",
    "answer": "\u0d09\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d23\u0d3f",
    "status": "4"
  },
  {
    "id": "275",
    "question": "\u0d38\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d3f\u0d2e - \u0d15\u0d23\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d15\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d06\u0d30\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d15\u0d43\u0d24\u0d3f ?",
    "answer": "\u0d36\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d40\u0d15\u0d41\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d7b \u0d24\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d3f",
    "status": "4"
  },
  {
    "id": "276",
    "question": "\u0d38\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d3f\u0d2e\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d39\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d36\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d40 \u0d06\u0d30\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d15\u0d43\u0d24\u0d3f ?",
    "answer": "\u0d0e\u0d02.\u0d0e\u0d02 \u0d35\u0d7c\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3f",
    "status": "4"
  },
  {
    "id": "277",
    "question": "\u0d1a\u0d32\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30 \u0d38\u0d4d\u0d35\u0d30\u0d42\u0d2a\u0d02 \u0d06\u0d30\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d15\u0d43\u0d24\u0d3f ?",
    "answer": "\u0d2a\u0d3f.\u0d0e\u0d7b.\u0d36\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d40\u0d15\u0d41\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d7c",
    "status": "4"
  },
  {
    "id": "278",
    "question": "\u0d2a\u0d3f.\u0d2d\u0d3e\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d30\u0d7b \u0d17\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d30\u0d1a\u0d28 \u0d28\u0d3f\u0d7c\u0d35\u0d4d\u0d35\u0d39\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a \u0d06\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f \u0d1a\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d02 ?",
    "answer": "\u0d1a\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d15.",
    "status": "4"
  },
  {
    "id": "279",
    "question": "\u0d12\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31 \u0d38\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d40 \u0d2a\u0d4b\u0d32\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d05\u0d2d\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24 \u0d38\u0d4d\u0d24' \u0d2e\u0d32\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d33 \u0d1a\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d02 ?",
    "answer": "\u0d2e\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d41\u0d15\u0d7e",
    "status": "4"
  },
  {
    "id": "280",
    "question": "\u0d38\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d7b \u0d06\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d3f \u0d05\u0d2d\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a \u0d1a\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d02 ?",
    "answer": "\u0d06\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d38\u0d16\u0d3f",
    "status": "4"
  },
  {
    "id": "281",
    "question": "\u0d12\u0d30\u0d41 \u0d35\u0d28\u0d3f\u0d24 \u0d38\u0d02\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d27\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d02 \u0d1a\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d4d\u0d24 \u0d06\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d2e\u0d32\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d33\u0d1a\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d02 ?",
    "answer": "\u0d28\u0d3f\u0d34\u0d32\u0d3e\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d02. \u0d38\u0d02\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d27\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d02 \u0d37\u0d40\u0d32",
    "status": "4"
  },
  {
    "id": "282",
    "question": "\u0d32\u0d4b\u0d15 \u0d38\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d3f\u0d2e\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d35\u0d4d ?",
    "answer": "\u0d13\u0d17\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d38\u0d4d \u0d32\u0d41\u0d2e\u0d3f\u0d7c&\u0d32\u0d42\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d38\u0d4d \u0d32\u0d41\u0d2e\u0d3f\u0d7c",
    "status": "4"
  },
  {
    "id": "283",
    "question": "\u0d06\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d46 \u0d32\u0d4b\u0d15 \u0d38\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d3f\u0d2e ?",
    "answer": "\u0d05\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d35\u0d7d \u0d13\u0d2b\u0d4d \u0d0e \u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d7b",
    "status": "4"
  },
  {
    "id": "284",
    "question": "\u0d38\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d3f\u0d2e \u0d06\u0d15\u0d3f\u0d2f \u0d06\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f \u0d38\u0d3e\u0d39\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f \u0d15\u0d43\u0d24\u0d3f ?",
    "answer": "\u0d26\u0d3f \u0d21\u0d46\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d13\u0d2b\u0d4d \u0d28\u0d3e\u0d7b\u0d38\u0d3f \u0d38\u0d48\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d38\u0d4d(1897)",
    "status": "4"
  },
  {
    "id": "285",
    "question": "\u0d32\u0d4b\u0d15\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d06\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f \u0d36\u0d2c\u0d4d\u0d26 \u0d1a\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d02 ?",
    "answer": "\u0d26\u0d3f \u0d1c\u0d3e\u0d38\u0d4d \u0d38\u0d3f\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d19\u0d7c(1927)",
    "status": "4"
  },
  {
    "id": "286",
    "question": "\u0d32\u0d4b\u0d15 \u0d38\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d3f\u0d2e\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d7d \u0d06\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d02\r\n\u0d38\u0d02\u0d38\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a \u0d35\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f ?",
    "answer": "\u0d05\u0d7d \u0d1c\u0d4b\u0d32\u0d3f\u0d38\u0d4b\u0d23\u0d4d(\u0d1c\u0d3e\u0d38\u0d4d \u0d38\u0d3f\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d19\u0d7c 1927)",
    "status": "4"
  },
  {
    "id": "287",
    "question": "\u0d32\u0d4b\u0d15 \u0d38\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d3f\u0d2e\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d7d \u0d06\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d02\r\n\u0d38\u0d02\u0d38\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a \u0d35\u0d3e\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4d ?",
    "answer": "\u0d35\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d \u0d0e \u0d2e\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d3f\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d",
    "status": "4"
  },
  {
    "id": "288",
    "question": "\u0d06\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d02 \u0d38\u0d02\u0d38\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a \u0d28\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d15 \u0d28\u0d1f\u0d7b ?",
    "answer": "\u0d05\u0d7d \u0d1c\u0d4b\u0d32\u0d3f\u0d38\u0d4b\u0d23\u0d4d",
    "status": "4"
  },
  {
    "id": "289",
    "question": "\u0d06\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d02 \u0d38\u0d02\u0d38\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a \u0d28\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d3e \u0d28\u0d1f\u0d3f ?",
    "answer": "\u0d2f\u0d42\u0d1c\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d3f\u0d2f \u0d2c\u0d47\u0d38\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d47\u0d7c",
    "status": "4"
  },
  {
    "id": "290",
    "question": "\u0d32\u0d4b\u0d15\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d06\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f \u0d15\u0d33\u0d7c \u0d1a\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d02 ?",
    "answer": "\u0d32\u0d48\u0d2b\u0d4d \u0d06\u0d7b\u0d21\u0d4d \u0d2a\u0d3e\u0d37\u0d7b \u0d13\u0d2b\u0d4d \u0d26\u0d3f \u0d15\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d48\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d(1903)",
    "status": "4"
  },
  {
    "id": "291",
    "question": "\u0d06\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f \u0d2a\u0d41\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d23 \u0d1a\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d02 ?",
    "answer": "\u0d13\u0d21\u0d3f\u0d38\u0d4d\u200c\u0d38\u0d40 (1911)",
    "status": "4"
  },
  {
    "id": "292",
    "question": "\u0d06\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f industry \u0d39\u0d3f\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d \u0d1a\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d02 ?",
    "answer": "\u0d26\u0d3f \u0d2c\u0d7c\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d13\u0d2b\u0d4d \u0d26\u0d3f \u0d28\u0d47\u0d37\u0d7b (1915)",
    "status": "4"
  },
  {
    "id": "293",
    "question": "\u0d06\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f \u0d28\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d4b \u0d31\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d32\u0d3f\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d \u0d1a\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d02 ?",
    "answer": "\u0d12\u0d36\u0d47\u0d37\u0d28\u0d46 (1943)",
    "status": "4"
  },
  {
    "id": "294",
    "question": "\u0d06\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f \u0d38\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d3f\u0d2e \u0d38\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4b\u0d2a\u0d4d \u0d1a\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d02 ?",
    "answer": "\u0d26\u0d3f \u0d31\u0d4b\u0d2c\u0d4d (1953)",
    "status": "4"
  },
  {
    "id": "295",
    "question": "\u0d06\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f 70mm \u0d1a\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d02 ?",
    "answer": "\u0d12\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d32\u0d39\u0d4b\u0d2e (1955)",
    "status": "4"
  },
  {
    "id": "296",
    "question": "\u0d12\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d32\u0d39\u0d4b\u0d2e \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d3e \u0d1a\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\r\n\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d47\u0d30\u0d15\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d2f \u0d05\u0d2e\u0d47\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d7b \u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d42\u0d38\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d7d ?",
    "answer": "\u0d12\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d32\u0d39\u0d4b\u0d2e",
    "status": "4"
  },
  {
    "id": "297",
    "question": "\u0d06\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f 3D \u0d1a\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d02 ?",
    "answer": "\u0d26\u0d3f \u0d2a\u0d35\u0d7c \u0d13\u0d2b\u0d4d \u0d32\u0d35\u0d4d (1922)",
    "status": "4"
  },
  {
    "id": "298",
    "question": "\u0d06\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f \u0d21\u0d4b\u0d7e\u0d2c\u0d3f \u0d38\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d40\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d4a \u0d1a\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d02 ?",
    "answer": "\u0d0e \u0d15\u0d4d\u0d32\u0d4b\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d35\u0d4b\u0d7c\u0d15\u0d4d \u0d13\u0d31\u0d1e\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d4d (1971)",
    "status": "4"
  },
  {
    "id": "299",
    "question": "\u0d06\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f \u0d21\u0d3f \u0d1f\u0d3f \u0d0e\u0d38\u0d4d \u0d1a\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d02 ?",
    "answer": "\u0d1c\u0d41\u0d31\u0d3e\u0d38\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d \u0d2a\u0d3e\u0d7c\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4d(1993)",
    "status": "4"
  },
  {
    "id": "300",
    "question": "\u0d06\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f \u0d21\u0d3f\u0d1c\u0d3f\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d7d \u0d38\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d3f\u0d2e ?",
    "answer": "\u0d12\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d38\u0d4d \u0d09\u0d2a\u0d4b\u0d7a \u0d0e \u0d1f\u0d48\u0d02 \u0d07\u0d7b \u0d2e\u0d46\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d38\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4b (2001)",
    "status": "4"
  },
  {
    "id": "301",
    "question": "\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d3f\u0d7d \u0d2a\u0d3e\u0d32\u0d2e\u0d4d \u0d21\u0d3f \u0d14\u0d7c\r\n\u0d28\u0d47\u0d1f\u0d3f\u0d2f \u0d06\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f \u0d1a\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d02 ?",
    "answer": "\u0d2f\u0d42\u0d23\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d7b \u0d2a\u0d38\u0d3f\u0d2b\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d (1939)",
    "status": "4"
  },
  {
    "id": "302",
    "question": "\u0d13\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d7c\r\n\u0d28\u0d47\u0d1f\u0d3f\u0d2f \u0d06\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f \u0d1a\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d02 ?",
    "answer": "\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d19\u0d4d\u200c\u0d38\u0d4d",
    "status": "4"
  },
  {
    "id": "303",
    "question": "\u0d06\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f \u0d2b\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d3f\u0d02 \u0d38\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d41\u0d21\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d4b ?",
    "answer": "\u0d2c\u0d4d\u0d32\u0d3e\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4d \u0d2e\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d2f (1893)",
    "status": "4"
  },
  {
    "id": "304",
    "question": "\u0d06\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f \u0d2b\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d3f\u0d02 \u0d38\u0d4a\u0d38\u0d48\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d3f ?",
    "answer": "\u0d32\u0d46\u0d38\u0d4d \u0d05\u0d2e\u0d3f\u0d38\u0d4d \u0d1f\u0d41 \u0d38\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d3f\u0d2e (1930)",
    "status": "4"
  },
  {
    "id": "305",
    "question": "\u0d06\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f \u0d38\u0d3f\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d7d \u0d21\u0d3f \u0d2e\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4d\u0d32\u0d47 \u0d05\u0d35\u0d3e\u0d7c\u0d21\u0d4d ?",
    "answer": "\u0d38\u0d46\u0d38\u0d3f\u0d7d \u0d21\u0d3f \u0d2e\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4d\u0d32\u0d47 (1952)",
    "status": "4"
  },
  {
    "id": "306",
    "question": "\u0d2e\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d1a\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d41\u0d33\u0d4d\u0d33 \u0d06\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f \u0d05\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d26\u0d2e\u0d3f\r\n\u0d05\u0d35\u0d3e\u0d7c\u0d21\u0d4d ?",
    "answer": "\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d19\u0d4d\u200c\u0d38\u0d4d (1927)",
    "status": "4"
  },
  {
    "id": "307",
    "question": "\u0d2e\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a \u0d28\u0d1f\u0d28\u0d41\u0d33\u0d4d\u0d33 \u0d06\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f \u0d13\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d7c \u0d05\u0d35\u0d3e\u0d7c\u0d21\u0d4d ?",
    "answer": "\u0d0e\u0d2e\u0d3f\u0d7d \u0d1c\u0d46\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d3f\u0d19\u0d4d\u200c\u0d38\u0d4d(\u0d26\u0d3f \u0d32\u0d3e\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d \u0d15\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d7b\u0d21\u0d4d -1928)",
    "status": "4"
  },
  {
    "id": "308",
    "question": "\u0d2e\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a \u0d28\u0d1f\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d41\u0d33\u0d4d\u0d33 \u0d06\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f \u0d13\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d7c\r\n\u0d05\u0d35\u0d3e\u0d7c\u0d21\u0d4d ?",
    "answer": "\u0d1c\u0d28\u0d46\u0d31\u0d4d \u0d17\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d7c (1927)",
    "status": "4"
  },
  {
    "id": "309",
    "question": "\u0d0e\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d35\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d15\u0d42\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d24\u0d7d \u0d13\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d7c \u0d05\u0d35\u0d3e\u0d7c\u0d21\u0d4d \u0d28\u0d47\u0d1f\u0d3f\u0d2f \u0d28\u0d1f\u0d7b ?",
    "answer": "\u0d21\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d47\u0d7d \u0d21\u0d47 \u0d32\u0d46\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d19\u0d4d\u200c\u0d38\u0d4d ",
    "status": "4"
  },
  {
    "id": "310",
    "question": "\u0d0e\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d35\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d15\u0d42\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d24\u0d7d \u0d13\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d7c \u0d05\u0d35\u0d3e\u0d7c\u0d21\u0d4d\r\n\u0d28\u0d47\u0d1f\u0d3f\u0d2f \u0d28\u0d1f\u0d3f ?",
    "answer": "\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d24\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d7b \u0d39\u0d46\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d4d\u200c\u0d7c\u0d28\u0d4d",
    "status": "4"
  },
  {
    "id": "311",
    "question": "\u0d0e\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d35\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d15\u0d42\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d24\u0d7d \u0d38\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d3f\u0d2e\u0d15\u0d33\u0d3f\u0d7d\r\n\u0d05\u0d2d\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a \u0d28\u0d1f\u0d7b ?",
    "answer": "\u0d12\u0d32\u0d3f\u0d35\u0d7c \u0d39\u0d3e\u0d7b\u0d21\u0d3f",
    "status": "4"
  },
  {
    "id": "312",
    "question": "\u0d0e\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d35\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d15\u0d42\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d24\u0d7d \u0d38\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d3f\u0d2e\u0d15\u0d33\u0d3f\u0d7d\r\n\u0d05\u0d2d\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a \u0d28\u0d1f\u0d3f ?",
    "answer": "\u0d2e\u0d47\u0d30\u0d3f \u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d2b\u0d4b\u0d21\u0d4d",
    "status": "4"
  },
  {
    "id": "313",
    "question": "\u0d0e\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d35\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d15\u0d42\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d24\u0d7d \u0d38\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d3f\u0d2e\u0d15\u0d33\u0d3f\u0d7d\r\n\u0d28\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d3e -\u0d28\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d15\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d7c ?",
    "answer": "\u0d39\u0d41\u0d02\u0d2b\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d47\u0d2f\u0d4d \u0d2c\u0d4b\u0d17\u0d7c\u0d1f\u0d4d\r\n,\u0d2c\u0d46\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d21\u0d47\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d38\u0d4d",
    "status": "4"
  },
  {
    "id": "314",
    "question": "\u0d0e\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d35\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d15\u0d42\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d24\u0d7d \u0d2a\u0d41\u0d30\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d19\u0d7e \u0d28\u0d47\u0d1f\u0d3f\u0d2f \u0d38\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d3f\u0d2e ?",
    "answer": "\u0d26\u0d3f \u0d32\u0d4b\u0d7c\u0d21\u0d4d \u0d13\u0d2b\u0d4d \u0d26\u0d3f \u0d31\u0d3f\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d38\u0d4d:\u0d26\u0d3f \u0d31\u0d3f\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d47\u0d7a \u0d13\u0d2b\u0d4d \u0d26\u0d3f \u0d15\u0d3f\u0d02\u0d17\u0d4d",
    "status": "4"
  },
  {
    "id": "315",
    "question": "\u0d0e\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d35\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d15\u0d42\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d24\u0d7d \u0d05\u0d35\u0d3e\u0d7c\u0d21\u0d4d \u0d28\u0d47\u0d1f\u0d3f\u0d2f\r\n\u0d38\u0d02\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d27\u0d2f\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d7b ?",
    "answer": "\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d02 \u0d35\u0d47\u0d33\u0d7c",
    "status": "4"
  },
  {
    "id": "316",
    "question": "5 \u0d15\u0d4b\u0d1f\u0d3f \u0d15\u0d33\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d37\u0d7b \u0d28\u0d47\u0d1f\u0d3f\u0d2f \u0d06\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f \u0d1a\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d02 ?",
    "answer": "\u0d26\u0d3f \u0d2c\u0d7c\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d13\u0d2b\u0d4d \u0d26\u0d3f \u0d28\u0d47\u0d37\u0d7b",
    "status": "4"
  },
  {
    "id": "317",
    "question": "40 \u0d15\u0d4b\u0d1f\u0d3f \u0d15\u0d33\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d37\u0d7b \u0d28\u0d47\u0d1f\u0d3f\u0d2f \u0d06\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f \u0d1a\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d02 ?",
    "answer": "\u0d38\u0d4d\u200c\u0d28\u0d57 \u0d35\u0d48\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d \u0d06\u0d7b\u0d21\u0d4d \u0d26\u0d3f \u0d38\u0d46\u0d35\u0d7b \u0d26\u0d4d\u0d35\u0d3e\u0d7c\u0d2b\u0d4d\u0d38\u0d4d",
    "status": "4"
  },
  {
    "id": "318",
    "question": "30 \u0d15\u0d4b\u0d1f\u0d3f \u0d15\u0d33\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d37\u0d7b \u0d28\u0d47\u0d1f\u0d3f\u0d2f \u0d06\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f \u0d1a\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d02 ?",
    "answer": "\u0d17\u0d4a\u0d23\u0d47 \u0d35\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d26\u0d3f \u0d35\u0d3f\u0d7b\u0d21\u0d4d",
    "status": "4"
  },
  {
    "id": "319",
    "question": "100 \u0d15\u0d4b\u0d1f\u0d3f \u0d15\u0d33\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d37\u0d7b \u0d28\u0d47\u0d1f\u0d3f\u0d2f \u0d06\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f \u0d1a\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d02 ?",
    "answer": "\u0d1c\u0d41\u0d31\u0d3e\u0d38\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d \u0d2a\u0d3e\u0d7c\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4d",
    "status": "4"
  },
  {
    "id": "320",
    "question": "200 \u0d15\u0d4b\u0d1f\u0d3f \u0d15\u0d4d\u0d32\u0d2c\u0d4d\u0d2c\u0d3f\u0d7d \u0d15\u0d47\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d2f \u0d06\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f\r\n\u0d1a\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d02 ?",
    "answer": "\u0d1f\u0d48\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d ",
    "status": "4"
  },
  {
    "id": "321",
    "question": "\u0d1a\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d4d\u0d32\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d \u0d1a\u0d3e\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d32\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d46 \u0d38\u0d42\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d7c \u0d38\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d3e\u0d7c \u0d06\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3f\u0d2f \u0d1a\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d02 ?",
    "answer": "\u0d32\u0d3f\u0d2e\u0d47 \u0d32\u0d48\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d",
    "status": "4"
  },
  {
    "id": "322",
    "question": "\u0d2c\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d7c \u0d15\u0d47\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d28\u0d46 \u0d38\u0d42\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d7c \u0d38\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d3e\u0d7c \u0d06\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3f\u0d2f \u0d1a\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d02 ?",
    "answer": "\u0d26\u0d3f \u0d30\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d7d\u0d31\u0d4b\u0d21\u0d4d\u0d21\u0d7c",
    "status": "4"
  },
  {
    "id": "323",
    "question": "\u0d32\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d32\u0d4d&\u0d39\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d4d\u0d26\u0d2f\u0d46 \u0d38\u0d42\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d7c \u0d38\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d3e\u0d7c \u0d06\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3f\u0d2f \u0d1a\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d02 ?",
    "answer": "\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d38\u0d4d \u0d2e\u0d3f\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d38\u0d4d",
    "status": "4"
  },
  {
    "id": "324",
    "question": "\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d32\u0d3e\u0d7c\u0d15\u0d4d \u0d17\u0d3e\u0d2c\u0d4d\u0d32\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d4d\u200c\u0d28\u0d46 \u0d38\u0d42\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d7c \u0d38\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d3e\u0d7c \u0d06\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3f\u0d2f \u0d1a\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d02 ?",
    "answer": "\u0d2c\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d4d \u0d28\u0d4b\u0d1f\u0d4d \u0d2b\u0d4b\u0d7c \u0d2e\u0d3f",
    "status": "4"
  },
  {
    "id": "325",
    "question": "\u0d1a\u0d3e\u0d7e\u0d38\u0d4d \u0d2c\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d4b\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d46 \u0d38\u0d42\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d7c \u0d38\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d3e\u0d7c \u0d06\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3f\u0d2f \u0d1a\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d02 ?",
    "answer": "\u0d15\u0d4b\u0d7e\u0d21\u0d4d \u0d38\u0d4d\u0d35\u0d40\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d",
    "status": "4"
  },
  {
    "id": "326",
    "question": "\u0d17\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d17\u0d31\u0d3f \u0d2a\u0d47\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d46 \u0d38\u0d42\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d7c \u0d38\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d3e\u0d7c \u0d06\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3f\u0d2f \u0d1a\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d02 ?",
    "answer": "\u0d26\u0d3f \u0d2c\u0d3f\u0d17\u0d4d \u0d15\u0d7a\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d3f",
    "status": "4"
  },
  {
    "id": "327",
    "question": "\u0d39\u0d41\u0d02\u0d2b\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d47\u0d2f\u0d4d \u0d2d\u0d4b\u0d17\u0d7c\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d46 \u0d38\u0d42\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d7c \u0d38\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d3e\u0d7c \u0d06\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3f\u0d2f \u0d1a\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d02 ?",
    "answer": "\u0d39\u0d48 \u0d38\u0d46\u0d7c\u0d31",
    "status": "4"
  },
  {
    "id": "328",
    "question": "\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d02 \u0d39\u0d4b\u0d33\u0d4d\u0d21\u0d28\u0d46 \u0d38\u0d42\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d7c \u0d38\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d3e\u0d7c \u0d06\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3f\u0d2f \u0d1a\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d02 ?",
    "answer": "\u0d35\u0d48\u0d7d\u0d21\u0d4d \u0d31\u0d4b\u0d35\u0d47\u0d34\u0d4d\u200c\u0d38\u0d4d",
    "status": "4"
  },
  {
    "id": "329",
    "question": "\u0d31\u0d4b\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4d \u0d39\u0d41\u0d21\u0d4d\u0d38\u0d7a \u0d38\u0d42\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d7c \u0d38\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d3e\u0d7c \u0d06\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3f\u0d2f \u0d1a\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d02 ?",
    "answer": "\u0d37\u0d4b\u0d21\u0d57\u0d7a",
    "status": "4"
  },
  {
    "id": "330",
    "question": "\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d32\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d \u0d08\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d35\u0d41\u0d21\u0d4d \u0d38\u0d42\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d7c \u0d38\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d3e\u0d7c \u0d06\u0d2f \u0d1a\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d02 ?",
    "answer": "\u0d0e\u0d35\u0d47\u0d31\u0d3f \u0d35\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d4d \u0d35\u0d47 \u0d2c\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d4d \u0d32\u0d42\u0d38\u0d4d",
    "status": "4"
  },
  {
    "id": "331",
    "question": "\u0d2e\u0d7c\u0d32\u0d4a\u0d28\u0d4d \u0d2c\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d4b \u0d38\u0d42\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d7c \u0d06\u0d2f \u0d1a\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d02 ?",
    "answer": "\u0d38\u0d42\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d7c\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d",
    "status": "4"
  },
  {
    "id": "332",
    "question": "\u0d05\u0d7d \u0d2a\u0d3e\u0d38\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4b \u0d38\u0d42\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d7c \u0d38\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d3e\u0d7c \u0d06\u0d2f \u0d1a\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d02 ?",
    "answer": "\u0d06\u0d7b\u0d21\u0d4d \u0d1c\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d38\u0d4d \u0d2b\u0d4b\u0d7c \u0d13\u0d7e",
    "status": "4"
  },
  {
    "id": "333",
    "question": "\u0d39\u0d46\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d3f \u0d2b\u0d4b\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d1f \u0d38\u0d42\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d7c \u0d38\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d3e\u0d7c \u0d06\u0d2f \u0d1a\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d02 ?",
    "answer": "\u0d13\u0d7a \u0d17\u0d4b\u0d7e\u0d21\u0d7b \u0d2a\u0d4a\u0d7b\u0d21\u0d4d",
    "status": "4"
  },
  {
    "id": "334",
    "question": "\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d3e\u0d7c\u0d21\u0d4d \u0d1a\u0d3e\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d7c\u0d32\u0d48\u0d7b \u0d38\u0d42\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d7c \u0d38\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d3e\u0d7c \u0d06\u0d2f \u0d1a\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d02 ?",
    "answer": "\u0d15\u0d3f\u0d02\u0d17\u0d4d \u0d38\u0d4b\u0d33\u0d4b\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d7b\u0d38\u0d4d \u0d2e\u0d48\u0d7b\u0d38\u0d4d",
    "status": "4"
  },
  {
    "id": "335",
    "question": "\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d7c\u0d1f\u0d4d \u0d35\u0d48\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d \u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d7b \u0d38\u0d42\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d7c \u0d38\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d3e\u0d7c \u0d06\u0d2f \u0d1a\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d02 ?",
    "answer": "\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d42\u0d2c \u0d15\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d4b\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d38\u0d3f\u0d19\u0d4d",
    "status": "4"
  },
  {
    "id": "336",
    "question": "\u0d2b\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d46\u0d21\u0d4d \u0d06\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d7c \u0d38\u0d42\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d7c \u0d38\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d3e\u0d7c \u0d06\u0d2f \u0d1a\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d02 ?",
    "answer": "\u0d16\u0d4b\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d \u0d38\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4b\u0d31\u0d3f",
    "status": "4"
  },
  {
    "id": "337",
    "question": "\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d02 \u0d30\u0d3e\u0d1c\u0d3f\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d38\u0d42\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d7c \u0d38\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d3e\u0d7c \u0d06\u0d2f \u0d1a\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d02 ?",
    "answer": "\u0d2b\u0d4d\u200c\u0d31\u0d48\u0d31\u0d4d \u0d28\u0d48\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d",
    "status": "4"
  },
  {
    "id": "338",
    "question": "\u0d38\u0d3f\u0d7d\u0d35\u0d46\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4b\u0d7c \u0d38\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d3e\u0d32\u0d4d\u0d32\u0d4b\u0d28\u0d46 \u0d38\u0d42\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d7c\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d3e\u0d31\u0d3e\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3f\u0d2f \u0d38\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d3f\u0d2e ",
    "answer": "\u0d13\u0d35\u0d7c \u0d26\u0d3f \u0d1f\u0d4b\u0d2a\u0d4d",
    "status": "4"
  },
  {
    "id": "339",
    "question": "\u0d05\u0d7c\u0d23\u0d4b\u0d7e\u0d21\u0d4d \u0d37\u0d4d\u0d35\u0d3e\u0d31\u0d4d\u200c\u0d38\u0d4d\u200c\u0d28\u0d47\u0d17\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d46 \u0d38\u0d42\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d7c\u0d38 \u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3f\u0d2f \u0d38\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d3f\u0d2e ?",
    "answer": "\u0d30\u0d57 \u0d21\u0d40\u0d7d",
    "status": "4"
  },
  {
    "id": "340",
    "question": "\u0d2a\u0d47\u0d30\u0d4d\u0d38\u0d4d \u0d2c\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d4b\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d \u0d38\u0d42\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d7c \u0d38\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d3e\u0d7c \u0d06\u0d2f \u0d1a\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d02 ?",
    "answer": "\u0d17\u0d4b\u0d7e\u0d21\u0d7b \u0d10",
    "status": "4"
  },
  {
    "id": "341",
    "question": "\u0d32\u0d47\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4b\u0d28\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d4d\u0d21\u0d4b \u0d21\u0d46\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d40\u0d2f \u0d38\u0d42\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d7c \u0d38\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d3e\u0d7c \u0d06\u0d2f \u0d1a\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d02 ?",
    "answer": "\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d4d \u0d2e\u0d3f \u0d07\u0d2b\u0d4d \u0d2f\u0d41 \u0d15\u0d3e\u0d7b",
    "status": "4"
  },
  {
    "id": "342",
    "question": "\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d7b \u0d21\u0d40\u0d38\u0d7d \u0d38\u0d42\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d7c \u0d38\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d3e\u0d7c \u0d06\u0d2f \u0d1a\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d02 ?",
    "answer": "\u0d2b\u0d3e\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d&\u0d2b\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d42\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d38\u0d4d",
    "status": "4"
  },
  {
    "id": "343",
    "question": "\u0d06\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d3f 100 \u0d15\u0d4b\u0d1f\u0d3f \u0d15\u0d33\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d37\u0d7b \u0d28\u0d47\u0d1f\u0d3f\u0d2f \u0d38\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d3f\u0d2e ?",
    "answer": "\u0d1c\u0d41\u0d31\u0d3e\u0d38\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d \u0d2a\u0d3e\u0d7c\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4d ",
    "status": "4"
  },
  {
    "id": "344",
    "question": "\"Mathematics\" \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d35\u0d3e\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4d \u0d30\u0d42\u0d2a\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d46\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d24\u0d4d ?",
    "answer": "\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31 (\u0d17\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d40\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4d)",
    "status": "5"
  },
  {
    "id": "345",
    "question": "\u0d17\u0d23\u0d3f\u0d24 \u0d36\u0d3e\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30 \u0d28\u0d4a\u0d2c\u0d47\u0d32\u0d4d\u200d ?",
    "answer": "\u0d2b\u0d40\u0d32\u0d4d\u200d\u0d21\u0d4d\u0d38\u0d4d \u0d2e\u0d46\u0d21\u0d32\u0d4d\u200d",
    "status": "5"
  },
  {
    "id": "346",
    "question": "\"Zeero\" \u0d07\u0d32\u0d4d\u0d32\u0d3e\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24 \u0d38\u0d02\u0d16\u0d43\u0d28\u0d41 \u0d38\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d26\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d02 ?",
    "answer": "\u0d31\u0d4b\u0d2e\u0d28\u0d4d\u200d \u0d38\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d26\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d02",
    "status": "5"
  },
  {
    "id": "347",
    "question": " \" \u0d32\u0d41\u0d21\u0d4b\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d\u0d2b\u0d4d \u0d28\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d\" \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d46\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d38\u0d02\u0d16\u0d43 ?",
    "answer": "\u0d2a\u0d48",
    "status": "5"
  },
  {
    "id": "348",
    "question": "\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d41\u0d1c\u0d28\u0d4d\u200d \u0d38\u0d02\u0d16\u0d43 ?",
    "answer": " 1729",
    "status": "5"
  },
  {
    "id": "349",
    "question": "\u0d2e\u0d28\u0d41\u0d37\u0d43 \u0d15\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d43\u0d42\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d46\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d2d\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d24\u0d40\u0d2f \u0d17\u0d23\u0d3f\u0d24 \u0d36\u0d3e\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d1c\u0d4d\u0d1e ?",
    "answer": "\u0d36\u0d15\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d33 \u0d26\u0d47\u0d35\u0d3f",
    "status": "5"
  },
  {
    "id": "350",
    "question": "\u0d32\u0d4b\u0d15\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d06\u0d26\u0d43 \u0d17\u0d23\u0d3f\u0d24 \u0d36\u0d3e\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d1c\u0d4d\u0d1e ?",
    "answer": "\u0d39\u0d3f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d47\u0d37\u0d43",
    "status": "5"
  },
  {
    "id": "351",
    "question": "\u0d39\u0d30\u0d23 \u0d1a\u0d3f\u0d39\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d35\u0d41\u0d02, \u0d17\u0d41\u0d23\u0d28 \u0d1a\u0d3f\u0d39\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d35\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d06\u0d26\u0d43\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d3f \u0d09\u0d2a\u0d2f\u0d4b\u0d17\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a \u0d36\u0d3e\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d1c\u0d4d\u0d1e\u0d28\u0d4d\u200d ?",
    "answer": "\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4d\u0d32\u0d43\u0d02 \u0d13\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d47\u0d21\u0d4d",
    "status": "5"
  },
  {
    "id": "352",
    "question": "\u0d2d\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d24\u0d40\u0d2f \u0d17\u0d23\u0d3f\u0d24 \u0d36\u0d3e\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u200d\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d35\u0d4d ?",
    "answer": "\u0d2d\u0d3e\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d1a\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d43",
    "status": "5"
  },
  {
    "id": "353",
    "question": "\u0d2a\u0d3e\u0d32\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u200d\u0d21\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d4b\u0d02 \u0d38\u0d02\u0d16\u0d43 ?",
    "answer": "\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d46\u0d34\u0d41\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d32\u0d41\u0d02, \u0d2e\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d46\u0d34\u0d41\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d32\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d12\u0d30\u0d47 \u0d38\u0d02\u0d16\u0d43 .\r\ni.e, 525, 323, 848.....",
    "status": "5"
  },
  {
    "id": "354",
    "question": "\"\u0d38\u0d48\u0d2b\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d\" \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d46\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d38\u0d02\u0d16\u0d43 ?",
    "answer": "\u0d2a\u0d42\u0d1c\u0d43\u0d02.",
    "status": "5"
  },
  {
    "id": "355",
    "question": "\u0d2d\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d24\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d2f\u0d42\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d32\u0d3f\u0d21\u0d4d ?",
    "answer": "\u0d2d\u0d3e\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d1a\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d43",
    "status": "5"
  },
  {
    "id": "356",
    "question": "Ramanujan Institute of Mathematics ",
    "answer": "CHENNAI",
    "status": "5"
  },
  {
    "id": "357",
    "question": "Binomial \u0d38\u0d02\u0d16\u0d43\u0d28\u0d41 \u0d38\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d26\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u200d\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d35\u0d4d ?",
    "answer": "\u0d26\u0d3e\u0d32\u0d02\u0d2c\u0d47\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d",
    "status": "5"
  },
  {
    "id": "358",
    "question": "\u0d17\u0d23\u0d3f\u0d24 \u0d36\u0d3e\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d30\u0d3e\u0d1c\u0d15\u0d41\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d28\u0d4d\u200d ?",
    "answer": "\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d33\u0d4d\u200d \u0d2b\u0d46\u0d21\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d \u0d17\u0d4b\u0d38\u0d4d",
    "status": "5"
  },
  {
    "id": "359",
    "question": "Google \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d46\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d38\u0d02\u0d16\u0d43 ?",
    "answer": "10 race to 100",
    "status": "5"
  },
  {
    "id": "360",
    "question": "\u0d38\u0d2e\u0d41\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d30 \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d46\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d38\u0d02\u0d16\u0d43 ?",
    "answer": "10 race to 9",
    "status": "5"
  },
  {
    "id": "361",
    "question": "\u0d32\u0d4b\u0d17\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d02 \u0d2a\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d09\u0d2a\u0d1c\u0d4d\u0d1e\u0d3e\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d35\u0d4d ?",
    "answer": "\u0d1c\u0d4b\u0d23\u0d4d\u200d \u0d28\u0d47\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d",
    "status": "5"
  },
  {
    "id": "362",
    "question": "\u0d2a\u0d48 \u0d26\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d02 \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d4d ?",
    "answer": "\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d4d 14",
    "status": "5"
  },
  {
    "id": "363",
    "question": "\u0d12\u0d30\u0d41 \u0d38\u0d2e\u0d1a\u0d24\u0d41\u0d30\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u200d\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d35\u0d3f\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d40\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d23\u0d35\u0d41\u0d02, \u0d1a\u0d41\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d33\u0d35\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d24\u0d41\u0d32\u0d43\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d3f \u0d35\u0d30\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d0f\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d35\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d1a\u0d46\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d2f \u0d38\u0d02\u0d16\u0d43 ?",
    "answer": "16",
    "status": "5"
  },
  {
    "id": "364",
    "question": "\u0d07\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d7d \u0d07\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d4b\u0d7e - \u0d30\u0d3e\u0d37\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d2a\u0d24\u0d3f ?",
    "answer": ":\u0d36\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d40. \u0d30\u0d3e\u0d02 \u0d28\u0d3e\u0d25\u0d4d \u0d15\u0d4b\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d26\u0d4d",
    "status": "3"
  },
  {
    "id": "365",
    "question": "\u0d09\u0d2a \u0d30\u0d3e\u0d37\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d2a\u0d24\u0d3f :",
    "answer": "\u0d36\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d40. \u0d2e\u0d41\u0d39\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d26\u0d4d\u200c \u0d39\u0d2e\u0d40\u0d26\u0d4d \u0d05\u0d7b\u0d38\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d3f",
    "status": "3"
  },
  {
    "id": "366",
    "question": "\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d27\u0d3e\u0d28 \u0d2e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d3f :",
    "answer": "\u0d36\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d40. \u0d28\u0d30\u0d47\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d30 \u0d2e\u0d4b\u0d26\u0d3f",
    "status": "3"
  },
  {
    "id": "367",
    "question": "\u0d28\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d3f \u0d06\u0d2f\u0d4b\u0d17\u0d4d \u0d1a\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d7c\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d7b :",
    "answer": "\u0d36\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d40. \u0d28\u0d30\u0d47\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d30 \u0d2e\u0d4b\u0d26\u0d3f",
    "status": "3"
  },
  {
    "id": "368",
    "question": "\u0d28\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d3f \u0d06\u0d2f\u0d4b\u0d17\u0d4d \u0d35\u0d48\u0d38\u0d4d \u0d1a\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d7c\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d7b :",
    "answer": "\u0d36\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d40. \u0d05\u0d30\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d26\u0d4d \u0d2a\u0d28\u0d17\u0d3f\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d3e",
    "status": "3"
  },
  {
    "id": "369",
    "question": "\u0d28\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d3f \u0d06\u0d2f\u0d4b\u0d17\u0d4d CEO :",
    "answer": "\u0d36\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d40. \u0d05\u0d2e\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d2c\u0d4d \u0d15\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d",
    "status": "3"
  },
  {
    "id": "370",
    "question": "\u0d38\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d40\u0d02 \u0d15\u0d4b\u0d1f\u0d24\u0d3f \u0d1a\u0d40\u0d2b\u0d4d \u0d1c\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d38\u0d4d : ",
    "answer": "\u0d1c\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d38\u0d4d. \u0d1c\u0d17\u0d26\u0d40\u0d37\u0d4d \u0d1a\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d30 \u0d16\u0d47\u0d39\u0d7c (44\u0d2e\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d46 \u0d35\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f )",
    "status": "3"
  },
  {
    "id": "371",
    "question": "\u0d05\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4b\u0d7c\u0d23\u0d3f \u0d1c\u0d28\u0d31\u0d7d :",
    "answer": "\u0d2e\u0d41\u0d15\u0d41\u0d7e \u0d31\u0d4b\u0d39\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f (14\u0d2e\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d46 \u0d35\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f )",
    "status": "3"
  },
  {
    "id": "372",
    "question": "\u0d38\u0d4b\u0d33\u0d3f\u0d38\u0d3f\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d7c \u0d1c\u0d28\u0d31\u0d7d :",
    "answer": "\u0d30\u0d1e\u0d4d\u0d1c\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d15\u0d41\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d7c (2017 \u0d1c\u0d42\u0d7a \u0d35\u0d30\u0d46 )",
    "status": "3"
  },
  {
    "id": "373",
    "question": "\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d38\u0d47\u0d7c\u0d35\u0d4d \u0d2c\u0d3e\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4d \u0d17\u0d35\u0d7c\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d23\u0d7c :",
    "answer": "\u0d09\u0d7c\u0d1c\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d2a\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d47\u0d7d (24\u0d2e\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d46 \u0d35\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f )",
    "status": "3"
  },
  {
    "id": "374",
    "question": "\u0d15\u0d02\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d4b\u0d33\u0d7c \u0d06\u0d7b\u0d21\u0d4d\u200c \u0d13\u0d21\u0d3f\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d7c \u0d1c\u0d28\u0d31\u0d7d : ",
    "answer": "\u0d36\u0d36\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d36\u0d7c\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2e",
    "status": "3"
  },
  {
    "id": "375",
    "question": "\u0d05\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4b\u0d2e\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d7c\u0d1c\u0d3f \u0d15\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d40\u0d37\u0d7b \u0d1a\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d7c\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d7b :",
    "answer": "Dr.\u0d36\u0d47\u0d16\u0d7c \u0d2c\u0d38\u0d41",
    "status": "3"
  },
  {
    "id": "376",
    "question": "ISRO \u0d1a\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d7c\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d7b :",
    "answer": "Dr.\u0d0e \u0d0e\u0d38\u0d4d \u0d15\u0d3f\u0d30\u0d7a \u0d15\u0d41\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d7c",
    "status": "3"
  },
  {
    "id": "377",
    "question": "UPAC \u0d1a\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d7c\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d7b : ",
    "answer": "\u0d21\u0d47\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d21\u0d4d\u200c \u0d06\u0d7c . \u0d38\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d2e\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46\u0d39\u0d4d",
    "status": "3"
  },
  {
    "id": "378",
    "question": "UGC \u0d1a\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d7c\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d7b : ",
    "answer": "\u0d35\u0d47\u0d21\u0d4d \u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d36\u0d4d\u200c",
    "status": "3"
  },
  {
    "id": "379",
    "question": "\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d35\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d35\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d36 \u0d15\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d40\u0d37\u0d23\u0d7c :",
    "answer": "\u0d06\u0d7c. \u0d15\u0d46 \u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d42\u0d7c",
    "status": "3"
  },
  {
    "id": "380",
    "question": "\u0d2e\u0d16\u0d4d\u0d2f \u0d24\u0d3f\u0d30\u0d46\u0d1e\u0d4d\u0d1e\u0d46\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d4d \u0d15\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d40\u0d37\u0d23\u0d7c :",
    "answer": "\u0d38\u0d2f\u0d4d\u0d26\u0d4d \u0d28\u0d38\u0d3f\u0d02 \u0d05\u0d39\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d26\u0d4d \u0d38\u0d2f\u0d46\u0d26\u0d4d",
    "status": "3"
  },
  {
    "id": "381",
    "question": "\u0d32\u0d4b\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d38\u0d2d \u0d38\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d40\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d7c :",
    "answer": "\u0d38\u0d41\u0d2e\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30 \u0d2e\u0d39\u0d3e\u0d1c\u0d7b",
    "status": "3"
  },
  {
    "id": "382",
    "question": "\u0d32\u0d4b\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d38\u0d2d \u0d21\u0d46\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d42\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d3f \u0d38\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d40\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d7c : ",
    "answer": "\u0d0e\u0d02 \u0d24\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d3f \u0d26\u0d41\u0d30\u0d48",
    "status": "3"
  },
  {
    "id": "383",
    "question": "\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d1c\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d38\u0d2d\u0d3e \u0d1a\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d7c\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d7b :",
    "answer": "\u0d36\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d40. \u0d2e\u0d41\u0d39\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d26\u0d4d\u200c \u0d39\u0d2e\u0d40\u0d26\u0d4d \u0d05\u0d7b\u0d38\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d3f",
    "status": "3"
  },
  {
    "id": "384",
    "question": "\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d1c\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d38\u0d2d\u0d3e \u0d21\u0d46\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d42\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d3f \u0d1a\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d7c\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d7b :",
    "answer": "\u0d36\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d40. \u0d2a\u0d3f \u0d1c\u0d46 \u0d15\u0d41\u0d30\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d7b\r\n",
    "status": "3"
  },
  {
    "id": "385",
    "question": "\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d1c\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d38\u0d2d\u0d3e \u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d2a\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d37 \u0d28\u0d47\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d35\u0d4d :",
    "answer": "\u0d36\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d40. \u0d17\u0d41\u0d32\u0d3e\u0d02 \u0d28\u0d2c\u0d3f \u0d06\u0d38\u0d3e\u0d26\u0d4d\u200c",
    "status": "3"
  },
  {
    "id": "386",
    "question": "\u0d32\u0d4b\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d38\u0d2d \u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d2a\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d37 \u0d28\u0d47\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d35\u0d4d :",
    "answer": "NILL",
    "status": "3"
  },
  {
    "id": "387",
    "question": "\u0d32\u0d4b\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d38\u0d2d \u0d38\u0d46\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d1f\u0d31\u0d3f \u0d1c\u0d28\u0d31\u0d7d : ",
    "answer": "\u0d05\u0d28\u0d42\u0d2a\u0d4d \u0d2e\u0d3f\u0d36\u0d4d\u0d30",
    "status": "3"
  },
  {
    "id": "388",
    "question": "\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d1c\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d38\u0d2d\u0d3e \u0d38\u0d46\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d1f\u0d31\u0d3f \u0d1c\u0d28\u0d31\u0d7d :",
    "answer": "\u0d36\u0d41\u0d02\u0d37\u0d46\u0d7c \u0d15\u0d46 \u0d37\u0d46\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d2b\u0d4d",
    "status": "3"
  },
  {
    "id": "389",
    "question": "\u0d38\u0d46\u0d7b\u0d38\u0d38\u0d4d \u0d15\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d3f\u0d37\u0d23\u0d7c :",
    "answer": "\u0d36\u0d48\u0d32\u0d47\u0d37\u0d4d ",
    "status": "3"
  },
  {
    "id": "390",
    "question": "\u0d2e\u0d28\u0d41\u0d37\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d35\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d36 \u0d15\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d3f\u0d37\u0d23\u0d7c :",
    "answer": "\u0d39\u0d46\u0d1a\u0d4d \u0d0e\u0d7d \u0d26\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d41 (7\u0d2e\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d46 \u0d35\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f )",
    "status": "3"
  },
  {
    "id": "391",
    "question": "\u0d35\u0d28\u0d3f\u0d24 \u0d15\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d40\u0d37\u0d7b \u0d1a\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d7c\u0d2a\u0d47\u0d34\u0d4d\u0d38\u0d7a : ",
    "answer": "\u0d32\u0d33\u0d3f\u0d24 \u0d15\u0d41\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d30 \u0d2e\u0d02\u0d17\u0d32\u0d02",
    "status": "3"
  },
  {
    "id": "392",
    "question": "\u0d2e\u0d48\u0d28\u0d4b\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d3f \u0d15\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d40\u0d37\u0d7b \u0d1a\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d7c\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d7b : ",
    "answer": "MR. \u0d28\u0d38\u0d40\u0d02 \u0d05\u0d39\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d26\u0d4d",
    "status": "3"
  },
  {
    "id": "393",
    "question": "\u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d4b\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15 \u0d15\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d40\u0d37\u0d7b \u0d1a\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d7c\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d7b : ",
    "answer": "\u0d1c\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d38\u0d4d\u200c \u0d35\u0d3f \u0d08\u0d36\u0d4d\u0d35\u0d30\u0d2f\u0d4d\u0d2f",
    "status": "3"
  },
  {
    "id": "394",
    "question": "\u0d37\u0d46\u0d21\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d42\u0d7e\u0d21\u0d4d \u0d15\u0d3e\u0d38\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d \u0d1a\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d7c\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d7b :",
    "answer": "\u0d2a\u0d3f \u0d0e\u0d7d \u0d2a\u0d41\u0d28\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d3e",
    "status": "3"
  },
  {
    "id": "395",
    "question": "\u0d37\u0d46\u0d21\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d42\u0d7e\u0d21\u0d4d \u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d48\u0d2c\u0d4d \u0d1a\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d7c\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d7b : ",
    "answer": "\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d2e\u0d47\u0d36\u0d4d\u0d35\u0d7c \u0d12\u0d31\u0d4b\u0d7a",
    "status": "3"
  },
  {
    "id": "396",
    "question": "14\u0d2e\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d2b\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d3e\u0d7b\u0d38\u0d4d \u0d15\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d40\u0d37\u0d7b \u0d1a\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d7c\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d7b : ",
    "answer": "\u0d35\u0d48 \u0d35\u0d3f \u0d31\u0d46\u0d21\u0d4d\u200c\u0d21\u0d3f",
    "status": "3"
  },
  {
    "id": "397",
    "question": "21 \u0d2e\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d32\u0d4b \u0d15\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d40\u0d37\u0d7b \u0d1a\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d7c\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d7b :",
    "answer": "\u0d1c\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d38\u0d4d\u200c \u0d2c\u0d7d\u0d2c\u0d40\u0d7c \u0d38\u0d3f\u0d02\u0d17\u0d4d \u0d1a\u0d57\u0d39\u0d3e\u0d7b",
    "status": "3"
  },
  {
    "id": "398",
    "question": "VSSC \u0d1a\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d7c\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d7b :",
    "answer": "DR.\u0d15\u0d46 \u0d36\u0d3f\u0d35\u0d7b ",
    "status": "3"
  },
  {
    "id": "399",
    "question": "\u0d38\u0d46\u0d7bc\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d7d \u0d2c\u0d4b\u0d7c\u0d21\u0d4d \u0d2b\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d3f\u0d02 \u0d38\u0d46\u0d30\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d3f\u0d2b\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d37\u0d7b \u0d1a\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d7c\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d7b : ",
    "answer": "\u0d2a\u0d39\u0d4d\u200c\u0d32\u0d1c\u0d4d \u0d28\u0d3f\u0d39\u0d32\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d3f",
    "status": "3"
  },
  {
    "id": "400",
    "question": "\u0d07\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d7b \u0d12\u0d33\u0d3f\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d \u0d05\u0d38\u0d4b\u0d38\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d47\u0d37\u0d7b \u0d1a\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d7c\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d7b :",
    "answer": "\u0d0e\u0d7b \u0d30\u0d3e\u0d2e\u0d1a\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d7b",
    "status": "3"
  },
  {
    "id": "401",
    "question": "\u0d2a\u0d30\u0d38\u0d4d \u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d\u200c \u0d13\u0d2b\u0d4d\u200c \u0d07\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d1a\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d7c\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d7b :",
    "answer": "\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d26\u0d4d \u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d41",
    "status": "3"
  },
  {
    "id": "402",
    "question": "\u0d31\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d7d\u0d35\u0d47 \u0d2c\u0d4b\u0d7c\u0d21\u0d4d \u0d1a\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d7c\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d7b :",
    "answer": "\u0d0e \u0d15\u0d46 \u0d2e\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d7d",
    "status": "3"
  },
  {
    "id": "403",
    "question": "TRAI \u0d1a\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d7c\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d7b :",
    "answer": "\u0d06\u0d7c \u0d0e\u0d38\u0d4d \u0d36\u0d7c\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2e",
    "status": "3"
  },
  {
    "id": "404",
    "question": "\u0d28\u0d3e\u0d37\u0d23\u0d7d \u0d21\u0d2f\u0d31\u0d3f \u0d21\u0d46\u0d35\u0d32\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d4d \u0d2e\u0d46\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d \u0d2c\u0d4b\u0d7c\u0d21\u0d4d \u0d1a\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d7c\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d7b : ",
    "answer": "\u0d26\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d3f\u0d2a\u0d4d \u0d30\u0d3e\u0d24\u0d4d",
    "status": "3"
  },
  {
    "id": "405",
    "question": "\u0d15\u0d47\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d30 \u0d38\u0d3e\u0d39\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f \u0d05\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d21\u0d2e\u0d3f \u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d38\u0d3f\u0d21\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d\u200c : ",
    "answer": "\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d36\u0d4d\u0d35\u0d28\u0d3e\u0d25\u0d4d \u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d38\u0d3e\u0d26\u0d4d\u200c \u0d24\u0d40\u0d35\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d3f",
    "status": "3"
  },
  {
    "id": "406",
    "question": "\u0d15\u0d47\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d30 \u0d38\u0d02\u0d17\u0d40\u0d24 \u0d28\u0d3e\u0d1f\u0d15 \u0d05\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d21\u0d2e\u0d3f \u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d38\u0d3f\u0d21\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d\u200c :",
    "answer": "\u0d36\u0d47\u0d16\u0d7c \u0d38\u0d46\u0d7b",
    "status": "3"
  },
  {
    "id": "407",
    "question": "\u0d07\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d1a\u0d41\u0d35\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d28\u0d26\u0d3f \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d46\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d4d ?",
    "answer": "\u0d2c\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d39\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d2a\u0d41\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30",
    "status": "1"
  },
  {
    "id": "408",
    "question": "\u0d05\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d37\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d30 \u0d26\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d3e\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d15 \u0d30\u0d47\u0d16 \u0d15\u0d1f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d41 \u0d2a\u0d4b\u0d15\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d15\u0d1f\u0d32\u0d3f\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4d \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d4d",
    "answer": "\u0d2c\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d02\u0d17\u0d4d \u0d15\u0d1f\u0d32\u0d3f\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4d",
    "status": "1"
  },
  {
    "id": "409",
    "question": "\u0d05\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d30\u0d40\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d37 \u0d2a\u0d3e\u0d33\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d33\u0d3f\u0d7d \u0d0f\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d35\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d38\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d24 \u0d15\u0d42\u0d1f\u0d3f\u0d2f \u0d2d\u0d3e\u0d17\u0d02 \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d4d ?",
    "answer": "\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d4b\u0d2a\u0d4b\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d2b\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d7c",
    "status": "1"
  },
  {
    "id": "410",
    "question": "\u0d28\u0d3e\u0d25\u0d41\u0d32 \u0d1a\u0d41\u0d30\u0d02 \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d38\u0d02\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d ?",
    "answer": "\u0d38\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3f\u0d02",
    "status": "1"
  },
  {
    "id": "411",
    "question": "\u0d2d\u0d42\u0d2a\u0d1f \u0d28\u0d3f\u0d7c\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d46\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d41\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d4d \u0d2a\u0d20\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d36\u0d3e\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30 \u0d36\u0d3e\u0d16 \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d4d ?",
    "answer": "\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d7c\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d4a\u0d17\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d2b\u0d3f",
    "status": "1"
  },
  {
    "id": "412",
    "question": "\u0d2d\u0d42\u0d2e\u0d27\u0d4d\u0d2f \u0d30\u0d47\u0d16 \u0d15\u0d1f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d41\u0d2a\u0d4b\u0d15\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d0f\u0d15 \u0d0f\u0d37\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d7b \u0d30\u0d3e\u0d1c\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d02 \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d4d ?",
    "answer": "\u0d07\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4b\u0d28\u0d47\u0d37\u0d4d\u0d2f",
    "status": "1"
  },
  {
    "id": "413",
    "question": "\u0d07\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d7b \u0d2e\u0d39\u0d3e\u0d38\u0d2e\u0d41\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d0f\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d35\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d35\u0d32\u0d3f\u0d2f \u0d26\u0d4d\u0d35\u0d40\u0d2a\u0d4d\u200c \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d4d ?",
    "answer": "\u0d2e\u0d21\u0d17\u0d3e\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d7c",
    "status": "1"
  },
  {
    "id": "414",
    "question": "\u0d0f\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d35\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d15\u0d42\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d24\u0d7d \u0d2a\u0d4b\u0d37\u0d15 \u0d28\u0d26\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d33\u0d41\u0d33\u0d4d\u0d33 \u0d15\u0d47\u0d30\u0d33\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d28\u0d26\u0d3f \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d4d ?",
    "answer": "\u0d2a\u0d46\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d7c",
    "status": "1"
  },
  {
    "id": "415",
    "question": "\u0d15\u0d47\u0d30\u0d33\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d46 \u0d15\u0d7c\u0d23\u0d3e\u0d1f\u0d15\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d15\u0d42\u0d7c\u0d17\u0d41\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d3f \u0d2c\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d27\u0d3f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d1a\u0d41\u0d30\u0d02 \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d4d ?",
    "answer": "\u0d2a\u0d46\u0d30\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d3e\u0d1f\u0d3f \u0d1a\u0d41\u0d30\u0d02",
    "status": "1"
  },
  {
    "id": "416",
    "question": "\u0d32\u0d3f\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d7d \u0d1f\u0d3f\u0d2c\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d\u200c \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d46\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d26\u0d47\u0d36\u0d02 \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d4d ?",
    "answer": "\u0d32\u0d21\u0d3e\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4d",
    "status": "1"
  },
  {
    "id": "417",
    "question": "\u0d32\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d57 \u0d28\u0d17\u0d30\u0d02 \u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d3f \u0d1a\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d28\u0d26\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d40\u0d30\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d ?",
    "answer": "\u0d17\u0d4b\u0d2e\u0d24\u0d3f \u0d28\u0d26\u0d3f",
    "status": "1"
  },
  {
    "id": "418",
    "question": "\u0d28\u0d3e\u0d38\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d \u0d28\u0d17\u0d30\u0d02 \u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d3f \u0d1a\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d28\u0d26\u0d3f \u0d24\u0d40\u0d30\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d ?",
    "answer": "\u0d17\u0d4b\u0d26\u0d3e\u0d35\u0d30\u0d3f",
    "status": "1"
  },
  {
    "id": "419",
    "question": "\u0d05\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d3e\u0d7c\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d7d \u0d07\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f \u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d3e\u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a \u0d06\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f \u0d17\u0d35\u0d47\u0d37\u0d23 \u0d15\u0d47\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d2a\u0d47\u0d30\u0d46\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d ?",
    "answer": "\u0d26\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d37\u0d3f\u0d23 \u0d17\u0d02\u0d17\u0d4b\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d3f",
    "status": "1"
  },
  {
    "id": "420",
    "question": "\u0d2d\u0d42\u0d2e\u0d27\u0d4d\u0d2f \u0d30\u0d47\u0d16\u0d2f\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4d \u0d38\u0d2e\u0d40\u0d2a\u0d2e\u0d41\u0d33\u0d4d\u0d33 \u0d07\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d7b \u0d2e\u0d46\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d4b\u0d2a\u0d4a\u0d33\u0d3f\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d7b \u0d28\u0d17\u0d30\u0d02 \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d4d\r\n?",
    "answer": "\u0d1a\u0d46\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d48 ",
    "status": "1"
  },
  {
    "id": "421",
    "question": "\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d30\u0d41\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d3f\u0d31\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d33\u0d4d\u0d33\u0d3f \u0d28\u0d17\u0d30\u0d02 \u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d3f \u0d1a\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d28\u0d26\u0d3f \u0d24\u0d40\u0d30\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d ?",
    "answer": "\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d35\u0d47\u0d30\u0d3f \u0d28\u0d26\u0d3f",
    "status": "1"
  },
  {
    "id": "422",
    "question": "\u0d24\u0d1e\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d3e\u0d35\u0d42\u0d7c \u0d28\u0d17\u0d30\u0d02 \u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d3f \u0d1a\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d28\u0d26\u0d3f \u0d24\u0d40\u0d30\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d ?",
    "answer": "\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d35\u0d47\u0d30\u0d3f \u0d28\u0d26\u0d3f",
    "status": "1"
  },
  {
    "id": "423",
    "question": "\u0d2e\u0d2f\u0d42\u0d30\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d37\u0d3f \u0d1c\u0d32\u0d35\u0d48\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d24 \u0d2a\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d27\u0d24\u0d3f \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d38\u0d02\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d ?",
    "answer": "\u0d2a\u0d36\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d3f\u0d2e \u0d2c\u0d02\u0d17\u0d3e\u0d7e",
    "status": "1"
  },
  {
    "id": "424",
    "question": "\u0d05\u0d1c\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d40\u0d7c \u0d28\u0d17\u0d30\u0d02 \u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d3f \u0d1a\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d28\u0d26\u0d3f \u0d24\u0d40\u0d30\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d ?",
    "answer": "\u0d32\u0d42\u0d23\u0d3f",
    "status": "1"
  },
  {
    "id": "425",
    "question": "\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d32\u0d39\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d3f \u0d2e\u0d30\u0d41\u0d2d\u0d42\u0d2e\u0d3f \u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d3f \u0d1a\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d0e\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d1f\u0d46 ?",
    "answer": "\u0d26\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d37\u0d3f\u0d23\u0d3e\u0d2b\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15",
    "status": "1"
  },
  {
    "id": "426",
    "question": "\u0d2e\u0d27\u0d41\u0d30 \u0d28\u0d17\u0d30\u0d02 \u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d3f \u0d1a\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d28\u0d26\u0d3f \u0d24\u0d40\u0d30\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d ?",
    "answer": "\u0d35\u0d48\u0d17",
    "status": "1"
  },
  {
    "id": "427",
    "question": "\u0d17\u0d4b\u0d26\u0d3e\u0d35\u0d30\u0d3f \u0d28\u0d26\u0d3f \u0d09\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2d\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d0e\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d28\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d4d ?",
    "answer": "\u0d28\u0d3e\u0d38\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d \u0d15\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d41\u0d15\u0d7e",
    "status": "1"
  },
  {
    "id": "428",
    "question": "\u0d0f\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d35\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d28\u0d40\u0d33\u0d02 \u0d15\u0d42\u0d1f\u0d3f\u0d2f \u0d39\u0d3f\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d32\u0d2f\u0d7b \u0d28\u0d26\u0d3f \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d4d ?",
    "answer": "\u0d17\u0d02\u0d17",
    "status": "1"
  },
  {
    "id": "429",
    "question": "\u0d31\u0d37\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d26\u0d47\u0d36\u0d40\u0d2f \u0d28\u0d26\u0d3f \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d4d ?",
    "answer": "\u0d35\u0d4b\u0d7e\u0d17",
    "status": "1"
  },
  {
    "id": "430",
    "question": "\u0d2e\u0d4b\u0d39\u0d7b\u0d1c\u0d26\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d4a ,\u0d39\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d40 \u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d1a\u0d40\u0d28 \u0d28\u0d17\u0d30\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d19\u0d7e \u0d07\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d4d \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d30\u0d3e\u0d1c\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d3f \u0d1a\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d41 ?",
    "answer": "\u0d2a\u0d3e\u0d15\u0d3f\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d3e\u0d7b",
    "status": "1"
  },
  {
    "id": "431",
    "question": "\u0d0f\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d38\u0d02\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d \u0d2c\u0d17\u0d4d\u0d32\u0d3f\u0d39\u0d3e\u0d7c \u0d05\u0d23\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d46\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d4d \u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d3f \u0d1a\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d24\u0d4d ?",
    "answer": "\u0d1c\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d41 \u0d15\u0d3e\u0d36\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d40\u0d7c",
    "status": "1"
  },
  {
    "id": "432",
    "question": "\u0d1f\u0d48\u0d17\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d38\u0d4d\u200c \u0d28\u0d26\u0d3f \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d30\u0d3e\u0d1c\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d42\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d12\u0d34\u0d41\u0d15\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d41 ?",
    "answer": "\u0d07\u0d31\u0d3e\u0d16\u0d4d",
    "status": "1"
  },
  {
    "id": "433",
    "question": "\u0d15\u0d47\u0d30\u0d33\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d28\u0d26\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d \u0d0f\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d35\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d15\u0d42\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d24\u0d7d \u0d05\u0d23\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d46\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d15\u0d7e \u0d09\u0d33\u0d4d\u0d33\u0d24\u0d4d ?",
    "answer": "\u0d2a\u0d46\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d7c",
    "status": "1"
  },
  {
    "id": "434",
    "question": "\u0d07\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d0f\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d35\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d35\u0d32\u0d3f\u0d2f \u0d09\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d41 \u0d1c\u0d32 \u0d24\u0d1f\u0d3e\u0d15\u0d02 \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d ?",
    "answer": "\u0d1a\u0d3f\u0d7d\u0d15( \u0d12\u0d31\u0d40\u0d38 )",
    "status": "1"
  },
  {
    "id": "435",
    "question": "\u0d39\u0d3f\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d41\u0d21\u0d4d \u0d05\u0d23\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d46\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d4d \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d28\u0d26\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d \u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d3f \u0d1a\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d24\u0d4d ?",
    "answer": "\u0d2e\u0d39\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d26\u0d3f",
    "status": "1"
  },
  {
    "id": "436",
    "question": "\u0d07\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d0f\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d35\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d35\u0d32\u0d3f\u0d2f \u0d36\u0d41\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d27\u0d1c\u0d32 \u0d24\u0d1f\u0d3e\u0d15\u0d02 \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d4d ?",
    "answer": "\u0d15\u0d4a\u0d32\u0d4d\u0d32\u0d46\u0d30\u0d41",
    "status": "1"
  },
  {
    "id": "437",
    "question": "\u0d2a\u0d7c\u0d35\u0d24\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d19\u0d33\u0d46\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d41\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d41\u0d33\u0d4d\u0d33 \u0d2a\u0d20\u0d28\u0d02 \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d2a\u0d47\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d7d \u0d05\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d46\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d41 ?",
    "answer": "\u0d12\u0d31\u0d4b\u0d33\u0d1c\u0d3f",
    "status": "1"
  },
  {
    "id": "438",
    "question": "\u0d15\u0d4a\u0d2f\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d21\u0d3e\u0d02 \u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d3f \u0d1a\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d38\u0d02\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d ?",
    "answer": "\u0d2e\u0d39\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d37\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d30",
    "status": "1"
  },
  {
    "id": "439",
    "question": "\u0d38\u0d02\u0d2d\u0d3e\u0d7c \u0d24\u0d1f\u0d3e\u0d15\u0d02 \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d38\u0d02\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d ?",
    "answer": "\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d1c\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d3e\u0d7b",
    "status": "1"
  },
  {
    "id": "440",
    "question": "\u0d07\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d0f\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d35\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d1a\u0d40\u0d28\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d2f \u0d2a\u0d7c\u0d35\u0d24\u0d28\u0d3f\u0d30 \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d4d ?",
    "answer": "\u0d06\u0d30\u0d35\u0d32\u0d4d\u0d32\u0d3f \u0d2a\u0d7c\u0d35\u0d24\u0d02",
    "status": "1"
  },
  {
    "id": "441",
    "question": "\u0d05\u0d7d\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d3f \u0d21\u0d3e\u0d02 \u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d3f \u0d1a\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d28\u0d26\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d ?",
    "answer": "\u0d15\u0d43\u0d37\u0d4d\u0d23 \u0d28\u0d26\u0d3f",
    "status": "1"
  },
  {
    "id": "442",
    "question": "\u0d2e\u0d23\u0d4d\u200d\u0d38\u0d42\u0d23\u0d4d\u200d \u0d15\u0d3e\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d41\u0d15\u0d7e \u0d15\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d1f\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a \u0d28\u0d3e\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d7b \u0d06\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d30\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d41 ?",
    "answer": "\u0d39\u0d3f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d3e\u0d32\u0d38\u0d4d",
    "status": "1"
  },
  {
    "id": "443",
    "question": "\u0d39\u0d3f\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d32\u0d2f \u0d2a\u0d3e\u0d7c\u0d35\u0d24\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d28\u0d40\u0d33\u0d02 \u0d0e\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d ?",
    "answer": "2400 \u0d15\u0d3f \u0d2e\u0d40",
    "status": "1"
  },
  {
    "id": "444",
    "question": "\u0d05\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d35\u0d3e\u0d7b \u0d05\u0d23\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d46\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d4d \u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d3f \u0d1a\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d30\u0d3e\u0d1c\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d ?",
    "answer": "\u0d08\u0d1c\u0d3f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d",
    "status": "1"
  },
  {
    "id": "445",
    "question": "\u0d0f\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d28\u0d26\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d30\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d \u0d37\u0d3e\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d39\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d4d \u0d28\u0d17\u0d30\u0d02 \u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d3f \u0d1a\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d24\u0d4d ?",
    "answer": "\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d38\u0d3f",
    "status": "1"
  },
  {
    "id": "446",
    "question": "\u0d31\u0d4b\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d40\u0d38\u0d4d \u0d2a\u0d7c\u0d35\u0d24\u0d02 \u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d3f \u0d1a\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d30\u0d3e\u0d1c\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d ?",
    "answer": "\u0d05\u0d2e\u0d47\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15",
    "status": "1"
  },
  {
    "id": "447",
    "question": "\u0d32\u0d4b\u0d15\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d0f\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d35\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d35\u0d32\u0d3f\u0d2f \u0d24\u0d1f\u0d3e\u0d15\u0d02 \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d ?",
    "answer": "\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d7b \u0d38\u0d40",
    "status": "1"
  },
  {
    "id": "448",
    "question": "\u0d2e\u0d57\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d4d \u0d05\u0d31\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d2a\u0d7c\u0d35\u0d24\u0d02 \u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d3f \u0d1a\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d30\u0d3e\u0d1c\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d ?",
    "answer": "\u0d24\u0d41\u0d7c\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3f",
    "status": "1"
  },
  {
    "id": "449",
    "question": "\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d40 \u0d17\u0d4b\u0d7c\u0d1c\u0d38\u0d4d \u0d21\u0d3e\u0d02 \u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d3f \u0d1a\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d30\u0d3e\u0d1c\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d ?",
    "answer": "\u0d1a\u0d48\u0d28",
    "status": "1"
  },
  {
    "id": "450",
    "question": "\u0d0f\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d30\u0d3e\u0d1c\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d \u0d28\u0d47\u0d35 \u0d28\u0d26\u0d3f \u0d12\u0d34\u0d41\u0d15\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d24\u0d4d ?",
    "answer": "\u0d31\u0d37\u0d4d\u0d2f",
    "status": "1"
  },
  {
    "id": "451",
    "question": "\u0d0e\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d05\u0d17\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d3f \u0d2a\u0d7c\u0d35\u0d24\u0d02 \u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d3f \u0d1a\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d30\u0d3e\u0d1c\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d ?",
    "answer": "\u0d07\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d32\u0d3f",
    "status": "1"
  },
  {
    "id": "452",
    "question": "\u0d06\u0d30\u0d35\u0d32\u0d4d\u0d32\u0d3f \u0d2a\u0d7c\u0d35\u0d24\u0d28\u0d3f\u0d30 \u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d26\u0d47\u0d36\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d3f \u0d1a\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d38\u0d41\u0d16\u0d35\u0d3e\u0d38 \u0d15\u0d47\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d02 \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d ?",
    "answer": "\u0d2e\u0d4c\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d4d \u0d05\u0d2c\u0d41",
    "status": "1"
  },
  {
    "id": "453",
    "question": "\u0d15\u0d47\u0d30\u0d33\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d06\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d46 \u0d06\u0d7c\u0d1a\u0d4d \u0d21\u0d3e\u0d02 \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d ?",
    "answer": "\u0d07\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3f \u0d21\u0d3e\u0d02",
    "status": "1"
  },
  {
    "id": "454",
    "question": "\u0d0f\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d32\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d35\u0d46\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d \u0d2a\u0d36\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d3f\u0d2e \u0d18\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d35\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d2a\u0d42\u0d7c\u0d35\u0d18\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d35\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d2f\u0d4b\u0d1c\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d24\u0d4d ?",
    "answer": "\u0d28\u0d40\u0d32\u0d17\u0d3f\u0d30\u0d3f",
    "status": "1"
  },
  {
    "id": "455",
    "question": "\u0d07\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d0f\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d35\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d28\u0d40\u0d33\u0d02 \u0d15\u0d42\u0d1f\u0d3f\u0d2f \u0d05\u0d23\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d46\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d4d \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d ?",
    "answer": "\u0d39\u0d3f\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d41\u0d21\u0d4d",
    "status": "1"
  },
  {
    "id": "456",
    "question": "\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d31\u0d3e\u0d7e \u0d2a\u0d7c\u0d35\u0d24\u0d02 \u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d3f \u0d1a\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d30\u0d3e\u0d1c\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d ?",
    "answer": "\u0d31\u0d37\u0d4d\u0d2f",
    "status": "1"
  },
  {
    "id": "457",
    "question": "\u0d0f\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d35\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d1a\u0d46\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d2f \u0d28\u0d3e\u0d32\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15 \u0d38\u0d02\u0d16\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d0f\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d35\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d35\u0d32\u0d3f\u0d2f \u0d2e\u0d42\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15 \u0d38\u0d02\u0d16\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d24\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d41\u0d33\u0d4d\u0d33 \u0d35\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d38\u0d2e\u0d46\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30 ?",
    "answer": "1",
    "status": "5"
  },
  {
    "id": "458",
    "question": "\u0d12\u0d30\u0d41 \u0d24\u0d3e\u0d2e\u0d30\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d41 \u0d33\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d24\u0d3e\u0d2e\u0d30\u0d15\u0d33\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d0e\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d23\u0d02 \u0d26\u0d3f\u0d35\u0d38\u0d35\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d07\u0d30\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d15\u0d41\u0d02 .\u0d0f\u0d34\u0d3e\u0d2e\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d46 \u0d26\u0d3f\u0d35\u0d38\u0d02 \u0d24\u0d3e\u0d2e\u0d30\u0d15\u0d7e \u0d15\u0d4a\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d4d \u0d15\u0d41\u0d33\u0d02 \u0d2a\u0d15\u0d41\u0d24\u0d3f \u0d28\u0d3f\u0d31\u0d1e\u0d4d\u0d1e\u0d41.\r\n\u0d2e\u0d41\u0d34\u0d41\u0d35\u0d28\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d28\u0d3f\u0d31\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d7b \u0d0e\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30 \u0d26\u0d3f\u0d35\u0d38\u0d02 \u0d15\u0d42\u0d1f\u0d3f \u0d35\u0d47\u0d23\u0d02?",
    "answer": "\u0d12\u0d30\u0d41 \u0d26\u0d3f\u0d35\u0d38\u0d02.",
    "status": "5"
  },
  {
    "id": "459",
    "question": "20 x 36x 42x 84 x O = ?",
    "answer": "0",
    "status": "5"
  },
  {
    "id": "460",
    "question": "0, I, 2 \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d40 \u0d38\u0d02\u0d16\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d15\u0d7e \u0d06\u0d35\u0d7c\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d24\u0d46 \u0d09\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d3e\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d35\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d0f\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d35\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d35\u0d32\u0d3f\u0d2f \u0d38\u0d02\u0d16\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d2f\u0d47\u0d24\u0d4d?",
    "answer": "210",
    "status": "5"
  },
  {
    "id": "461",
    "question": " \u0d12\u0d30\u0d41 \u0d05\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1b\u0d28\u0d46\u0d31\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d2e\u0d15\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d07\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d4b\u0d34\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d46 \u0d35\u0d2f\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d38\u0d41\u0d15\u0d33\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d24\u0d41\u0d15 49. \u0d2a\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d41 \u0d35\u0d7c\u0d37\u0d02 \u0d15\u0d34\u0d3f\u0d1e\u0d4d\u0d1e\u0d3e\u0d7d \u0d07\u0d30\u0d41\u0d35\u0d30\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d35\u0d2f\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d38\u0d41\u0d15\u0d33\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d24\u0d41\u0d15 \u0d0e\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d41\u0d02 ?",
    "answer": "69",
    "status": "5"
  },
  {
    "id": "462",
    "question": " \u0d12\u0d30\u0d41 \u0d2e\u0d40\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d7c \u0d28\u0d40\u0d33\u0d35\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d12\u0d30\u0d41 \u0d2e\u0d40\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d7c \u0d35\u0d40\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d2e\u0d41\u0d33\u0d4d\u0d33 \u0d24\u0d41\u0d23\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4d 50 \u0d30\u0d42\u0d2a\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d \u0d35\u0d3f\u0d32.\r\n\u0d0e\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3f\u0d7d, 2 \u0d2e\u0d40\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d7c \u0d28\u0d40\u0d33\u0d35\u0d41\u0d02 2 \u0d2e\u0d40\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d7c \u0d35\u0d40\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d2e\u0d41\u0d33\u0d4d\u0d33 \u0d24\u0d41\u0d23\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4d \u0d0e\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30 \u0d30\u0d42\u0d2a\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d15\u0d41\u0d02 ?",
    "answer": "200 \u0d30\u0d42\u0d2a",
    "status": "5"
  },
  {
    "id": "463",
    "question": "\u0d32\u0d4b\u0d15 \u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d36\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d28\u0d3e\u0d2f \u0d12\u0d30\u0d41 \u0d07\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d7b \u0d17\u0d23\u0d3f\u0d24 \u0d36\u0d3e\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d1c\u0d4d\u0d1e\u0d7b?",
    "answer": "\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d41\u0d1c\u0d7b",
    "status": "5"
  },
  {
    "id": "464",
    "question": "\u0d12\u0d30\u0d41 \u0d15\u0d41\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d05\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d7d \u0d28\u0d3f\u0d31\u0d2f\u0d46 \u0d2a\u0d3e\u0d32\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d15\u0d42\u0d1f\u0d3f 5 \u0d15\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4b \u0d2d\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d2e\u0d41\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d4d.\r\n\u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d3e\u0d7d \u0d15\u0d41\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d2a\u0d15\u0d41\u0d24\u0d3f \u0d2a\u0d3e\u0d32\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d15\u0d42\u0d1f\u0d3f 3 \u0d15\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4b \u0d2d\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d2e\u0d41\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d46\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3f\u0d7d \u0d15\u0d41\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d2d\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d02 \u0d0e\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30 ?",
    "answer": "\u0d12\u0d30\u0d41 \u0d15\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4b\u0d17\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d02",
    "status": "5"
  },
  {
    "id": "465",
    "question": "1 \u0d2e\u0d41\u0d24\u0d7d 1000 \u0d35\u0d30\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d33\u0d4d\u0d33 \u0d38\u0d02\u0d16\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d15\u0d33\u0d3f\u0d7d \u0d0f\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d35\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d35\u0d32\u0d3f\u0d2f \u0d12\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d38\u0d02\u0d16\u0d4d\u0d2f ?",
    "answer": "999",
    "status": "5"
  },
  {
    "id": "466",
    "question": "\u0d0f\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d35\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d1a\u0d46\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d2f \u0d05\u0d16\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d21 \u0d38\u0d02\u0d16\u0d4d\u0d2f?",
    "answer": "0",
    "status": "5"
  },
  {
    "id": "467",
    "question": "\u0d17\u0d02\u0d17, \u0d2f\u0d2e\u0d41\u0d28, \u0d38\u0d30\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d35\u0d24\u0d3f \u0d28\u0d26\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d33\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d38\u0d02\u0d17\u0d2e\u0d02 \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d38\u0d02\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d?\r\n",
    "answer": "\u0d09\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d26\u0d47\u0d36\u0d4d\r\n",
    "status": "1"
  },
  {
    "id": "468",
    "question": "\u0d0f\u0d24\u0d41 \u0d28\u0d26\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d2a\u0d4b\u0d37\u0d15\u0d28\u0d26\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d33\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4d\u200d \u0d28\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d \u0d2a\u0d1e\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d3e\u0d2c\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d \u0d06 \u0d2a\u0d47\u0d30\u0d41\u0d32\u0d2d\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d24\u0d4d?\r\n",
    "answer": "\u0d38\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d27\u0d41\r\n",
    "status": "1"
  },
  {
    "id": "469",
    "question": "\u0d15\u0d4a\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d23\u0d4d\u200d \u0d31\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4d\u200d\u0d35\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d28\u0d40\u0d33\u0d02?\r\n",
    "answer": "760 \u0d15\u0d3f.\u0d2e\u0d40\r\n",
    "status": "1"
  },
  {
    "id": "470",
    "question": "'\u0d07\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d2a\u0d42\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4b\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d02' \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d4d?\r\n",
    "answer": "\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d36\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d40\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d\r\n",
    "status": "1"
  },
  {
    "id": "471",
    "question": "\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d02 \u0d38\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d2d\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d4d \u0d38\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d47\u0d38\u0d4d \u0d38\u0d46\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d7c \u0d0e\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d1f\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d?\r\n",
    "answer": "\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d30\u0d41\u0d35\u0d28\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d2a\u0d41\u0d30\u0d02\r\n",
    "status": "1"
  },
  {
    "id": "472",
    "question": "\u0d28\u0d3e\u0d37\u0d23\u0d32\u0d4d\u200d \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u200d\u0d35\u0d2f\u0d4b\u0d7a\u0d2e\u0d46\u0d7b\u0d31\u0d4d \u0d0e\u0d1e\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d40\u0d2f\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d19\u0d4d \u0d07\u0d28\u0d4d\u200d\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d42\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d4d \u0d0e\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d1f\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d?\r\n",
    "answer": "\u0d28\u0d3e\u0d17\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d41\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d\r\n",
    "status": "1"
  },
  {
    "id": "473",
    "question": "\u0d0f\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d30\u0d3e\u0d1c\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u200d\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d38\u0d3e\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d47\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d15 \u0d38\u0d39\u0d15\u0d30\u0d23\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4b\u0d1f\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d \u0d12\u0d31\u0d40\u0d38\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d31\u0d42\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d47\u0d32 \u0d38\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d40\u0d32\u0d4d\u200d \u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d32\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d4d\u200d\u0d31\u0d4d \u0d28\u0d3f\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d24\u0d4d?\r\n",
    "answer": "\u0d1c\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d\u0d2e\u0d28\u0d3f\r\n",
    "status": "1"
  },
  {
    "id": "474",
    "question": "\u0d0f\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d35\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d15\u0d42\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d24\u0d32\u0d4d\u200d \u0d38\u0d02\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d19\u0d33\u0d41\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d3f \u0d05\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f \u0d2a\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3f\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d07\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d28\u0d4d\u200d \u0d38\u0d02\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d02?\r\n",
    "answer": "\u0d09\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d26\u0d47\u0d36\u0d4d\r\n",
    "status": "1"
  },
  {
    "id": "475",
    "question": "\u0d07\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d32\u0d4b\u0d15 \u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d38\u0d3f\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d27\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d2f \u0d27\u0d3e\u0d24\u0d41\u0d2e\u0d47\u0d16\u0d32?\r\n",
    "answer": "\u0d1b\u0d4b\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d3e \u0d28\u0d3e\u0d17\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d41\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d \u0d2a\u0d40\u0d20\u0d2d\u0d42\u0d2e\u0d3f\r\n",
    "status": "1"
  },
  {
    "id": "476",
    "question": "\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d35\u0d47\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d2a\u0d4b\u0d37\u0d15\u0d28\u0d26\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d33\u0d4d\u200d?\r\n",
    "answer": "\u0d15\u0d2c\u0d28\u0d3f , \u0d05\u0d2e\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d35\u0d24\u0d3f\r\n",
    "status": "1"
  },
  {
    "id": "477",
    "question": "\u0d07\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d31\u0d2c\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d\u0d15\u0d43\u0d37\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d0e\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d36\u0d24\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d \u0d15\u0d47\u0d30\u0d33\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d41\u0d33\u0d4d\u0d33\u0d24\u0d4d?\r\n",
    "answer": "92%\r\n",
    "status": "1"
  },
  {
    "id": "478",
    "question": "\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d35\u0d24\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30 \u0d07\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d2e\u0d27\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d2d\u0d3e\u0d17\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d41\u0d33\u0d4d\u0d33 \u0d28\u0d17\u0d30\u0d02\r\n",
    "answer": "\u0d28\u0d3e\u0d17\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d42\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d",
    "status": "1"
  },
  {
    "id": "479",
    "question": "'\u0d15\u0d3f\u0d34\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u200d\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d38\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4b\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d32 \u0d28\u0d4d\u200d\u0d21\u0d4d' \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d46\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d07\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d28\u0d4d\u200d \u0d38\u0d02\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d02?\r\n",
    "answer": "\u0d1c\u0d2c\u0d32\u0d4d\u200d\u0d2a\u0d42\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d\r\n",
    "status": "1"
  },
  {
    "id": "480",
    "question": "\u0d32\u0d4b\u0d15\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4d\u200d \u0d0f\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d35\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d15\u0d42\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d24\u0d32\u0d4d\u200d \u0d38\u0d4d\u0d35\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d\u0d23\u0d02 \u0d09\u0d2a\u0d2f\u0d4b\u0d17\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d30\u0d3e\u0d1c\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d02 \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d4d?\r\n",
    "answer": "\u0d07\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f\r\n",
    "status": "1"
  },
  {
    "id": "481",
    "question": "\u0d38\u0d42\u0d30\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d4b\u0d26\u0d2f\u0d35\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d38\u0d42\u0d30\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d2e\u0d2f\u0d35\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d15\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d3e\u0d35\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d32\u0d02?\r\n",
    "answer": "\u0d15\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d15\u0d41\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d3f\r\n",
    "status": "1"
  },
  {
    "id": "482",
    "question": "\u0d15\u0d4b\u0d33\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d \u0d38\u0d4d\u0d35\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d\u0d23\u0d16\u0d28\u0d3f \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d38\u0d02\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d?\r\n",
    "answer": "\u0d15\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d\u0d23\u0d3e\u0d1f\u0d15\r\n",
    "status": "1"
  },
  {
    "id": "483",
    "question": "\u0d1c\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d41\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d15\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d15\u0d41\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d2c\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d27\u0d3f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d4d \u0d13\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u200d \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d.?\r\n",
    "answer": "\u0d39\u0d3f\u0d2e\u0d38\u0d3e\u0d17\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d \u0d0e\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d38\u0d4d\r\n",
    "status": "1"
  },
  {
    "id": "484",
    "question": "\u0d38\u0d24\u0d47\u0d23\u0d4d\u200d \u0d31\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4d\u200d\u0d35\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d2e\u0d41\u0d16\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d06\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d02 \u0d0e\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d1f\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d?\r\n",
    "answer": "\u0d1a\u0d46\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d48\r\n",
    "status": "1"
  },
  {
    "id": "485",
    "question": "\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d36\u0d40\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d\u0d37 \u0d35\u0d30\u0d41\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d02 \u0d0f\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d35\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d15\u0d41\u0d31\u0d1e\u0d4d\u0d1e \u0d07\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d28\u0d4d\u200d \u0d38\u0d02\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d02?\r\n",
    "answer": "\u0d2c\u0d3f\u0d39\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d\r\n",
    "status": "1"
  },
  {
    "id": "486",
    "question": "\u0d07\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4d\u200d \u0d0f\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d35\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d15\u0d42\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d24\u0d32\u0d4d\u200d \u0d28\u0d17\u0d30\u0d35\u0d32\u0d4d\u200d\u0d15\u0d43\u0d24\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d2f \u0d38\u0d02\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d02?\r\n",
    "answer": "\u0d17\u0d4b\u0d35\r\n",
    "status": "1"
  },
  {
    "id": "487",
    "question": "\u0d1f\u0d3e\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d3e \u0d05\u0d2f\u0d23\u0d4d\u200d \u0d06\u0d28\u0d4d\u200d\u0d21\u0d4d \u0d38\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d40\u0d32\u0d4d\u200d \u0d2b\u0d3e\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d31\u0d3f \u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d32\u0d02?\r\n",
    "answer": "\u0d1c\u0d02\u0d37\u0d21\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d41\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d",
    "status": "1"
  },
  {
    "id": "488",
    "question": "\u0d21\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d3f\u0d17\u0d3e\u0d02 \u0d35\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d1c\u0d40\u0d35\u0d3f \u0d38\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d47\u0d24\u0d02 \u0d0e\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d1f\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d?\r\n",
    "answer": "\u0d36\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d40\u0d28\u0d17\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d\r\n",
    "status": "1"
  },
  {
    "id": "489",
    "question": "\u0d32\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d37\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d35\u0d40\u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d2d\u0d3e\u0d37?\r\n",
    "answer": "\u0d2e\u0d32\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d33\u0d02\r\n",
    "status": "1"
  },
  {
    "id": "490",
    "question": "\u0d07\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d2a\u0d3e\u0d15\u0d3f\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d41\u0d2e\u0d3f\u0d1f\u0d2f\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4d \u0d38\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d\u0d35\u0d40\u0d38\u0d4d \u0d28\u0d1f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d24\u0d40\u0d35\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d3f?\r\n",
    "answer": "\u0d38\u0d02\u0d1c\u0d4b\u0d27\u0d3e \u0d0e\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d38\u0d4d\r\n",
    "status": "1"
  },
  {
    "id": "491",
    "question": "\u0d18\u0d3e\u0d28 \u0d2a\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d37\u0d3f\u0d38\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d47\u0d24\u0d02 \u0d0e\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d1f\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d?\r\n",
    "answer": "\u0d2d\u0d30\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d42\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d\r\n",
    "status": "1"
  },
  {
    "id": "492",
    "question": "\u0d07\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d3e \u0d1a\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d38\u0d41\u0d35\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d23 \u0d15\u0d3e\u0d32\u0d18\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d02 \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d46\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d24\u0d4d ?\r\n",
    "answer": "\u0d17\u0d41\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d32\u0d18\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d02\r\n",
    "status": "2"
  },
  {
    "id": "493",
    "question": "\u0d0f\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d35\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d15\u0d41\u0d31\u0d1e\u0d4d\u0d1e\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d32\u0d02 \u0d2d\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d3f\u0d30\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d38\u0d41\u0d32\u0d4d\u200d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d4d\u200d \u0d35\u0d02\u0d36\u0d02 ?\r\n",
    "answer": "\u0d16\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4d\u200d\u0d1c\u0d3f \u0d35\u0d02\u0d36\u0d02\r\n",
    "status": "2"
  },
  {
    "id": "494",
    "question": "\u0d36\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d40 \u0d2c\u0d41\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d27\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d2f\u0d25\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d25 \u0d28\u0d3e\u0d2e\u0d02 ?\r\n",
    "answer": "\u0d38\u0d3f\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d27\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d28\u0d4d\u200d\r\n",
    "status": "2"
  },
  {
    "id": "495",
    "question": "\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d1c\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d1c \u0d1a\u0d4b\u0d33\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d2d\u0d30\u0d23 \u0d24\u0d32\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d02 ?\r\n",
    "answer": "\u0d24\u0d1e\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d3e\u0d35\u0d42\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d\r\n",
    "status": "2"
  },
  {
    "id": "496",
    "question": "\u0d1c\u0d48\u0d28\u0d2e\u0d24\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 23- \u0d24\u0d40\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d30\u0d28\u0d4d\u200d ?\r\n",
    "answer": "\u0d2a\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d\u0d36\u0d4d\u0d35\u0d28\u0d3e\u0d25\u0d28\u0d4d\u200d\r\n",
    "status": "2"
  },
  {
    "id": "497",
    "question": "\u0d36\u0d3f\u0d35\u0d1c\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4d \u0d1b\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d2a\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d02 \u0d32\u0d2d\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a \u0d35\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d\u0d37\u0d02 ?\r\n",
    "answer": "1674\r\n",
    "status": "2"
  },
  {
    "id": "498",
    "question": "\u0d2c\u0d41\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d27\u0d2e\u0d24\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d15\u0d4b\u0d23\u0d4d\u200d\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u200d ?\r\n",
    "answer": "\u0d05\u0d36\u0d4b\u0d15\u0d28\u0d4d\u200d\r\n",
    "status": "2"
  },
  {
    "id": "499",
    "question": "\u0d0f\u0d24\u0d41 \u0d30\u0d3e\u0d1c\u0d3e\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d05\u0d02\u0d2c\u0d3e\u0d38\u0d3f\u0d21\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d \u0d24\u0d4b\u0d2e\u0d38\u0d4d \u0d31\u0d4b\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d02, \u0d35\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d02 \u0d39\u0d4b\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u200d\u0d38\u0d41\u0d02 ?\r\n",
    "answer": "\u0d1c\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d02\u0d38\u0d4d I\r\n",
    "status": "2"
  },
  {
    "id": "500",
    "question": "\u0d32\u0d4b\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d32\u0d4d\u200d \u0d15\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d24\u0d4d ?\r\n",
    "answer": "\u0d0e\u0d38\u0d4d.\u0d06\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d. \u0d31\u0d3e\u0d35\u0d41\r\n",
    "status": "2"
  },
  {
    "id": "501",
    "question": "\u0d06\u0d17\u0d4d\u0d30 \u0d15\u0d4b\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f \u0d2a\u0d23\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d34\u0d3f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d4d ?\r\n",
    "answer": "\u0d05\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d2c\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d\r\n",
    "status": "2"
  },
  {
    "id": "502",
    "question": "\u0d07\u0d02\u0d17\u0d4d\u0d33\u0d40\u0d37\u0d4d \u0d08\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d3e \u0d15\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d28\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d2e\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4a\u0d30\u0d41 \u0d2a\u0d47\u0d30\u0d4d ?\r\n",
    "answer": "\u0d1c\u0d4b\u0d23\u0d4d\u200d \u0d15\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d28\u0d3f\r\n",
    "status": "2"
  },
  {
    "id": "503",
    "question": "\u0d1a\u0d57\u0d38 \u0d2f\u0d41\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d27\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4d\u200d \u0d37\u0d47\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d\u0d37 \u0d2a\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d1c\u0d2f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d46\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d06\u0d30\u0d46 ?\r\n",
    "answer": "\u0d39\u0d41\u0d2e\u0d2f\u0d42\u0d23\u0d4d\u200d\r\n",
    "status": "2"
  },
  {
    "id": "504",
    "question": "\u0d16\u0d41\u0d31\u0d02 \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d46\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d06\u0d30\u0d4d ?\r\n",
    "answer": "\u0d37\u0d3e\u0d1c\u0d39\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d4d\u200d\r\n",
    "status": "2"
  },
  {
    "id": "505",
    "question": "\u0d17\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d38\u0d41\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d26\u0d40\u0d28\u0d4d\u200d \u0d24\u0d41\u0d17\u0d4d\u0d32\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d2f\u0d25\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d25 \u0d2a\u0d47\u0d30\u0d4d ?\r\n",
    "answer": "\u0d17\u0d3e\u0d38\u0d3f \u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d32\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\r\n",
    "status": "2"
  },
  {
    "id": "506",
    "question": "\u0d2a\u0d3e\u0d1f\u0d32\u0d40\u0d2a\u0d41\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d02 \u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d3e\u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d24\u0d4d ?\r\n",
    "answer": "\u0d05\u0d1c\u0d3e\u0d24\u0d36\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d41\r\n",
    "status": "2"
  },
  {
    "id": "507",
    "question": "\u0d21\u0d32\u0d4d\u200d\u0d39\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d06\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d46 \u0d38\u0d41\u0d32\u0d4d\u200d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d4d\u200d \u0d35\u0d02\u0d36\u0d02 ?\r\n",
    "answer": "\u0d05\u0d1f\u0d3f\u0d2e \u0d35\u0d02\u0d36\u0d02\r\n",
    "status": "2"
  },
  {
    "id": "508",
    "question": "\u0d2e\u0d39\u0d3e\u0d35\u0d40\u0d30\u0d28\u0d4d\u200d \u0d38\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d27\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d35\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d\u0d37\u0d02 ?\r\n",
    "answer": "BC.468, \u0d2a\u0d35\u0d2a\u0d41\u0d30\u0d3f\r\n",
    "status": "2"
  },
  {
    "id": "509",
    "question": "\u0d30\u0d1c\u0d2a\u0d41\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30 \u0d36\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d3e\u0d26\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d28\u0d4d\u200d \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d46\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d06\u0d30\u0d4d ?\r\n",
    "answer": "\u0d39\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d\u0d37\u0d35\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d\u0d27\u0d28\u0d28\u0d4d\u200d\r\n",
    "status": "2"
  },
  {
    "id": "510",
    "question": "\u0d39\u0d48\u0d26\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d2c\u0d3e\u0d26\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d3e\u0d2a\u0d15\u0d28\u0d4d\u200d ?\r\n",
    "answer": "\u0d15\u0d41\u0d32\u0d40\u0d15\u0d41\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d2c\u0d4d\u0d37\u0d3e\r\n",
    "status": "2"
  },
  {
    "id": "511",
    "question": "\u0d36\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d3f \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d46\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d06\u0d30\u0d4d ?\r\n",
    "answer": "\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d26\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d28\u0d4d\u200d\r\n",
    "status": "2"
  },
  {
    "id": "512",
    "question": "\u0d15\u0d32\u0d4d\u200d\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f \u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d3e\u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d24\u0d4d ?\r\n",
    "answer": "\u0d1c\u0d4b\u0d2c\u0d4d \u0d1a\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d\u0d28\u0d4b\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4d\r\n",
    "status": "2"
  },
  {
    "id": "513",
    "question": "\u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d38\u0d4d \u0d07\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f \u0d2c\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4d\u200d \u0d05\u0d35\u0d24\u0d30\u0d23\u0d02 \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d41 \u0d35\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d\u0d37\u0d02 ?\r\n",
    "answer": "1784\r\n",
    "status": "2"
  },
  {
    "id": "514",
    "question": "\u0d1a\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d06\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f \u0d12\u0d33\u0d3f\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d38\u0d4d \u0d28\u0d1f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d24\u0d46\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d4d ?\r\n",
    "answer": "\u0d2c\u0d3f.\u0d38\u0d3f. 776\u0d32\u0d4d\u200d\r\n",
    "status": "6"
  },
  {
    "id": "515",
    "question": "\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d4b\u0d38\u0d4d\u200c\u0d15\u200c\u0d23\u0d4d\u200d\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d3f \u0d2e\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d38\u0d30\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d26\u0d48\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d\u0d18\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d02 \u0d0e\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30 ?\r\n",
    "answer": "10\u0d15\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4b\u0d2e\u0d40\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d\r\n",
    "status": "6"
  },
  {
    "id": "516",
    "question": "\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d40\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d33\u0d4d\u200d\u0d1a\u0d47\u0d38\u0d4d \u0d2e\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d38\u0d30\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d26\u0d48\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d\u0d18\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d02 \u0d0e\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30 ?\r\n",
    "answer": "3000 \u0d2e\u0d40\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d\r\n",
    "status": "6"
  },
  {
    "id": "517",
    "question": "\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4b\u0d23\u0d4d\u200d \u0d2e\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d38\u0d30\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d26\u0d42\u0d30\u0d02 \u0d0e\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30 ?\r\n",
    "answer": "42.195 \u0d15\u0d3f.\u0d2e\u0d40.( 26\u0d2e\u0d48\u0d32\u0d4d\u200d385\u0d05\u0d1f\u0d3f)\r\n",
    "status": "6"
  },
  {
    "id": "518",
    "question": "\u0d06\u0d30\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d13\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d2f\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d \u0d12\u0d33\u0d3f\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d38\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4d\u200d \u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4b\u0d23\u0d4d\u200d \u0d2e\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d38\u0d30\u0d02 \u0d28\u0d1f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d24\u0d4d ?\r\n",
    "answer": "\u0d2b\u0d3f\u0d21\u0d3f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d21\u0d38\u0d4d (\u0d17\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d40\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4d \u0d38\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d26\u0d47\u0d36 \u0d35\u0d3e\u0d39\u0d15\u0d28\u0d4d\u200d)\r\n",
    "status": "6"
  },
  {
    "id": "519",
    "question": "\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4b\u0d23\u0d4d\u200d \u0d2f\u0d41\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d27\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4d\u200d \u0d2a\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d46\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24 \u0d30\u0d3e\u0d1c\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d19\u0d33\u0d4d\u200d ?\r\n",
    "answer": "\u0d0f\u0d24\u0d28\u0d4d\u200d\u0d38\u0d4d - \u0d2a\u0d47\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d\u0d37\u0d4d\u0d2f\r\n",
    "status": "6"
  },
  {
    "id": "520",
    "question": "\u0d12\u0d33\u0d3f\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d38\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d0f\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d35\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d26\u0d48\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d\u0d18\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d2e\u0d47\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d2f \u0d05\u0d24\u0d4d\u200c\u0d32\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d38\u0d4d \u0d07\u0d28\u0d02 ?\r\n",
    "answer": "\u0d2a\u0d41\u0d30\u0d41\u0d37\u0d28\u0d4d\u200d\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 50\u0d15\u0d3f.\u0d2e\u0d40\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d \u0d28\u0d1f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d02\r\n",
    "status": "6"
  },
  {
    "id": "521",
    "question": "\u0d12\u0d33\u0d3f\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d38\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d28\u0d1f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d2e\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d38\u0d30\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d46 \u0d35\u0d3f\u0d33\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d2a\u0d47\u0d30\u0d4d ?\r\n",
    "answer": "\u0d31\u0d47\u0d38\u0d4d \u0d35\u0d3e\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3f\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d19\u0d4d\r\n",
    "status": "6"
  },
  {
    "id": "522",
    "question": "\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d33\u0d4d\u200d\u0d1c\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d46 \u0d35\u0d3f\u0d33\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d2e\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4a\u0d30\u0d41 \u0d2a\u0d47\u0d30\u0d4d ?\r\n",
    "answer": "\u0d39\u0d4b\u0d2a\u0d4d \u0d38\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d46\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d4d \u0d06\u0d28\u0d4d\u200d\u0d21\u0d4d \u0d1c\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d4d\r\n",
    "status": "6"
  },
  {
    "id": "523",
    "question": "\u0d2a\u0d4b\u0d33\u0d4d\u200d\u0d35\u0d3e\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4d\u200d \u0d38\u0d46\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d\u0d1c\u0d3f \u0d2c\u0d42\u0d2c\u0d4d\u0d15 (\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d48\u0d28\u0d4d\u200d) \u0d0e\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30 \u0d24\u0d35\u0d23 \u0d32\u0d4b\u0d15\u0d31\u0d46\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d\u0d21\u0d4d \u0d24\u0d3f\u0d30\u0d41\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d4d ?\r\n",
    "answer": "35 \u0d24\u0d35\u0d23\r\n",
    "status": "6"
  },
  {
    "id": "524",
    "question": "\u0d35\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d34\u0d35\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d30\u0d23\u0d15\u0d33\u0d4d\u200d \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d06\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d15\u0d25 \u0d0e\u0d34\u0d41\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d4d ?\r\n",
    "answer": "\u0d2c\u0d3f. \u0d15\u0d32\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2e\r\n",
    "status": "9"
  },
  {
    "id": "525",
    "question": "\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d27\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d06\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d15\u0d25\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d2a\u0d47\u0d30\u0d4d ?\r\n",
    "answer": "\u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d15\u0d25\r\n",
    "status": "9"
  },
  {
    "id": "526",
    "question": "\u0d06\u0d30\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d06\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d15\u0d25\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d \u0d15\u0d34\u0d3f\u0d1e\u0d4d\u0d1e\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d32\u0d02 ?\r\n",
    "answer": "\u0d15\u0d46.\u0d2a\u0d3f.\u0d15\u0d47\u0d36\u0d35\u0d2e\u0d47\u0d28\u0d4b\u0d28\u0d4d\u200d\r\n",
    "status": "9"
  },
  {
    "id": "527",
    "question": "\u0d06\u0d30\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d06\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d15\u0d25\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d \u0d12\u0d30\u0d41 \u0d38\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d\u0d1c\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d13\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d41\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d41\u0d15\u0d33\u0d4d\u200d ?\r\n",
    "answer": "\u0d21\u0d4b.\u0d2a\u0d3f.\u0d15\u0d46.\u0d06\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d\u0d35\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d\r\n",
    "status": "9"
  },
  {
    "id": "528",
    "question": "\u0d24\u0d15\u0d34\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d06\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d15\u0d25\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d2a\u0d47\u0d30\u0d4d ?\r\n",
    "answer": "\u0d13\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d24\u0d40\u0d30\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d19\u0d33\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4d\u200d\r\n",
    "status": "9"
  },
  {
    "id": "529",
    "question": "\u0d38\u0d2e\u0d30\u0d02 \u0d24\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d46 \u0d1c\u0d40\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d02 \u0d06\u0d30\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d06\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d15\u0d25 ?\r\n",
    "answer": "\u0d35\u0d3f. \u0d0e\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d05\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d26\u0d28\u0d4d\u200d\r\n",
    "status": "9"
  },
  {
    "id": "530",
    "question": "\u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d1c\u0d40\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d30\u0d23\u0d15\u0d33\u0d4d\u200d \u0d06\u0d30\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d06\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d15\u0d25\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d ?\r\n",
    "answer": "\u0d2e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d28\u0d3e\u0d2d\u0d28\u0d4d\u200d\r\n",
    "status": "9"
  },
  {
    "id": "531",
    "question": "\u0d2a\u0d3f. \u0d2d\u0d3e\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d30\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d06\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d15\u0d25\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d2a\u0d47\u0d30\u0d4d ?\r\n",
    "answer": "\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d1f\u0d3e\u0d31\u0d41\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d38\u0d02\r\n",
    "status": "9"
  },
  {
    "id": "532",
    "question": "\u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d15\u0d25\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4d\u0d32\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d15\u0d33\u0d4d\u200d \u0d06\u0d30\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d06\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d15\u0d25\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d ?\r\n",
    "answer": "\u0d0e.\u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d09\u0d26\u0d2f\u0d2d\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d41\r\n",
    "status": "9"
  },
  {
    "id": "533",
    "question": "\u0d06\u0d30\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d06\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d15\u0d25\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d46 \u0d1e\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d4d\u200d \u0d15\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d41\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d4b\u0d33\u0d4d\u200d ?\r\n",
    "answer": "\u0d15\u0d46.\u0d0e\u0d02\u0d1c\u0d4b\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d\u0d1c\u0d4d\u0d1c\u0d4d\r\n",
    "status": "9"
  },
  {
    "id": "534",
    "question": "\u0d35\u0d48\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d02\u0d2e\u0d41\u0d39\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d26\u0d4d \u0d2c\u0d37\u0d40\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d06\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d15\u0d25 \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d4d ?\r\n",
    "answer": "\u0d13\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d05\u0d31\u0d15\u0d33\u0d4d\u200d\r\n",
    "status": "9"
  },
  {
    "id": "535",
    "question": "\u0d06\u0d30\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d06\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d15\u0d25\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d \u0d28\u0d28\u0d1e\u0d4d\u0d1e\u0d41 \u0d2a\u0d4b\u0d2f\u0d46\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d1c\u0d4d\u0d35\u0d3e\u0d32 ?\r\n",
    "answer": "\u0d15\u0d46. \u0d2c\u0d3e\u0d32\u0d15\u0d43\u0d37\u0d4d\u0d23\u0d28\u0d4d\u200d\r\n",
    "status": "9"
  },
  {
    "id": "536",
    "question": "\u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d35\u0d34\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d35\u0d4d \u0d06\u0d30\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d06\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d15\u0d25\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d ?\r\n",
    "answer": "\u0d2a\u0d4a\u0d28\u0d4d\u200d\u0d15\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d02\u0d35\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3f\r\n",
    "status": "9"
  },
  {
    "id": "537",
    "question": "\u0d1c\u0d40\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d1b\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d15\u0d33\u0d4d\u200d \u0d06\u0d30\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d06\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d15\u0d25 ?\r\n",
    "answer": "\u0d12. \u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d27\u0d35\u0d28\u0d4d\u200d\r\n",
    "status": "9"
  },
  {
    "id": "538",
    "question": "\u0d0e\u0d38\u0d4d.\u0d15\u0d46\u0d2a\u0d4a\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d1f\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d06\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d15\u0d25\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d2a\u0d47\u0d30\u0d4d ?\r\n",
    "answer": "\u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d35\u0d34\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d32\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d19\u0d33\u0d4d\u200d\r\n",
    "status": "9"
  },
  {
    "id": "539",
    "question": "\u0d0e\u0d38\u0d4d \u0d17\u0d41\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d28\u0d4d\u200d\u0d28\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d30\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d06\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d15\u0d25 \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d4d ?\r\n",
    "answer": "\u0d2e\u0d28\u0d38\u0d3e\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d2e\u0d3f\r\n",
    "status": "9"
  },
  {
    "id": "540",
    "question": "\u0d0e\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d4d \u0d06\u0d30\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d06\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d15\u0d25\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d ?\r\n",
    "answer": "\u0d15\u0d47\u0d36\u0d35\u0d26\u0d47\u0d35\u0d4d\r\n",
    "status": "9"
  },
  {
    "id": "541",
    "question": "\u0d06\u0d30\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d06\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d15\u0d25\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d \u0d12\u0d30\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d13\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d41\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d41\u0d15\u0d33\u0d4d\u200d ?\r\n",
    "answer": "\u0d08\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d30\u0d35\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d\r\n",
    "status": "9"
  },
  {
    "id": "542",
    "question": "\u0d0e\u0d02.\u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d35\u0d40\u0d30\u0d47\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d15\u0d41\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d06\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d15\u0d25\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d2a\u0d47\u0d30\u0d4d ?\r\n",
    "answer": "\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d1e\u0d4d\u0d1e\u0d41 \u0d28\u0d4b\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d41\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d4b\u0d33\u0d4d\u200d\r\n",
    "status": "9"
  },
  {
    "id": "543",
    "question": "\u0d2f\u0d41.\u0d0e\u0d16\u0d3e\u0d26\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d06\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d15\u0d25\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d2a\u0d47\u0d30\u0d4d ?\r\n",
    "answer": "\u0d15\u0d33\u0d3f\u0d2e\u0d41\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d02\r\n",
    "status": "9"
  },
  {
    "id": "544",
    "question": "\u0d2e\u0d32\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d33\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d32\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d37\u0d23\u0d2e\u0d4a\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24 \u0d06\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f \u0d06\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d15\u0d25 ?\r\n",
    "answer": "\u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d28\u0d3e\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d15\u0d1f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d32\u0d4d\u200d(1911)\r\n",
    "status": "9"
  },
  {
    "id": "545",
    "question": "\u0d06\u0d30\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d06\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d15\u0d25\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d28\u0d3e\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d15\u0d1f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d32\u0d4d\u200d ?\r\n",
    "answer": "\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d35\u0d26\u0d47\u0d36\u0d3e\u0d2d\u0d3f\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d3f\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d2e\u0d15\u0d43\u0d37\u0d4d\u0d23 \u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d33\u0d4d\u0d33\r\n",
    "status": "9"
  },
  {
    "id": "546",
    "question": "\u0d06\u0d30\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d06\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d15\u0d25\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d \u0d06\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d15\u0d25\u0d2f\u0d4d\u200c\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4a\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d2e\u0d41\u0d16\u0d02 ?\r\n",
    "answer": "\u0d32\u0d33\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d02\u0d2c\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d05\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d\u0d1c\u0d4d\u0d1c\u0d28\u0d02\r\n",
    "status": "9"
  },
  {
    "id": "547",
    "question": "\u0d1e\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d4d\u200d \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d2a\u0d47\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4d\u200d \u0d06\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d15\u0d25\u0d15\u0d33\u0d4d\u200d \u0d0e\u0d34\u0d41\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d35\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d \u0d06\u0d30\u0d4a\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d46 ?\r\n",
    "answer": "\u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u200d.\u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u200d\u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d33\u0d4d\u0d33, \u0d38\u0d3f.\u0d35\u0d3f \u0d15\u0d41\u0d1e\u0d4d\u0d1e\u0d3f\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d2e\u0d28\u0d4d\u200d\r\n",
    "status": "9"
  },
  {
    "id": "548",
    "question": "\u0d06\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d15\u0d25 \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d2a\u0d47\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4d\u200d \u0d06\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d15\u0d25\u0d15\u0d33\u0d4d\u200d \u0d0e\u0d34\u0d41\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d35\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d \u0d06\u0d30\u0d4a\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d46 ?\r\n",
    "answer": "\u0d15\u0d46.\u0d0e\u0d02\u0d2a\u0d23\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d, \u0d07.\u0d0e\u0d02.\u0d0e\u0d38\u0d4d, \u0d05\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d3e\u0d1a\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d3f\r\n",
    "status": "9"
  },
  {
    "id": "549",
    "question": "\u0d1c\u0d40\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d30\u0d23\u0d15\u0d33\u0d4d\u200d \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d2a\u0d47\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4d\u200d \u0d06\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d15\u0d25\u0d15\u0d33\u0d4d\u200d \u0d0e\u0d34\u0d41\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d35\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d \u0d06\u0d30\u0d4a\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d46 ?\r\n",
    "answer": "\u0d07.\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d43\u0d37\u0d4d\u0d23\u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d33\u0d4d\u0d33, \u0d15\u0d46.\u0d38\u0d3f \u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d2e\u0d28\u0d4d\u200d\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d33\r\n",
    "status": "9"
  },
  {
    "id": "550",
    "question": "\u0d1c\u0d4b\u0d38\u0d2b\u0d4d \u0d2e\u0d41\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d36\u0d4d\u0d36\u0d47\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d06\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d15\u0d25\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d2a\u0d47\u0d30\u0d4d ?\r\n",
    "answer": "\u0d15\u0d4a\u0d34\u0d3f\u0d1e\u0d4d\u0d1e \u0d07\u0d32\u0d15\u0d33\u0d4d\u200d\r\n",
    "status": "9"
  },
  {
    "id": "551",
    "question": "\u0d15\u0d41\u0d1e\u0d4d\u0d1e\u0d41\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d23\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d06\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d15\u0d25 ?\r\n",
    "answer": "\u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d42\u0d1f\u0d46\r\n",
    "status": "9"
  },
  {
    "id": "552",
    "question": "\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d30\u0d23\u0d3e\u0d2e\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d21\u0d32\u0d02 \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d2a\u0d47\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4d\u200d \u0d06\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d15\u0d25 \u0d0e\u0d34\u0d41\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d4d ?\r\n",
    "answer": "\u0d38\u0d3e\u0d39\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f \u0d2a\u0d1e\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d28\u0d4d\u200d\r\n",
    "status": "9"
  },
  {
    "id": "553",
    "question": "\u0d15\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d15\u0d3e\u0d32\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d3e\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d15\u0d33\u0d4d\u200d, \u0d28\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d15\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d15\u0d2f\u0d46 \u0d24\u0d47\u0d1f\u0d3f \u0d07\u0d35 \u0d06\u0d30\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d06\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d15\u0d25\u0d15\u0d33\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d ?\r\n",
    "answer": "\u0d2a\u0d3f.\u0d15\u0d41\u0d1e\u0d4d\u0d1e\u0d3f\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d2e\u0d28\u0d4d\u200d \u0d28\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d\r\n",
    "status": "9"
  },
  {
    "id": "554",
    "question": "\u0d28\u0d3f\u0d34\u0d32\u0d41\u0d31\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d19\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d35\u0d34\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d7e \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d2e\u0d32\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d33 \u0d28\u0d4b\u0d35\u0d32\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d30\u0d1a\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d35\u0d4d ?\r\n",
    "answer": "\u0d2a\u0d3f. \u0d35\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d38\u0d32\r\n",
    "status": "9"
  },
  {
    "id": "555",
    "question": "\u0d2a\u0d3f. \u0d35\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d38\u0d32\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4d \u0d15\u0d47\u0d30\u0d33 \u0d38\u0d3e\u0d39\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f \u0d05\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d26\u0d2e\u0d3f \u0d05\u0d35\u0d3e\u0d7c\u0d21\u0d4d \u0d28\u0d47\u0d1f\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4a\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24 \u0d15\u0d43\u0d24\u0d3f ?\r\n",
    "answer": "\u0d28\u0d3f\u0d34\u0d32\u0d41\u0d31\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d19\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d35\u0d34\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d7e(1975)\r\n",
    "status": "9"
  },
  {
    "id": "556",
    "question": "\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d37\u0d4d\u0d23\u0d41 \u0d28\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d23\u0d7b \u0d28\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d42\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d27\u0d3e\u0d28 \u0d15\u0d43\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d7e ?\r\n",
    "answer": "\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d35\u0d3e\u0d24\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d46\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d41\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d4a\u0d30\u0d41 \u0d17\u0d40\u0d24\u0d02, \u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d23\u0d2f\u0d17\u0d40\u0d24\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d19\u0d7e, \u0d07\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d2f\u0d46\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d35\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d02, \u0d2e\u0d41\u0d16\u0d2e\u0d46\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d1f\u0d46, \u0d05\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d7c\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d47\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4a\u0d30\u0d41 \u0d2f",
    "status": "9"
  },
  {
    "id": "557",
    "question": "\u0d15\u0d47\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d30 \u0d38\u0d3e\u0d39\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f \u0d05\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d26\u0d2e\u0d3f \u0d05\u0d35\u0d3e\u0d7c\u0d21\u0d4d \u0d28\u0d47\u0d1f\u0d3f\u0d2f \u0d06\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f \u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d35\u0d30\u0d23 \u0d17\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d02 ?\r\n",
    "answer": "\u0d39\u0d48\u0d2e\u0d35\u0d24 \u0d2d\u0d42\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d7d (2010\u0d7d)\r\n",
    "status": "9"
  },
  {
    "id": "558",
    "question": "\u0d39\u0d48\u0d2e\u0d35\u0d24 \u0d2d\u0d42\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d7d - \u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d30\u0d1a\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d35\u0d4d ?\r\n",
    "answer": "\u0d0e\u0d02.\u0d2a\u0d3f \u0d35\u0d40\u0d30\u0d47\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d15\u0d41\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d7c\r\n",
    "status": "9"
  },
  {
    "id": "559",
    "question": "\u0d15\u0d47\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d30 \u0d38\u0d3e\u0d39\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f \u0d05\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d26\u0d2e\u0d3f \u0d05\u0d35\u0d3e\u0d7c\u0d21\u0d4d \u0d24\u0d41\u0d15 \u0d0e\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30 ?\r\n",
    "answer": "\u0d12\u0d30\u0d41 \u0d32\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d37\u0d02 \u0d30\u0d42\u0d2a\r\n",
    "status": "9"
  },
  {
    "id": "560",
    "question": "\u0d06\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d1c\u0d40\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d02 \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d2e\u0d32\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d33 \u0d28\u0d4b\u0d35\u0d32\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d30\u0d1a\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d35\u0d4d \u0d06\u0d30\u0d4d ?\r\n",
    "answer": "\u0d2c\u0d46\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d2e\u0d3f\u0d7b\r\n",
    "status": "9"
  },
  {
    "id": "561",
    "question": "\u0d2c\u0d46\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d2e\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d2f\u0d25\u0d3e\u0d7c\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d25 \u0d28\u0d3e\u0d2e\u0d02 ?\r\n",
    "answer": "\u0d2c\u0d46\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d3f \u0d21\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d47\u0d7d\r\n",
    "status": "9"
  },
  {
    "id": "562",
    "question": "\u0d2c\u0d46\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d2e\u0d3f\u0d7b \u0d15\u0d47\u0d30\u0d33 \u0d38\u0d3e\u0d39\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f \u0d05\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d26\u0d2e\u0d3f \u0d2a\u0d41\u0d30\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d02 \u0d28\u0d47\u0d1f\u0d3f\u0d2f \u0d35\u0d7c\u0d37\u0d02 ?\r\n",
    "answer": "2009 (\u0d06\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d1c\u0d40\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d02)\r\n",
    "status": "9"
  },
  {
    "id": "563",
    "question": "\u0d06\u0d35\u0d47 \u0d2e\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d2f \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d1a\u0d46\u0d31\u0d41\u0d15\u0d25\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d30\u0d1a\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d35\u0d4d ?\r\n",
    "answer": "\u0d15\u0d46.\u0d06\u0d7c \u0d2e\u0d40\u0d30(2009\u0d7d \u0d15\u0d47\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d30 \u0d38\u0d3e\u0d39\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f \u0d05\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d26\u0d2e\u0d3f \u0d05\u0d35\u0d3e\u0d7c\u0d21\u0d4d)\r\n",
    "status": "9"
  },
  {
    "id": "564",
    "question": "\u0d12\u0d30\u0d41 \u0d1a\u0d4a\u0d35\u0d4d\u0d35\u0d3e\u0d26\u0d3f\u0d35\u0d38\u0d02 \u0d0e\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30 \u0d2e\u0d23\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d42\u0d7c \u0d2e\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d3f\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d4d ?\r\n",
    "answer": "24 \u0d2e\u0d23\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d42\u0d7c 40 \u0d2e\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d3f\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d\r\n",
    "status": "1"
  },
  {
    "id": "565",
    "question": "\u0d1a\u0d4a\u0d35\u0d4d\u0d35\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d05\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d30\u0d40\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d37\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d7d \u0d0f\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d35\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d15\u0d42\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d24\u0d32\u0d41\u0d33\u0d4d\u0d33 \u0d35\u0d3e\u0d24\u0d15\u0d02 ?\r\n",
    "answer": "\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d7c\u0d2c\u0d7a \u0d21\u0d48 \u0d13\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d38\u0d48\u0d21\u0d4d\r\n",
    "status": "1"
  },
  {
    "id": "566",
    "question": "\u0d1a\u0d4a\u0d35\u0d4d\u0d35\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d35\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d38\u0d02 \u0d0e\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30 ?\r\n",
    "answer": "6779km\r\n",
    "status": "1"
  },
  {
    "id": "567",
    "question": "\u0d1a\u0d4a\u0d35\u0d4d\u0d35\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d17\u0d41\u0d30\u0d41\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d35\u0d3e\u0d15\u0d7c\u0d37\u0d23\u0d2c\u0d32\u0d02 \u0d2d\u0d42\u0d2e\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d47\u0d24\u0d41\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d3f \u0d24\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d24\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d02 \u0d1a\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d4b\u0d7e .....?\r\n",
    "answer": "\u0d2d\u0d42\u0d17\u0d41\u0d30\u0d41\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d35\u0d3e\u0d15\u0d7c\u0d37\u0d23\u0d2c\u0d32\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d46 38% \u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d02\r\n",
    "status": "1"
  },
  {
    "id": "568",
    "question": "\u0d1a\u0d4a\u0d35\u0d4d\u0d35\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d05\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d30\u0d40\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d37\u0d2e\u0d7c\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d26\u0d02 \u0d2d\u0d42\u0d2e\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d47\u0d24\u0d41\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d3f \u0d24\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d24\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d02 \u0d1a\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d4b\u0d7e .....?\r\n",
    "answer": "\u0d2d\u0d57\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d30\u0d40\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d37 \u0d2e\u0d7c\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d26\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d46 0.7% \u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d02\r\n",
    "status": "1"
  },
  {
    "id": "569",
    "question": "\u0d1a\u0d4a\u0d35\u0d4d\u0d35\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d36\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d36\u0d30\u0d3f \u0d24\u0d3e\u0d2a\u0d28\u0d3f\u0d32 ?\r\n",
    "answer": "-60\u00b0C\r\n",
    "status": "1"
  },
  {
    "id": "570",
    "question": "\u0d38\u0d57\u0d30\u0d2f\u0d42\u0d25\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d17\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d39\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d19\u0d33\u0d3f\u0d7d \u0d35\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d47\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d35\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d15\u0d42\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d24\u0d7d \u0d2a\u0d4a\u0d1f\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d \u0d35\u0d40\u0d36\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d24\u0d46\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d1f\u0d46 ?\r\n",
    "answer": "\u0d1a\u0d4a\u0d35\u0d4d\u0d35\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d7d\r\n",
    "status": "1"
  },
  {
    "id": "571",
    "question": "\u0d1a\u0d4a\u0d35\u0d4d\u0d35\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d0f\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d35\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d09\u0d2f\u0d30\u0d02 \u0d15\u0d42\u0d1f\u0d3f\u0d2f \u0d2a\u0d7c\u0d35\u0d4d\u0d35\u0d24\u0d02 ?\r\n",
    "answer": "\u0d12\u0d33\u0d3f\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d \u0d2e\u0d4b\u0d7a\u0d38\u0d4d\r\n",
    "status": "1"
  },
  {
    "id": "572",
    "question": "\u0d1a\u0d4a\u0d35\u0d4d\u0d35\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d09\u0d2a\u0d17\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d39\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d19\u0d7e \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d4a\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d46 ?\r\n",
    "answer": "\u0d2b\u0d4b\u0d2c\u0d4b\u0d38\u0d4d, \u0d21\u0d40\u0d2e\u0d4b\u0d38\u0d4d\r\n",
    "status": "1"
  },
  {
    "id": "573",
    "question": "\u0d2d\u0d42\u0d2e\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d7d \u0d28\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d1a\u0d4a\u0d35\u0d4d\u0d35\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d47\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d41\u0d33\u0d4d\u0d33 \u0d36\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d36\u0d30\u0d3f \u0d26\u0d42\u0d30\u0d02 \u0d0e\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30 ?\r\n",
    "answer": "22\u0d15\u0d4b\u0d1f\u0d3f 50 \u0d32\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d37\u0d02 \u0d15\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4b\u0d2e\u0d40\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d7c\r\n",
    "status": "1"
  },
  {
    "id": "574",
    "question": "\u0d2e\u0d32\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d33 \u0d15\u0d35\u0d3f \u0d0e \u0d05\u0d2f\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d27\u0d3e\u0d28 \u0d15\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d3e \u0d38\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d39\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d19\u0d7e ?\r\n",
    "answer": "\u0d2f\u0d1c\u0d4d\u0d1e\u0d02, \u0d35\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d7d \u0d24\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d2a\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d37\u0d3f, \u0d2c\u0d41\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d27\u0d28\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d06\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d3f\u0d7b\u0d15\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d02, \u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d33\u0d2e\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4d\u0d32\u0d3e\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24 \u0d2a\u0d3e\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d4d, \u0d17\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d40\u0d37\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d35\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d15\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d23\u0d40\u0d30\u0d41\u0d02 ",
    "status": "9"
  },
  {
    "id": "575",
    "question": "\u0d15\u0d35\u0d3f \u0d0e \u0d05\u0d2f\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d28\u0d4d \u0d15\u0d47\u0d30\u0d33 \u0d38\u0d3e\u0d39\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f \u0d05\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d26\u0d2e\u0d3f \u0d05\u0d35\u0d3e\u0d7c\u0d21\u0d4d \u0d32\u0d2d\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d24\u0d46\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d4d?\r\n",
    "answer": "1999\r\n",
    "status": "9"
  },
  {
    "id": "576",
    "question": "\u0d21\u0d4b. \u0d0e\u0d02 \u0d32\u0d40\u0d32\u0d3e\u0d35\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d27\u0d3e\u0d28 \u0d15\u0d43\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d7e ?\r\n",
    "answer": "\u0d15\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d23\u0d40\u0d30\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d2e\u0d34\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4d\u0d32\u0d41\u0d02, \u0d1c\u0d40\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d15\u0d3e\u0d35\u0d4d\u0d2f \u0d1c\u0d40\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d02, \u0d05\u0d2e\u0d43\u0d24\u0d2e\u0d36\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d41\u0d24\u0d47, \u0d15\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d27\u0d4d\u0d35\u0d28\u0d3f, \u0d06\u0d26\u0d3f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d30\u0d42\u0d2a\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d19\u0d7e \u0d38\u0d3e\u0d39\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d7d, \u0d38\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d02 ",
    "status": "9"
  },
  {
    "id": "577",
    "question": "\u0d21\u0d4b. \u0d0e\u0d02 \u0d32\u0d40\u0d32\u0d3e\u0d35\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4d \u0d32\u0d2d\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d33\u0d4d\u0d33 \u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d27\u0d3e\u0d28 \u0d2a\u0d41\u0d30\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d19\u0d7e ?\r\n",
    "answer": "*\u0d13\u0d1f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d41\u0d34\u0d7d \u0d05\u0d35\u0d3e\u0d7c\u0d21\u0d4d (1978), *\u0d15\u0d47\u0d30\u0d33 \u0d38\u0d3e\u0d39\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f \u0d05\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d26\u0d2e\u0d3f \u0d05\u0d35\u0d3e\u0d7c\u0d21\u0d4d (1980), *\u0d15\u0d47\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d30 \u0d38\u0d3e\u0d39\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f \u0d05\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d26\u0d2e\u0d3f \u0d05\u0d35\u0d3e\u0d7c\u0d21\u0d4d(1986",
    "status": "9"
  },
  {
    "id": "578",
    "question": "\u0d39\u0d43\u0d26\u0d2f\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d17\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d19\u0d33\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d15\u0d35\u0d3f \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d46\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d15\u0d35\u0d3f ?\r\n",
    "answer": "\u0d36\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d40\u0d15\u0d41\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d7b \u0d24\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d3f\r\n",
    "status": "9"
  },
  {
    "id": "579",
    "question": "\u0d36\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d40\u0d15\u0d41\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d7b \u0d24\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4d \u0d13\u0d1f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d41\u0d34\u0d7d \u0d05\u0d35\u0d3e\u0d7c\u0d21\u0d4d \u0d32\u0d2d\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d24\u0d46\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d4d?\r\n",
    "answer": "2010\u0d7d, \u0d05\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d2f\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4d \u0d12\u0d30\u0d41 \u0d24\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d4d \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d15\u0d3e\u0d35\u0d4d\u0d2f \u0d38\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d39\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d \u0d32\u0d2d\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d41\r\n",
    "status": "9"
  },
  {
    "id": "580",
    "question": "\u0d2f\u0d41 \u0d15\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d7d \u0d0e\u0d34\u0d41\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d41\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d33\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d15\u0d43\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d7e\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d41 \u0d28\u0d7d\u0d15\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d09\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d24\u0d2a\u0d41\u0d30\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d02 ?\r\n",
    "answer": "\u0d13\u0d31\u0d1e\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d4d \u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d48\u0d38\u0d4d \u0d2b\u0d4b\u0d7c \u0d2b\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d37\u0d7b\r\n",
    "status": "9"
  },
  {
    "id": "581",
    "question": "\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d25\u0d2e \u0d1f\u0d3e\u0d17\u0d4b\u0d7c \u0d38\u0d3e\u0d39\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f \u0d2a\u0d41\u0d30\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d02 \u0d28\u0d7d\u0d15\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d24\u0d46\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d4d?\r\n",
    "answer": "2010\u0d7d\r\n",
    "status": "9"
  },
  {
    "id": "582",
    "question": "2010\u0d7d , \u0d06\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f '\u0d39\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d26\u0d41 \u0d2c\u0d46\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d \u0d2b\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d37\u0d7b \u0d2a\u0d41\u0d30\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d02 ' \u0d32\u0d2d\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a '\u0d38\u0d40\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d38\u0d4d \u0d2e\u0d46\u0d7b' \u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d30\u0d1a\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d35\u0d4d ?\r\n",
    "answer": "\u0d2e\u0d28\u0d41 \u0d1c\u0d4b\u0d38\u0d2b\u0d4d\r\n",
    "status": "9"
  },
  {
    "id": "583",
    "question": "\u0d07\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d7b \u0d2d\u0d3e\u0d37\u0d15\u0d33\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d38\u0d3e\u0d39\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f \u0d15\u0d43\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d7e\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4d \u0d28\u0d7d\u0d15\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d09\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d24 \u0d2a\u0d41\u0d30\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d02 ?\r\n",
    "answer": "\u0d38\u0d30\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d35\u0d24\u0d3f \u0d38\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d7b\r\n",
    "status": "9"
  },
  {
    "id": "584",
    "question": "\u0d32\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d4a \u0d1f\u0d4b\u0d7e\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4b\u0d2f\u0d3f \u0d1c\u0d28\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d4d ?\r\n",
    "answer": "1828 \u0d06\u0d17\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d 28(\u0d38\u0d46\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d02\u0d2c\u0d7c 9- \u0d2a\u0d41\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d2f \u0d15\u0d32\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d7c \u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d02)\r\n",
    "status": "9"
  },
  {
    "id": "585",
    "question": "\u0d32\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d4a \u0d1f\u0d4b\u0d7e\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4b\u0d2f\u0d3f \u0d1c\u0d28\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d0e\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d1f\u0d46?\r\n",
    "answer": "\u0d31\u0d37\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d2a\u0d4b\u0d32\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d7d\r\n",
    "status": "9"
  },
  {
    "id": "586",
    "question": "\u0d32\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d4a \u0d1f\u0d4b\u0d7e\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4b\u0d2f\u0d3f \u0d2e\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d24\u0d46\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d4d ?\r\n",
    "answer": "1910 \u0d28\u0d35\u0d02\u0d2c\u0d7c 7\u0d28\u0d4d\r\n",
    "status": "9"
  },
  {
    "id": "587",
    "question": "\u0d32\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d4a \u0d1f\u0d4b\u0d7e\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4b\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d27\u0d3e\u0d28 \u0d15\u0d43\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d7e ?\r\n",
    "answer": "\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d27\u0d35\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d38\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d27\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d35\u0d41\u0d02(1869), \u0d05\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d3e\u0d15\u0d30\u0d47\u0d28\u0d3f\u0d28, \u0d07\u0d35\u0d3e\u0d7b \u0d07\u0d32\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d2e\u0d30\u0d23\u0d02, \u0d2e\u0d28\u0d41\u0d37\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d28\u0d4d \u0d0e\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30 \u0d2d\u0d42\u0d2e\u0d3f \u0d35\u0d47\u0d23\u0d02, \u0d05\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d4b\u0d7e \u0d28\u0d3e\u0d02 ",
    "status": "9"
  },
  {
    "id": "588",
    "question": "\u0d32\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d4a \u0d1f\u0d4b\u0d7e\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4b\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d06\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d15\u0d25\u0d3e \u0d28\u0d4b\u0d35\u0d7d \u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d2f\u0d02?\r\n",
    "answer": "\u0d36\u0d48\u0d36\u0d35\u0d02(1852), \u0d15\u0d57\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d02(1854), \u0d2f\u0d57\u0d35\u0d4d\u0d35\u0d28\u0d02(1857)\r\n",
    "status": "9"
  },
  {
    "id": "589",
    "question": "\u0d06\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d7b \u0d2a\u0d3e\u0d35\u0d4d\u0d32\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d4d \u0d1a\u0d46\u0d16\u0d4b\u0d2b\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d46 (\u0d31\u0d37\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d7b \u0d38\u0d3e\u0d39\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d7b) \u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d36\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d24 \u0d30\u0d1a\u0d28\u0d15\u0d7e?\r\n",
    "answer": "\u0d26\u0d4d \u0d1a\u0d46\u0d31\u0d3f \u0d13\u0d7c\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d21\u0d4d, \u0d26\u0d4d \u0d38\u0d40\u0d17\u0d7e, \u0d05\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3f\u0d7e \u0d35\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d2f, \u0d26\u0d4d \u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d40 \u0d38\u0d3f\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d47\u0d34\u0d4d\u0d38\u0d4d.\r\n",
    "status": "9"
  },
  {
    "id": "590",
    "question": "\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d7c\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4d \u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d35\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d7b \u0d1c\u0d28\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d4d ?\r\n",
    "answer": "1835 \u0d28\u0d35\u0d02\u0d2c\u0d7c 30\u0d28\u0d4d(\u0d2f\u0d41 \u0d0e\u0d38\u0d4d \u0d0e\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d2b\u0d4d\u0d32\u0d4b\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d21\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d7d)\r\n",
    "status": "9"
  },
  {
    "id": "591",
    "question": "\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d7c\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4d \u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d35\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d2f\u0d25\u0d3e\u0d7c\u0d25 \u0d28\u0d3e\u0d2e\u0d02?\r\n",
    "answer": "\u0d38\u0d3e\u0d2e\u0d41\u0d35\u0d47\u0d7d \u0d32\u0d3e\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d39\u0d4b\u0d7a \u0d15\u0d4d\u0d32\u0d2e\u0d7b\u0d38\u0d4d\r\n",
    "status": "9"
  },
  {
    "id": "592",
    "question": "\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d7c\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4d \u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d35\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d7b \u0d2e\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d24\u0d46\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d4d ?\r\n",
    "answer": "1910 \u0d0f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d7d 21\u0d28\u0d4d\r\n",
    "status": "9"
  },
  {
    "id": "593",
    "question": "\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d7c\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4d \u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d35\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d27\u0d3e\u0d28 \u0d15\u0d43\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d7e ?\r\n",
    "answer": "\u0d26\u0d3f \u0d05\u0d21\u0d4d\u0d35\u0d1e\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d47\u0d34\u0d4d\u0d38\u0d4d \u0d13\u0d2b\u0d4d \u0d39\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3f\u0d7e\u0d2c\u0d31\u0d3f \u0d2b\u0d3f\u0d7b,\u0d26\u0d3f \u0d05\u0d21\u0d4d\u0d35\u0d1e\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d47\u0d34\u0d4d\u0d38\u0d4d \u0d13\u0d2b\u0d4d \u0d1f\u0d4b\u0d02 \u0d38\u0d4b\u0d2f\u0d7c, \u0d32\u0d48\u0d2b\u0d4d \u0d13\u0d7a \u0d2e\u0d3f\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d38\u0d3f\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d38\u0d3f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d3f.\r\n",
    "status": "9"
  },
  {
    "id": "594",
    "question": "\u0d32\u0d4b\u0d15\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d06\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d3f \u0d12\u0d30\u0d41 \u0d38\u0d48\u0d2c\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d \u0d38\u0d48\u0d28\u0d3f\u0d15 \u0d35\u0d3f\u0d2d\u0d3e\u0d17\u0d02 \u0d30\u0d42\u0d2a\u0d40\u0d15\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a \u0d30\u0d3e\u0d1c\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d02?\r\n",
    "answer": "\u0d2f\u0d41.\u0d0e\u0d38\u0d4d.\u0d0e (2010\u0d32\u0d4d\u200d)\r\n",
    "status": "8"
  },
  {
    "id": "595",
    "question": "\u0d2f\u0d41.\u0d0e\u0d38\u0d4d.\u0d0e \u0d2f\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d38\u0d48\u0d2c\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d \u0d38\u0d48\u0d28\u0d3f\u0d15 \u0d35\u0d3f\u0d2d\u0d3e\u0d17\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d2a\u0d47\u0d30\u0d4d ?\r\n",
    "answer": "\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d23\u0d48\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d21\u0d4d \u0d38\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d47\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d38\u0d4d \u0d38\u0d48\u0d2c\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d \u0d15\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d4d\u200d\u0d21\u0d4d\r\n",
    "status": "8"
  },
  {
    "id": "596",
    "question": "\u0d1a\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d06\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d46 \u0d38\u0d48\u0d2c\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d \u0d2f\u0d41\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d27\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d3f \u0d05\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d46\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d24\u0d4d ?\r\n",
    "answer": "2007\u0d32\u0d4d\u200d \u0d31\u0d37\u0d4d\u0d2f \u0d0e\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4b\u0d23\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d46\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d30\u0d46 \u0d28\u0d1f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d24\u0d4d\r\n",
    "status": "8"
  },
  {
    "id": "597",
    "question": "\u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d \u0d1f\u0d48\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d4d\u200d \u0d31\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d4d\u200d(Titan Rain)?\r\n",
    "answer": "\u0d1a\u0d48\u0d28\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4d\u200d \u0d28\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d4d \u0d05\u0d2e\u0d47\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d2e\u0d47\u0d32\u0d4d\u200d \u0d28\u0d1f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d38\u0d48\u0d2c\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d \u0d06\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d2e\u0d23\u0d02\r\n",
    "status": "8"
  },
  {
    "id": "598",
    "question": "\u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d \u0d2e\u0d42\u0d7a\u0d32\u0d48\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d \u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d38\u0d46(Moon light Maze)?\r\n",
    "answer": "\u0d31\u0d37\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4d\u200d \u0d28\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d4d \u0d05\u0d2e\u0d47\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d2e\u0d47\u0d32\u0d4d\u200d \u0d28\u0d1f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d38\u0d48\u0d2c\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d \u0d06\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d2e\u0d23\u0d02\r\n",
    "status": "8"
  },
  {
    "id": "599",
    "question": "\u0d2c\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d4d\u0d26\u0d41 \u0d38\u0d46\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d4d \u0d0e\u0d1e\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u200d \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d41 \u0d30\u0d3e\u0d1c\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d47\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d ?\r\n",
    "answer": "\u0d1a\u0d48\u0d28\r\n",
    "status": "8"
  },
  {
    "id": "600",
    "question": "\u0d32\u0d4b\u0d15\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d06\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d46 \u0d38\u0d48\u0d2c\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d \u0d38\u0d42\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d\u0d35\u0d46\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d7a \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d4d \u0d35\u0d3f\u0d36\u0d47\u0d37\u0d3f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d46\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d33\u0d4d\u0d33 \u0d15\u0d02\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d42\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d \u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d4b\u0d17\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d02 ?\r\n",
    "answer": "\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d38\u0d4d \u0d28\u0d46\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d\r\n",
    "status": "8"
  },
  {
    "id": "601",
    "question": "\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d38\u0d4d \u0d28\u0d46\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d \u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d27\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d06\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d46\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d30\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d \u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d35\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d24\u0d4d ?\r\n",
    "answer": "\u0d07\u0d31\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d28\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d42\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d32\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d \u0d2a\u0d35\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d \u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d32\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d46\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d30\u0d46\r\n",
    "status": "8"
  },
  {
    "id": "602",
    "question": "\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d35\u0d24\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30 \u0d38\u0d4b\u0d2b\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d \u0d35\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d \u0d2b\u0d4c\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d47\u0d37\u0d28\u0d4d\u200d \u0d06\u0d30\u0d02\u0d2d\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d24\u0d46\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d4d ?\r\n",
    "answer": "1985 \u0d12\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d4b\u0d2c\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d\r\n",
    "status": "8"
  },
  {
    "id": "603",
    "question": "\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d35\u0d24\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30 \u0d38\u0d4b\u0d2b\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d35\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d \u0d2b\u0d4c\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d47\u0d37\u0d28\u0d4d\u200d \u0d06\u0d30\u0d02\u0d2d\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d06\u0d30\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d28\u0d47\u0d24\u0d43\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d35\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4d\u200d ?\r\n",
    "answer": "\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d\u0d21\u0d4d \u0d38\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d3e\u0d33\u0d4d\u200d\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d4d\u200d\r\n",
    "status": "8"
  },
  {
    "id": "604",
    "question": "\u0d17\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d41 \u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d4b\u0d1c\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d4d \u0d06\u0d30\u0d02\u0d2d\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d24\u0d46\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d4d ?\r\n",
    "answer": "1983 \u0d38\u0d46\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d02\u0d2c\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4d\u200d\r\n",
    "status": "8"
  },
  {
    "id": "605",
    "question": "\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d35\u0d24\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30 \u0d38\u0d4b\u0d2b\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d \u0d35\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d \u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d07\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d06\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d02 ?\r\n",
    "answer": "\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d30\u0d41\u0d35\u0d28\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d2a\u0d41\u0d30\u0d02\r\n",
    "status": "8"
  },
  {
    "id": "606",
    "question": "\u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d \u0d1a\u0d3e\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2a ()?\r\n",
    "answer": "\u0d2a\u0d15\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d35\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d36 \u0d28\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d23\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d19\u0d33\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4d\u0d32\u0d3e\u0d24\u0d46 \u0d38\u0d4d\u0d35\u0d24\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d3f \u0d2a\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3f\u0d1f\u0d3e\u0d35\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d38\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d3f\u0d2e \u0d15\u0d42\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d3f \u0d28\u0d3f\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d41\u0d33\u0d4d\u0d33 \u0d38\u0d02\u0d30\u0d02\u0d2d\u0d02",
    "status": "8"
  },
  {
    "id": "607",
    "question": "\u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d \u0d2f\u0d41\u0d07\u0d0e\u0d2b\u0d4d\u0d10 ()?\r\n",
    "answer": "\u0d15\u0d02\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d42\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d \u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d35\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d41 \u0d24\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d19\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d4d\u200d \u0d38\u0d39\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d2c\u0d2f\u0d4b\u0d38\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d41 \u0d2a\u0d15\u0d30\u0d2e\u0d41\u0d33\u0d4d\u0d33 \u0d38\u0d02\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d27\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d02\r\n",
    "status": "8"
  },
  {
    "id": "608",
    "question": "\u0d2b\u0d3f\u0d2b(FIFA)\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d06\u0d15\u0d46 \u0d05\u0d02\u0d17\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d19\u0d33\u0d4d\u200d ?\r\n",
    "answer": "202\r\n",
    "status": "6"
  },
  {
    "id": "609",
    "question": "\u0d2b\u0d3f\u0d2b \u0d32\u0d4b\u0d15\u0d15\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d4d \u0d2b\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d2c\u0d4b\u0d33\u0d4d\u200d \u0d06\u0d30\u0d02\u0d2d\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d24\u0d46\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d4d ?\r\n",
    "answer": "1930 \u0d2f\u0d41\u0d31\u0d42\u0d17\u0d4d\u0d35\u0d47\r\n",
    "status": "6"
  },
  {
    "id": "610",
    "question": "\u0d0f\u0d37\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d21\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d28\u0d1f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d \u0d2e\u0d47\u0d32\u0d4d\u200d \u0d28\u0d4b\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d02 \u0d35\u0d39\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d38\u0d02\u0d18\u0d1f\u0d28 ?\r\n",
    "answer": "\u0d12\u0d33\u0d3f\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d \u0d15\u0d57\u0d23\u0d4d\u200d\u0d38\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4d\u200d \u0d13\u0d2b\u0d4d \u0d0f\u0d37\u0d4d\u0d2f\r\n",
    "status": "6"
  },
  {
    "id": "611",
    "question": "1982 \u0d21\u0d32\u0d4d\u200d\u0d39\u0d3f \u0d0f\u0d37\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d21\u0d4d \u0d35\u0d30\u0d46 , \u0d0f\u0d37\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d21\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d28\u0d1f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d \u0d2e\u0d47\u0d32\u0d4d\u200d \u0d28\u0d4b\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d02 \u0d35\u0d39\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a \u0d38\u0d02\u0d18\u0d1f\u0d28 ?\r\n",
    "answer": "\u0d0f\u0d37\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d28\u0d4d\u200d \u0d17\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d02\u0d38\u0d4d \u0d2b\u0d46\u0d21\u0d31\u0d47\u0d37\u0d28\u0d4d\u200d\r\n",
    "status": "6"
  },
  {
    "id": "612",
    "question": "\u0d15\u0d3f\u0d33\u0d3f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d3e\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d4d \u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d09\u0d2a\u0d1c\u0d4d\u0d1e\u0d3e\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d35\u0d4d ?\r\n",
    "answer": "\u0d0e\u0d34\u0d41\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1b\u0d28\u0d4d\u200d\r\n",
    "status": "9"
  },
  {
    "id": "613",
    "question": "\u0d38\u0d4b\u0d2a\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d02 \u0d06\u0d30\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d06\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d15\u0d25\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d ?\r\n",
    "answer": "\u0d1e\u0d30\u0d33\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d30\u0d3e\u0d2e\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d4a\u0d24\u0d41\u0d35\u0d3e\u0d33\u0d4d\u200d\r\n",
    "status": "9"
  },
  {
    "id": "614",
    "question": "\u0d15\u0d4b\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d28\u0d4d\u200d \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d24\u0d42\u0d32\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d28\u0d3e\u0d2e\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4d\u200d \u0d05\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d46\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d38\u0d3e\u0d39\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d28\u0d4d\u200d ?\r\n",
    "answer": "\u0d2a\u0d3f.\u0d35\u0d3f. \u0d05\u0d2f\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d28\u0d4d\u200d\r\n",
    "status": "9"
  },
  {
    "id": "615",
    "question": "\u0d2a\u0d42\u0d24\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d3e\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d30\u0d1a\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d35\u0d4d ?\r\n",
    "answer": "\u0d07\u0d1f\u0d36\u0d4d\u0d36\u0d47\u0d30\u0d3f \u0d17\u0d4b\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d26\u0d28\u0d4d\u200d \u0d28\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d\r\n",
    "status": "9"
  },
  {
    "id": "616",
    "question": "\u0d1c\u0d4d\u0d1e\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d2a\u0d40\u0d20\u0d02 \u0d32\u0d2d\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a \u0d06\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f \u0d2e\u0d32\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d33 \u0d38\u0d3e\u0d39\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d28\u0d4d\u200d ?\r\n",
    "answer": "\u0d1c\u0d3f. \u0d36\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d30\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d41\u0d31\u0d41\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d4d\r\n",
    "status": "9"
  },
  {
    "id": "617",
    "question": "\u0d05\u0d33\u0d4d\u200d\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d35\u0d2f\u0d32\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d \u0d30\u0d36\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d33\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4d\u200d \u0d28\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d2d\u0d42\u0d2e\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d46 \u0d38\u0d02\u0d30\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d37\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d05\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d30\u0d40\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d37\u0d2a\u0d3e\u0d33\u0d3f ?\r\n",
    "answer": "\u0d13\u0d38\u0d4b\u0d23\u0d4d\u200d \u0d2a\u0d3e\u0d33\u0d3f\r\n",
    "status": "1"
  },
  {
    "id": "618",
    "question": "\u0d38\u0d42\u0d30\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d36\u0d02 \u0d2d\u0d42\u0d2e\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d4d\u200d \u0d35\u0d47\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d1f \u0d38\u0d2e\u0d2f\u0d02 ?\r\n",
    "answer": "8\u0d2e\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d3f\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d4d 20 \u0d38\u0d46\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d\r\n",
    "status": "1"
  },
  {
    "id": "619",
    "question": "\u0d32\u0d4b\u0d15\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d0f\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d35\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d35\u0d32\u0d3f\u0d2f \u0d26\u0d4d\u0d35\u0d40\u0d2a\u0d38\u0d2e\u0d42\u0d39\u0d02 ?\r\n",
    "answer": "\u0d07\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4b\u0d28\u0d47\u0d37\u0d4d\u0d2f\r\n",
    "status": "1"
  },
  {
    "id": "620",
    "question": "\u0d15\u0d30\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d0f\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d35\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d24\u0d3e\u0d34\u0d4d\u200c\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d2d\u0d3e\u0d17\u0d02 ?\r\n",
    "answer": "\u0d1a\u0d3e\u0d35\u0d41 \u0d15\u0d1f\u0d32\u0d4d\u200d (\u0d38\u0d2e\u0d41\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d30 \u0d28\u0d3f\u0d30\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4d\u200d \u0d28\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d41\u0d02 420\u0d2e\u0d40.\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d34\u0d46)\r\n",
    "status": "1"
  },
  {
    "id": "621",
    "question": "\u0d26\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d37\u0d3f\u0d23\u0d17\u0d02\u0d17\u0d4b\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d3f \u0d0e\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d3f \u0d1a\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d41 ?\r\n",
    "answer": "\u0d05\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4d\u200d\r\n",
    "status": "1"
  },
  {
    "id": "622",
    "question": "\u0d2e\u0d27\u0d41\u0d36\u0d3e\u0d32 \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d15\u0d43\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46(\u0d15\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d24) \u0d30\u0d1a\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d35\u0d4d ?\r\n",
    "answer": "\u0d39\u0d30\u0d3f \u0d35\u0d02\u0d36\u0d4d \u0d31\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d4d \u0d2c\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d28\u0d4d\u200d\r\n",
    "status": "9"
  },
  {
    "id": "623",
    "question": "\u0d15\u0d42\u0d32\u0d3f \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d28\u0d4b\u0d35\u0d32\u0d4d\u200d \u0d0e\u0d34\u0d41\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d4d ?\r\n",
    "answer": "\u0d2e\u0d41\u0d32\u0d4d\u200d\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4d \u0d30\u0d3e\u0d1c\u0d4d \u0d06\u0d28\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d26\u0d4d\r\n",
    "status": "9"
  },
  {
    "id": "624",
    "question": "\u0d38\u0d02\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d43\u0d24 \u0d28\u0d3e\u0d1f\u0d15\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d2f \u0d15\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d23\u0d2d\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d02 \u0d0e\u0d34\u0d41\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d4d ?\r\n",
    "answer": "\u0d2d\u0d3e\u0d38\u0d28\u0d4d\u200d\r\n",
    "status": "9"
  },
  {
    "id": "625",
    "question": "\u0d1a\u0d32\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d46\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f \u0d06\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f \u0d2e\u0d32\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d33 \u0d38\u0d3e\u0d39\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f \u0d15\u0d43\u0d24\u0d3f ?\r\n",
    "answer": "\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d21 \u0d35\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2e\r\n",
    "status": "9"
  },
  {
    "id": "626",
    "question": "\u0d38\u0d4b\u0d2e\u0d28\u0d4d\u200d \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d06\u0d30\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d24\u0d42\u0d32\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d3e\u0d2e\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d ?\r\n",
    "answer": "\u0d24\u0d4b\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4d\u200d \u0d2d\u0d3e\u0d38\u0d3f\r\n",
    "status": "9"
  },
  {
    "id": "627",
    "question": "\u0d17\u0d41\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d\u0d35\u0d40\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d26\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d \u0d38\u0d3f\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d19\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d \u0d2e\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a \u0d38\u0d02\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d27\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d15\u0d28\u0d41\u0d33\u0d4d\u0d33 \u0d26\u0d47\u0d36\u0d40\u0d2f \u0d2a\u0d41\u0d30\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d02 \u0d28\u0d47\u0d1f\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4a\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24 \u0d1a\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d02 ?\r\n",
    "answer": "\u0d06\u0d28\u0d4d\u200d\u0d39\u0d46 \u0d16\u0d4b\u0d30\u0d46 \u0d26\u0d3e \u0d26\u0d28\u0d4d\u200d (\u0d2a\u0d1e\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d3e\u0d2c\u0d3f )\r\n",
    "status": "4"
  },
  {
    "id": "628",
    "question": "\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d3e \u0d2c\u0d3e\u0d32\u0d28\u0d4d \u0d2e\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a \u0d28\u0d1f\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d41\u0d33\u0d4d\u0d33 \u0d26\u0d47\u0d36\u0d40\u0d2f \u0d2a\u0d41\u0d30\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d02 \u0d28\u0d47\u0d1f\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4a\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24 \u0d1a\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d02 ?\r\n",
    "answer": "\u0d21\u0d47\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d3f \u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d (\u0d39\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d26\u0d3f)\r\n",
    "status": "4"
  },
  {
    "id": "629",
    "question": "\u0d17\u0d3f\u0d30\u0d40\u0d37\u0d4d \u0d15\u0d41\u0d32\u0d4d\u200d\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d\u0d23\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4d \u0d2e\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a \u0d28\u0d1f\u0d28\u0d41\u0d33\u0d4d\u0d33 \u0d26\u0d47\u0d36\u0d40\u0d2f \u0d2a\u0d41\u0d30\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d02 \u0d28\u0d47\u0d1f\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4a\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24 \u0d1a\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d02 ?\r\n",
    "answer": "\u0d26\u0d47\u0d35\u0d42\u0d33\u0d4d\u200d (\u0d2e\u0d31\u0d3e\u0d20\u0d3f)\r\n",
    "status": "4"
  },
  {
    "id": "630",
    "question": "\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d4d\u200d \u0d2b\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d3f\u0d02 \u0d2b\u0d46\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d35\u0d46\u0d32\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4d\u200d \u0d06\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d3f \u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d26\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d\u0d36\u0d3f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a \u0d05\u0d28\u0d3f\u0d2e\u0d47\u0d37\u0d28\u0d4d\u200d \u0d1a\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d02 ?\r\n",
    "answer": "\u0d05\u0d2a\u0d4d (2010, 63-\u0d3e\u0d02 \u0d2e\u0d47\u0d33\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4d\u200d)\r\n",
    "status": "4"
  },
  {
    "id": "631",
    "question": "\u0d2e\u0d47\u0d33\u0d15\u0d33\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d2e\u0d47\u0d33 \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d4d \u0d2a\u0d47\u0d30\u0d41\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d30\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d1a\u0d32\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d2e\u0d47\u0d33 ?\r\n",
    "answer": "\u0d1f\u0d4a\u0d31\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4b \u0d05\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d37\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d30 \u0d1a\u0d32\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d2e\u0d47\u0d33 (TIFF)\r\n",
    "status": "4"
  },
  {
    "id": "632",
    "question": "\u0d1f\u0d4a\u0d31\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4b \u0d05\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d37\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d30 \u0d1a\u0d32\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d2e\u0d47\u0d33 \u0d06\u0d30\u0d02\u0d2d\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d24\u0d46\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d4d ?\r\n",
    "answer": "1976\u0d32\u0d4d\u200d",
    "status": "4"
  },
  {
    "id": "633",
    "question": "\u0d2d\u0d42\u0d2e\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d46\u0d1a\u0d41\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d3f \u0d38\u0d1e\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a \u0d06\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f \u0d28\u0d3e\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d28\u0d4d\u200d?\r\n",
    "answer": "\u0d2b\u0d46\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d\u0d21\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d17\u0d32\u0d4d\u0d32\u0d28\u0d4d\u200d\r\n",
    "status": "7"
  },
  {
    "id": "634",
    "question": "\u0d2d\u0d42\u0d2e\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d46\u0d1a\u0d41\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d3f \u0d38\u0d1e\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a \u0d06\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f \u0d15\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d32\u0d4d\u200d?\r\n",
    "answer": "\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d4b\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d2f\r\n",
    "status": "7"
  },
  {
    "id": "635",
    "question": "\u0d32\u0d4b\u0d15\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46\u0d0f\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d35\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d35\u0d32\u0d3f\u0d2f \u0d15\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d32\u0d4d\u200d \u0d2a\u0d4a\u0d33\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d32\u0d4d\u200d\u0d15\u0d47\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d02 ?\r\n",
    "answer": "\u0d05\u0d32\u0d3e\u0d19\u0d4d (\u0d17\u0d41\u0d1c\u0d31\u0d3e\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d)\r\n",
    "status": "7"
  },
  {
    "id": "636",
    "question": "\u0d32\u0d4b\u0d15\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d0f\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d35\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d15\u0d42\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d24\u0d32\u0d4d\u200d \u0d05\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d\u0d27\u0d38\u0d48\u0d28\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d30\u0d41\u0d33\u0d4d\u0d33\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d1c\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d02 ?\r\n",
    "answer": "\u0d1a\u0d48\u0d28(2-\u0d3e\u0d02\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d02 \u0d07\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4d)\r\n",
    "status": "7"
  },
  {
    "id": "637",
    "question": "\u0d1a\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46\u0d06\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f \u0d12\u0d33\u0d3f\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d38\u0d4d \u0d28\u0d1f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d24\u0d46\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d4d?\r\n",
    "answer": "\u0d2c\u0d3f.\u0d38\u0d3f.776\u0d32\u0d4d\u200d\r\n",
    "status": "6"
  },
  {
    "id": "638",
    "question": "\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d4b\u0d38\u0d4d\u200c\u0d15\u200c\u0d23\u0d4d\u200d\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d3f \u0d2e\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d38\u0d30\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d46\u0d26\u0d48\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d\u0d18\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d02 \u0d0e\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30 ?\r\n",
    "answer": "10\u0d15\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4b\u0d2e\u0d40\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d\r\n",
    "status": "6"
  },
  {
    "id": "639",
    "question": "\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d40\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d33\u0d4d\u200d\u0d1a\u0d47\u0d38\u0d4d \u0d2e\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d38\u0d30\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d26\u0d48\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d\u0d18\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d02\u0d0e\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30 ?\r\n",
    "answer": "3000 \u0d2e\u0d40\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d\r\n",
    "status": "6"
  },
  {
    "id": "640",
    "question": "\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4b\u0d23\u0d4d\u200d\u0d2e\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d38\u0d30\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d26\u0d42\u0d30\u0d02 \u0d0e\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30 ?\r\n",
    "answer": "42.195 \u0d15\u0d3f.\u0d2e\u0d40.(26\u0d2e\u0d48\u0d32\u0d4d\u200d385\u0d05\u0d1f\u0d3f)\r\n",
    "status": "6"
  },
  {
    "id": "641",
    "question": "\u0d06\u0d30\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46\u0d13\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d2f\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d12\u0d33\u0d3f\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d38\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4d\u200d \u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4b\u0d23\u0d4d\u200d\u0d2e\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d38\u0d30\u0d02 \u0d28\u0d1f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d24\u0d4d ?\r\n",
    "answer": "\u0d2b\u0d3f\u0d21\u0d3f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d21\u0d38\u0d4d(\u0d17\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d40\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4d \u0d38\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d26\u0d47\u0d36\u0d35\u0d3e\u0d39\u0d15\u0d28\u0d4d\u200d)\r\n",
    "status": "6"
  },
  {
    "id": "642",
    "question": "\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4b\u0d23\u0d4d\u200d\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d27\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4d\u200d \u0d2a\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d46\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d1c\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d19\u0d33\u0d4d\u200d ?\r\n",
    "answer": "\u0d0f\u0d24\u0d28\u0d4d\u200d\u0d38\u0d4d- \u0d2a\u0d47\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d\u0d37\u0d4d\u0d2f\r\n",
    "status": "6"
  },
  {
    "id": "643",
    "question": "\u0d12\u0d33\u0d3f\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d38\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46\u0d0f\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d35\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d26\u0d48\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d\u0d18\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d2e\u0d47\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d05\u0d24\u0d4d\u200c\u0d32\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d38\u0d4d \u0d07\u0d28\u0d02 ?\r\n",
    "answer": "\u0d2a\u0d41\u0d30\u0d41\u0d37\u0d28\u0d4d\u200d\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d4650\u0d15\u0d3f.\u0d2e\u0d40\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d\u0d28\u0d1f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d02\r\n",
    "status": "6"
  },
  {
    "id": "644",
    "question": "\u0d12\u0d33\u0d3f\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d38\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46\u0d28\u0d1f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d2e\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d38\u0d30\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d46 \u0d35\u0d3f\u0d33\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d2a\u0d47\u0d30\u0d4d ?\r\n",
    "answer": "\u0d31\u0d47\u0d38\u0d4d \u0d35\u0d3e\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3f\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d19\u0d4d\r\n",
    "status": "6"
  },
  {
    "id": "645",
    "question": "\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d33\u0d4d\u200d\u0d1c\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d46 \u0d35\u0d3f\u0d33\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d2e\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4a\u0d30\u0d41\u0d2a\u0d47\u0d30\u0d4d ?\r\n",
    "answer": "\u0d39\u0d4b\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d46\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d4d \u0d06\u0d28\u0d4d\u200d\u0d21\u0d4d \u0d1c\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d4d\r\n",
    "status": "6"
  },
  {
    "id": "646",
    "question": "\u0d2a\u0d4b\u0d33\u0d4d\u200d\u0d35\u0d3e\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4d\u200d\u0d38\u0d46\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d\u0d1c\u0d3f \u0d2c\u0d42\u0d2c\u0d4d\u0d15 (\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d48\u0d28\u0d4d\u200d)\u0d0e\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30 \u0d24\u0d35\u0d23 \u0d32\u0d4b\u0d15\u0d31\u0d46\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d\u0d21\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d30\u0d41\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d4d ?\r\n",
    "answer": "35 \u0d24\u0d35\u0d23\r\n",
    "status": "6"
  },
  {
    "id": "647",
    "question": "\u0d05\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d37\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d30 \u0d35\u0d28 \u0d35\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d\u0d37\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d3f \u0d2f\u0d41 \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u200d \u0d06\u0d18\u0d4b\u0d37\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d24\u0d4d ?\r\n",
    "answer": "2011\r\n",
    "status": "1"
  },
  {
    "id": "648",
    "question": "\u0d05\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d37\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d30 \u0d35\u0d28 \u0d35\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d\u0d37\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d2e\u0d41\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d35\u0d3e\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d02 ?\r\n",
    "answer": "\u0d35\u0d28\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d19\u0d33\u0d4d\u200d \u0d1c\u0d28\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d19\u0d33\u0d4d\u200d\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4d\r\n",
    "status": "1"
  },
  {
    "id": "649",
    "question": "\u0d05\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d37\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d30 \u0d35\u0d28 \u0d35\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d\u0d37\u0d3e\u0d1a\u0d30\u0d23\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d09\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d26\u0d47\u0d36\u0d02 ?\r\n",
    "answer": "\u0d35\u0d28\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d19\u0d33\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d38\u0d02\u0d30\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d37\u0d23\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d \u0d1c\u0d28\u0d15\u0d40\u0d2f \u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d35\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d28\u0d02\r\n",
    "status": "1"
  },
  {
    "id": "650",
    "question": "\u0d2d\u0d42\u0d2e\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d09\u0d2a\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d32\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d0e\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30 \u0d36\u0d24\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d \u0d35\u0d28\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d19\u0d33\u0d4d\u200d ?\r\n",
    "answer": "31%\r\n",
    "status": "1"
  },
  {
    "id": "651",
    "question": "\u0d1c\u0d4d\u0d1e\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d2a\u0d40\u0d20\u0d02 \u0d28\u0d47\u0d1f\u0d3f\u0d2f \u0d06\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f \u0d35\u0d28\u0d3f\u0d24 ?\r\n",
    "answer": "\u0d06\u0d36\u0d3e\u0d2a\u0d42\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d23\u0d3e\u0d26\u0d47\u0d35\u0d3f",
    "status": "9"
  },
  {
    "id": "652",
    "question": "\u0d15\u0d47\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d30 \u0d38\u0d3e\u0d39\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f \u0d05\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d26\u0d2e\u0d3f \u0d05\u0d35\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d\u0d21\u0d4d \u0d28\u0d47\u0d1f\u0d3f\u0d2f \u0d06\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f \u0d35\u0d28\u0d3f\u0d24 ?\r\n",
    "answer": "\u0d05\u0d2e\u0d43\u0d24\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d40\u0d24\u0d02 ( \u0d2a\u0d1e\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d3e\u0d2c\u0d4d )\r\n",
    "status": "9"
  },
  {
    "id": "653",
    "question": "\u0d0f\u0d37\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d28\u0d4d\u200d \u0d17\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d02\u0d38\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4d\u200d \u0d38\u0d4d\u0d35\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d23\u0d2e\u0d46\u0d21\u0d32\u0d4d\u200d \u0d28\u0d47\u0d1f\u0d3f\u0d2f \u0d06\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f \u0d07\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d3f ?\r\n",
    "answer": "\u0d15\u0d2e\u0d32\u0d4d\u200d \u0d1c\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d38\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d27\u0d41 (1970)\r\n",
    "status": "6"
  },
  {
    "id": "654",
    "question": "\u0d12\u0d33\u0d3f\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d38\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4d\u200d \u0d2e\u0d46\u0d21\u0d32\u0d4d\u200d \u0d28\u0d47\u0d1f\u0d3f\u0d2f \u0d06\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f \u0d07\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d3f ?\r\n",
    "answer": "\u0d15\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d23\u0d02 \u0d2e\u0d32\u0d4d\u0d32\u0d47\u0d36\u0d4d\u0d35\u0d30\u0d3f\r\n",
    "status": "6"
  },
  {
    "id": "655",
    "question": "\u0d17\u0d23\u0d3f\u0d24 \u0d36\u0d3e\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d28\u0d4b\u0d2c\u0d32\u0d4d\u200d \u0d38\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d02 \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d46\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d24\u0d4d ?\r\n",
    "answer": "\u0d06\u0d2c\u0d47\u0d32\u0d4d\u200d \u0d2a\u0d41\u0d30\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d02\r\n",
    "status": "5"
  },
  {
    "id": "656",
    "question": "'\u0d21\u0d3e\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d1e\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d3f \u0d15\u0d4b\u0d21\u0d4d ' \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d2a\u0d41\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d15\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d30\u0d1a\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d35\u0d4d ?\r\n",
    "answer": "\u0d21\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d4d\u200d \u0d2c\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d4c\u0d23\u0d4d\u200d\r\n",
    "status": "9"
  },
  {
    "id": "657",
    "question": "\u0d1f\u0d46\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d \u0d15\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4d\u200d \u0d06\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d3f \u0d21\u0d2c\u0d3f\u0d33\u0d4d\u200d \u0d38\u0d46\u0d1e\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d35\u0d31\u0d3f \u0d28\u0d47\u0d1f\u0d3f\u0d2f \u0d07\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d28\u0d4d\u200d ?\r\n",
    "answer": "\u0d2a\u0d4b\u0d33\u0d3f \u0d09\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d17\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d\r\n",
    "status": "6"
  },
  {
    "id": "658",
    "question": "\u0d06\u0d30\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d1c\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d26\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d \u0d32\u0d4b\u0d15 \u0d2a\u0d41\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d15 \u0d26\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d4d \u0d06\u0d1a\u200c\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d24\u0d4d ?\r\n",
    "answer": "\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d02 \u0d37\u0d47\u0d15\u0d4d\u200c\u0d38\u0d4d\u200c\u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d\r\n",
    "status": "9"
  },
  {
    "id": "659",
    "question": "\u0d07\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d\u0d28\u0d46\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d2e\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u200d\u0d17\u0d3e\u0d2e\u0d3f \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d46\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d28\u0d46\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d\u200c\u0d35\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4d \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d4d ?\r\n",
    "answer": "ARPANET(1969)\r\n",
    "status": "8"
  },
  {
    "id": "660",
    "question": "\u0d17\u0d42\u0d17\u0d3f\u0d33\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d38\u0d43\u0d37\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d3e\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d33\u0d4d\u200d ?\r\n",
    "answer": "\u0d32\u0d3e\u0d31\u0d3f \u0d2a\u0d47\u0d1c\u0d4d, \u0d38\u0d46\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d\u0d1c\u0d3f\u0d2c\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u200d\r\n",
    "status": "8"
  },
  {
    "id": "661",
    "question": "\u0d05\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d30\u0d40\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d37\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d13\u0d38\u0d4b\u0d23\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d05\u0d33\u0d35\u0d4d \u0d05\u0d33\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d2f\u0d42\u0d23\u0d3f\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d4d ?\r\n",
    "answer": "\u0d21\u0d4b\u0d2c\u0d4d\u0d38\u0d23\u0d4d\u200d\r\n",
    "status": "1"
  },
  {
    "id": "662",
    "question": "\u0d2a\u0d38\u0d2b\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d \u0d38\u0d2e\u0d41\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d \u0d06 \u0d2a\u0d47\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f \u0d2e\u0d39\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d4d\u200d ?\r\n",
    "answer": "\u0d2b\u0d46\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d\u0d21\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d \u0d2e\u0d17\u0d32\u0d4d\u0d32\u0d28\u0d4d\u200d\r\n",
    "status": "1"
  },
  {
    "id": "663",
    "question": "\u0d2e\u0d32\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d33\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d06\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f \u0d0f\u0d15\u0d2d\u0d3e\u0d37\u0d3e \u0d28\u0d3f\u0d18\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d30\u0d1a\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d35\u0d4d \u0d06\u0d30\u0d4d ?\r\n",
    "answer": "\u0d36\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d40\u0d15\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d20\u0d47\u0d36\u0d4d\u0d35\u0d30\u0d02 \u0d2a\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d28\u0d3e\u0d2d \u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d33\u0d4d\u0d33",
    "status": "9"
  },
  {
    "id": "664",
    "question": "\u0d2e\u0d32\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d33\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d06\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f \u0d38\u0d3e\u0d39\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d38\u0d3f\u0d15 \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d4d ?\r\n",
    "answer": "\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d3e\u0d38\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d3f",
    "status": "9"
  },
  {
    "id": "665",
    "question": "\u0d2e\u0d32\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d33\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d06\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d46 \u0d32\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d37\u0d23\u0d2e\u0d4a\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24 \u0d2e\u0d39\u0d3e\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d35\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d02 ?\r\n",
    "answer": "\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d2e\u0d1a\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d3e\u0d38\u0d02",
    "status": "9"
  },
  {
    "id": "666",
    "question": "\u0d2e\u0d32\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d33\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d06\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d46 \u0d38\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d26\u0d47\u0d36\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d35\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d02?\r\n",
    "answer": "\u0d2e\u0d2f\u0d42\u0d30\u0d38\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d26\u0d47\u0d36\u0d02",
    "status": "9"
  },
  {
    "id": "667",
    "question": "11,13,17,23,31, ___ ,\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d2a\u0d4b\u0d2f \u0d38\u0d02\u0d16\u0d4d\u0d2f \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d4d ?\r\n",
    "answer": "41",
    "status": "5"
  },
  {
    "id": "668",
    "question": "1X 2 X 3 X 0 X 4 x 1 =?\r\n",
    "answer": "0",
    "status": "5"
  },
  {
    "id": "669",
    "question": "\u0d38\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d32\u0d28\u0d17\u0d23\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u200d\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d35\u0d4d \u0d06\u0d30\u0d4d?\r\n",
    "answer": "\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d42\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d23\u0d4d\u200d",
    "status": "5"
  },
  {
    "id": "670",
    "question": "\u0d15\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d42\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d7c \u0d2e\u0d57\u0d38\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d35\u0d4d ?",
    "answer": "\u0d21\u0d17\u0d4d\u0d32\u0d38\u0d4d \u0d0e\u0d02\u0d17\u0d7d\u0d2c\u0d7c\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d4d.",
    "status": "8"
  },
  {
    "id": "671",
    "question": "\u0d12\u0d30\u0d41 \u0d35\u0d46\u0d2c\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d47\u0d1c\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d27\u0d3e\u0d28 \u0d2a\u0d47\u0d1c\u0d4d \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d2a\u0d47\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d46\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d41 ? ",
    "answer": "\u0d39\u0d47\u0d3e\u0d02 \u0d2a\u0d47\u0d1c\u0d4d.",
    "status": "8"
  },
  {
    "id": "672",
    "question": "\u0d12\u0d30\u0d41 \u0d21\u0d3e\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d3e \u0d2c\u0d47\u0d38\u0d3f\u0d7d \u0d28\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d4b \u0d28\u0d46\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d \u0d35\u0d7c\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3f\u0d7d \u0d28\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d4b \u0d21\u0d3e\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d3e \u0d38\u0d46\u0d7c\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d4d \u0d1a\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d2f ? ",
    "answer": "\u0d2c\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d57\u0d38\u0d4d",
    "status": "8"
  },
  {
    "id": "673",
    "question": ". \u0d38\u0d4d\u0d35\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d02 \u0d30\u0d1a\u0d28\u0d15\u0d7e \u0d35\u0d46\u0d2c\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d47\u0d1c\u0d41\u0d15\u0d33\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d3f \u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d38\u0d3f\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d27\u0d40\u0d15 \u0d30\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d7b \u0d38\u0d39\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d07\u0d7b\u0d31\u0d7c\u0d28\u0d46\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d \u0d38\u0d02\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d27\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d02 ?",
    "answer": "\u0d2c\u0d4d\u0d32\u0d4b\u0d17\u0d4d",
    "status": "8"
  },
  {
    "id": "674",
    "question": "\u0d07\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d7b \u0d35\u0d3f\u0d35\u0d30\u0d38\u0d3e\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d47\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d15 \u0d35\u0d3f\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d35\u0d4d ? ",
    "answer": "\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d1c\u0d40\u0d35\u0d4d \u0d17\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d27\u0d3f ",
    "status": "8"
  },
  {
    "id": "675",
    "question": "\u0d1c\u0d3f.\u0d2a\u0d3f.\u0d0e\u0d38\u0d4d (global positioning system) \u0d35\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d38\u0d3f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d46\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24 \u0d30\u0d3e\u0d1c\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d02 ? ",
    "answer": "\u0d2f\u0d41.\u0d0e\u0d38\u0d4d.\u0d0e",
    "status": "8"
  },
  {
    "id": "676",
    "question": "\u0d0f\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d35\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d15\u0d42\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d24\u0d7d \u0d31\u0d4b\u0d2c\u0d4b\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d15\u0d7e \u0d28\u0d3f\u0d7c\u0d2e\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d41\u0d15\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d09\u0d2a\u0d2f\u0d4b\u0d17\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d41\u0d15\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d1a\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d30\u0d3e\u0d1c\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d02 ?",
    "answer": "\u0d1c\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d3e\u0d7b",
    "status": "8"
  },
  {
    "id": "677",
    "question": ". \u0d07\u0d32\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d4b\u0d23\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d \u0d31\u0d46\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4b\u0d21\u0d41\u0d15\u0d33\u0d46 \u0d38\u0d41\u0d30\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d37\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d3f \u0d09\u0d2a\u0d2f\u0d4b\u0d17\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d2f ?",
    "answer": "\u0d0e\u0d7b\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d37\u0d7b",
    "status": "8"
  },
  {
    "id": "678",
    "question": "\u0d15\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d42\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d47\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4d \u0d35\u0d3f\u0d35\u0d30\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d19\u0d7e \u0d28\u0d7d\u0d15\u0d41\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d4b\u0d34\u0d4b \u0d28\u0d7d\u0d15\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d \u0d2e\u0d41\u0d7b\u0d2a\u0d4b \u0d2e\u0d28\u0d03\u0d2a\u0d42\u0d7c\u0d35\u0d02 \u0d05\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d21\u0d3e\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31 \u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d02 \u0d35\u0d30\u0d41\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d15\u0d41\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d15\u0d43\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d02 ?",
    "answer": "Data Diddling",
    "status": "8"
  },
  {
    "id": "679",
    "question": "\u0d12\u0d30\u0d41 \u0d2f\u0d42\u0d38\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d2b\u0d2f\u0d32\u0d41\u0d15\u0d33\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d21\u0d3e\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d05\u0d35\u0d30\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d24\u0d46 \u0d35\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d ?",
    "answer": "Snooping",
    "status": "8"
  },
  {
    "id": "680",
    "question": "\u0d06\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d2e\u0d4a\u0d2c\u0d48\u0d7d \u0d2b\u0d4b\u0d7a \u0d35\u0d48\u0d31\u0d38\u0d4d \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d4d ?",
    "answer": "Cabir",
    "status": "8"
  },
  {
    "id": "681",
    "question": "\u0d06\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f \u0d15\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d42\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d7c \u0d35\u0d48\u0d31\u0d38\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d ?",
    "answer": "\u0d2c\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d7b",
    "status": "8"
  },
  {
    "id": "682",
    "question": "\u0d17\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d3f \u0d15\u0d3e\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d31\u0d4b\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d46 \u0d1a\u0d46\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d38\u0d3f\u0d7d \u0d2a\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d1c\u0d2f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d46\u0d1f\u0d41 \u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d2f \u0d15\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d42\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d7c \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d4d ?",
    "answer": "\u0d21\u0d40\u0d2a\u0d4d \u0d2c\u0d4d\u0d32\u0d42",
    "status": "8"
  },
  {
    "id": "683",
    "question": "User \u0d15\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d42\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d7d\u0d28\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d4d \u0d2e\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d41 \u0d15\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d42\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d47\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4d \u0d2b\u0d2f\u0d32\u0d41\u0d15\u0d7e \u0d15\u0d4b\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d3f \u0d1a\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d2f ?",
    "answer": "\u0d05\u0d2a\u0d4d \u0d32\u0d4b\u0d21\u0d3f\u0d19\u0d4d",
    "status": "8"
  },
  {
    "id": "684",
    "question": "\u0d07\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d0f\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d35\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d35\u0d32\u0d3f\u0d2f \u0d07- \u0d17\u0d35\u0d47\u0d23\u0d7b\u0d38\u0d4d \u0d2a\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d27\u0d24\u0d3f ?",
    "answer": "\u0d2a\u0d3e\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d4b\u0d7c\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d4d \u0d38\u0d47\u0d35",
    "status": "8"
  },
  {
    "id": "685",
    "question": "EEPROM-\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d2a\u0d42\u0d7c\u0d23\u0d30\u0d42\u0d2a\u0d02 ?",
    "answer": "\u0d07\u0d32\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d32\u0d3f \u0d07\u0d31\u0d47\u0d38\u0d3f\u0d2c\u0d3f\u0d7e \u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d4b\u0d17\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d2e\u0d2c\u0d3f\u0d7e \u0d31\u0d40\u0d21\u0d4d \u0d13\u0d7a\u0d32\u0d3f \u0d2e\u0d46\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d31\u0d3f",
    "status": "8"
  },
  {
    "id": "686",
    "question": "\u0d2e\u0d4b\u0d21\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d38\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d40\u0d21\u0d4d \u0d38\u0d42\u0d1a\u0d3f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d24\u0d4d 56 kbps,256 kbps \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d3f\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d19\u0d28\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d. \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d \u0d07\u0d24\u0d41\u0d15\u0d4a\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d4d \u0d05\u0d7c\u0d25\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d24\u0d4d ?",
    "answer": "\u0d21\u0d3e\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d \u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d7b\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d7c \u0d38\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d40\u0d21\u0d4d.",
    "status": "8"
  },
  {
    "id": "687",
    "question": "\u0d12\u0d30\u0d41 \u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d47\u0d15 \u0d1c\u0d4b\u0d32\u0d3f \u0d1a\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d7b \u0d35\u0d47\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d33\u0d4d\u0d33 \u0d12\u0d30\u0d41 \u0d15\u0d42\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d02 \u0d28\u0d3f\u0d7c\u0d26\u0d47\u0d36\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d19\u0d33\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d38\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d39\u0d30\u0d23\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d ? ",
    "answer": "\u0d38\u0d4b\u0d2b\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d \u0d35\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d7c",
    "status": "8"
  },
  {
    "id": "688",
    "question": "\u0d12\u0d30\u0d41 \u0d15\u0d42\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d02 \u0d2b\u0d2f\u0d32\u0d41\u0d15\u0d33\u0d46 \u0d36\u0d47\u0d16\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d41\u0d35\u0d46\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d - - - - - - - - - \u0d09\u0d2a\u0d2f\u0d4b\u0d17\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d24\u0d4d ? ",
    "answer": "\u0d2b\u0d4b\u0d7c\u0d21\u0d7c",
    "status": "8"
  },
  {
    "id": "689",
    "question": "\u0d39\u0d3e\u0d7c\u0d21\u0d4d \u0d21\u0d3f\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4d, \u0d38\u0d3f.\u0d21\u0d3f., \u0d21\u0d3f.\u0d35\u0d3f.\u0d21\u0d3f. \u0d24\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d19\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d35 \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d30\u0d02 \u0d2e\u0d46\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4d \u0d09\u0d26\u0d3e\u0d39\u0d30\u0d23\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d ?",
    "answer": "\u0d38\u0d46\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d7b\u0d21\u0d31\u0d3f \u0d2e\u0d46\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d31\u0d3f",
    "status": "8"
  },
  {
    "id": "690",
    "question": "\u0d1f\u0d3e\u0d32\u0d3f \u0d38\u0d4b\u0d2b\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d35\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d7c \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d2e\u0d47\u0d16\u0d32\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d3f \u0d2c\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d27\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d46\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d3f\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d41 ?",
    "answer": "\u0d05\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d57\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d3f\u0d19\u0d4d",
    "status": "8"
  },
  {
    "id": "691",
    "question": "PDF-\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d2a\u0d42\u0d7c\u0d23\u0d30\u0d42\u0d2a\u0d02 ?",
    "answer": "\u0d2a\u0d4b\u0d7c\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d2c\u0d3f\u0d7e \u0d21\u0d4b\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d2e\u0d46\u0d7b\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d2b\u0d4b\u0d7c\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d",
    "status": "8"
  },
  {
    "id": "692",
    "question": "\u0d07\u0d7b\u0d31\u0d7c\u0d28\u0d46\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d7d\u0d28\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d4d \u0d35\u0d3f\u0d35\u0d30\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d19\u0d7e \u0d15\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d46\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d7b \u0d38\u0d39\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d24\u0d4d ?",
    "answer": "\u0d38\u0d46\u0d7c\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d4d \u0d0e\u0d1e\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d3f\u0d7b",
    "status": "8"
  },
  {
    "id": "693",
    "question": "\u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d \u0d12\u0d30\u0d41 \u0d05\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d3e\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d46\u0d7b\u0d31\u0d4d ? ",
    "answer": "\u0d12\u0d30\u0d41 \u0d07\u0d2e\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d7d \u0d38\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d26\u0d47\u0d36\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d46\u0d15\u0d42\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d05\u0d2f\u0d2f\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d2b\u0d2f\u0d7d",
    "status": "8"
  },
  {
    "id": "694",
    "question": "\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d7c \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d30\u0d02 \u0d09\u0d2a\u0d15\u0d30\u0d23\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d ?",
    "answer": "\u0d07\u0d7b\u0d2a\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d4d",
    "status": "8"
  },
  {
    "id": "695",
    "question": "JPG \u0d12\u0d30\u0d41 ....... \u0d06\u0d23\u0d4d ?",
    "answer": "\u0d17\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d2b\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d38\u0d4d \u0d2b\u0d2f\u0d7d \u0d0e\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d7b\u0d37\u0d7b",
    "status": "8"
  },
  {
    "id": "696",
    "question": "\u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d URL ?",
    "answer": "\u0d35\u0d46\u0d2c\u0d4d \u0d38\u0d48\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d \u0d05\u0d21\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d38\u0d4d.(Uniform Resource Locator)",
    "status": "8"
  },
  {
    "id": "697",
    "question": "E- mail-\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d09\u0d2a\u0d1c\u0d4d\u0d1e\u0d3e\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d35\u0d4d ?",
    "answer": "RayTomlinson (\u0d07\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d7b \u0d35\u0d02\u0d36\u0d1c\u0d28\u0d3e\u0d2f \u0d36\u0d3f\u0d35 \u0d05\u0d2f\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d3e \u0d26\u0d41\u0d30\u0d48\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d \u0d06\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d3f e-mail \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d06\u0d36\u0d2f\u0d02 \u0d2e\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d4b\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d4d \u0d35\u0d46\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d24\u0d46\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d41\u0d02 ",
    "status": "8"
  },
  {
    "id": "698",
    "question": "Don\u2019t be evil \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d24\u0d4d ?",
    "answer": "Google-\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d06\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d35\u0d3e\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d02.",
    "status": "8"
  },
  {
    "id": "699",
    "question": "\u0d10.\u0d1f\u0d3f. \u0d06\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d4d 2000 \u0d28\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d7d \u0d35\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d24\u0d4d ?",
    "answer": "2000 \u0d12\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d4b\u0d2c\u0d7c 17",
    "status": "8"
  },
  {
    "id": "700",
    "question": "\u0d12\u0d30\u0d41 \u0d15\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d42\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d4b, \u0d28\u0d46\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d \u0d35\u0d7c\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d4b \u0d38\u0d41\u0d30\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d37 \u0d2d\u0d47\u0d26\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d4d \u0d05\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d35\u0d3f\u0d35\u0d30\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d19\u0d7e \u0d15\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d1f\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d2f ?",
    "answer": "\u0d39\u0d3e\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3f\u0d19\u0d4d",
    "status": "8"
  },
  {
    "id": "701",
    "question": "\u0d38\u0d48\u0d2c\u0d7c \u0d28\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d2e\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d19\u0d7e \u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d2c\u0d32\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d41\u0d33\u0d4d\u0d33 \u0d26\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d37\u0d3f\u0d23\u0d47\u0d37\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d0f\u0d15 \u0d30\u0d3e\u0d1c\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d02 ?",
    "answer": "\u0d07\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f",
    "status": "8"
  },
  {
    "id": "702",
    "question": "\u0d26\u0d41\u0d30\u0d41\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d26\u0d47\u0d36\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4b\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d15\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d42\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4b \u0d28\u0d46\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d \u0d35\u0d7c\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4b \u0d05\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d2e\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d4d \u0d15\u0d2f\u0d31\u0d3f \u0d05\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d35\u0d3f\u0d35\u0d30\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d19\u0d7e \u0d1a\u0d4b\u0d7c\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d46\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d35\u0d43\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f ?",
    "answer": "\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3f\u0d19\u0d4d",
    "status": "8"
  },
  {
    "id": "703",
    "question": "\u201d\u0d30\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d35\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d15\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d23\u0d40\u0d30\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d35\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d7c\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d15\u0d20\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d3e\u0d27\u0d4d\u0d35\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d35\u0d41\u0d2e\u0d32\u0d4d\u0d32\u0d3e\u0d24\u0d46 \u0d2e\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4a\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d28\u0d3f\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d19\u0d7e\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4d \u0d24\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d7b \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4d\u0d32 \u201d \u2013 \u0d06\u0d30\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d35\u0d3e\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d41\u0d15\u0d7e ?",
    "answer": "\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d28\u0d4d \u0d1a\u0d30\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4d",
    "status": "7"
  },
  {
    "id": "704",
    "question": "\u0d2a\u0d4a\u0d24\u0d41\u0d2a\u0d23\u0d3f\u0d2e\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4d \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d06\u0d36\u0d2f\u0d02 \u0d09\u0d30\u0d41\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d1e\u0d4d\u0d1e\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d30\u0d3e\u0d1c\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d ?",
    "answer": "\u0d2c\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d28\u0d4d",
    "status": "7"
  },
  {
    "id": "705",
    "question": "\u0d17\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d3f \u0d2c\u0d3e\u0d7e\u0d21\u0d3f \u0d0f\u0d15\u0d40\u0d15\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a \u0d30\u0d3e\u0d37\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d02 ?",
    "answer": "\u0d07\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d32\u0d3f",
    "status": "7"
  },
  {
    "id": "706",
    "question": "\u0d2a\u0d41\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d24\u0d28 \u0d15\u0d3e\u0d32\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d05\u0d38\u0d40\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d2f \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d46\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f \u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d26\u0d47\u0d36\u0d02 \u0d07\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d4b\u0d7e \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d30\u0d3e\u0d1c\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d ? ",
    "answer": "\u0d07\u0d31\u0d3e\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4d",
    "status": "7"
  },
  {
    "id": "707",
    "question": "\u0d1c\u0d42\u0d24\u0d2e\u0d24\u0d02 \u0d14\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d4b\u0d17\u0d3f\u0d15 \u0d2e\u0d24\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d33\u0d4d\u0d33 \u0d0f\u0d15 \u0d30\u0d3e\u0d1c\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d02 ?",
    "answer": "\u0d07\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d2f\u0d47\u0d32\u0d4d",
    "status": "7"
  },
  {
    "id": "708",
    "question": "\u0d32\u0d4b\u0d15\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d06\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d3f \u0d39\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d32\u0d35\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d \u0d24\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d02 \u0d15\u0d41\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a \u0d30\u0d3e\u0d1c\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d02 ? ",
    "answer": "\u0d2e\u0d46\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d38\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4b",
    "status": "7"
  },
  {
    "id": "709",
    "question": "\u201d\u0d0e\u0d28\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4d \u0d28\u0d3f\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d19\u0d7e \u0d28\u0d32\u0d4d\u0d32 \u0d05\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d46 \u0d24\u0d30\u0d42, \u0d1e\u0d3e\u0d7b \u0d28\u0d3f\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d19\u0d7e\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4d \u0d2e\u0d39\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d2f \u0d30\u0d3e\u0d37\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d02 \u0d24\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d02\u201d \u0d06\u0d30\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d35\u0d3e\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d41\u0d15\u0d7e ?",
    "answer": "\u0d28\u0d46\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d4b\u0d33\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d28\u0d4d",
    "status": "7"
  },
  {
    "id": "710",
    "question": "\u0d2c\u0d4a\u0d33\u0d40\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d7b \u0d21\u0d2f\u0d31\u0d3f \u2013 \u0d06\u0d30\u0d46\u0d34\u0d41\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d ?",
    "answer": "\u0d1a\u0d46\u0d17\u0d41\u0d35\u0d47\u0d30",
    "status": "7"
  },
  {
    "id": "711",
    "question": "\u0d32\u0d4b\u0d15\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d47\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d35\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d15\u0d42\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d24\u0d32\u0d4d \u0d2e\u0d24\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d19\u0d33\u0d41\u0d33\u0d4d\u0d33 \u0d30\u0d3e\u0d1c\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d02 ?",
    "answer": "\u0d07\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f",
    "status": "7"
  },
  {
    "id": "712",
    "question": "\u0d0f\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d35\u0d3f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d32\u0d35\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d2e\u0d41\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d35\u0d3e\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d30\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d41 \u0d38\u0d4d\u0d35\u0d3e\u0d24\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d02 ,\u0d38\u0d2e\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d35\u0d02, \u0d38\u0d3e\u0d39\u0d4b\u0d26\u0d30\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d02 ?",
    "answer": "\u0d2b\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d1e\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d4d \u0d35\u0d3f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d32\u0d35\u0d02",
    "status": "7"
  },
  {
    "id": "713",
    "question": "\u0d38\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d4b\u0d23\u0d3f\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d \u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d2b\u0d32\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d3f \u0d30\u0d42\u0d2a\u0d02 \u0d15\u0d4a\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d1f \u0d30\u0d3e\u0d1c\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d02 ?",
    "answer": "\u0d07\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d2f\u0d47\u0d7d",
    "status": "7"
  },
  {
    "id": "714",
    "question": "\u0d1a\u0d46\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3f\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d16\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d4d \u0d07\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d28\u0d4d \u0d06\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d2e\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a \u0d35\u0d30\u0d4d\u0d37\u0d02.?",
    "answer": "AD 1221",
    "status": "7"
  },
  {
    "id": "715",
    "question": "\u0d36\u0d24\u0d35\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d38\u0d30 \u0d2f\u0d41\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d27\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d7d \u0d07\u0d02\u0d17\u0d4d\u0d32\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4b\u0d1f\u0d4d \u0d0f\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d41\u0d2e\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d3f\u0d2f \u0d30\u0d3e\u0d1c\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d02 ? ",
    "answer": "\u0d2b\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d38\u0d4d",
    "status": "7"
  },
  {
    "id": "716",
    "question": "\u0d05\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3f\u0d7e \u0d39\u0d4b \u2013 \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d05\u0d2a\u0d30\u0d28\u0d3e\u0d2e\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d7d \u0d05\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d46\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f \u0d35\u0d3f\u0d2e\u0d4b\u0d1a\u0d28\u0d28\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d15\u0d7b ?",
    "answer": "\u0d39\u0d4b\u0d1a\u0d3f\u0d2e\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d",
    "status": "7"
  },
  {
    "id": "717",
    "question": "\u0d2e\u0d28\u0d41\u0d37\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d28\u0d4d \u0d38\u0d3e\u0d2e\u0d42\u0d39\u0d3f\u0d15 \u0d1c\u0d40\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d02 \u0d06\u0d30\u0d02\u0d2d\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a \u0d15\u0d3e\u0d32\u0d18\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d02 \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d ? ",
    "answer": "\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d1a\u0d40\u0d28 \u0d36\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d17\u0d02",
    "status": "7"
  },
  {
    "id": "718",
    "question": "\u0d39\u0d3f\u0d30\u0d4b\u0d37\u0d3f\u0d2e\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d7d \u0d05\u0d23\u0d41\u0d2c\u0d4b\u0d02\u0d2c\u0d4d \u0d05\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d2e\u0d23\u0d02 \u0d28\u0d1f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d35\u0d7c\u0d37\u0d02 ?",
    "answer": "1945",
    "status": "7"
  },
  {
    "id": "719",
    "question": "\u0d15\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d41\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d4d \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d3e \u0d05\u0d30\u0d4d\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d27 \u0d38\u0d48\u0d28\u0d3f\u0d15 \u0d38\u0d02\u0d18\u0d1f\u0d28\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d41 \u0d30\u0d42\u0d2a\u0d02 \u0d28\u0d32\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d06\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d.? ",
    "answer": "\u0d2e\u0d41\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d38\u0d4b\u0d33\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d3f",
    "status": "7"
  },
  {
    "id": "720",
    "question": "\u0d24\u0d46\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d47 \u0d05\u0d2e\u0d47\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d0f\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d35\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d2a\u0d34\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d02 \u0d1a\u0d46\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d28\u0d3e\u0d17\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d24 .?",
    "answer": "\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d28\u0d4d \u0d38\u0d02\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d02",
    "status": "7"
  },
  {
    "id": "721",
    "question": "\u0d35\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d2f \u0d2b\u0d3e\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d31\u0d3f \u0d28\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d2e\u0d02 \u0d2a\u0d3e\u0d38\u0d3e\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3f\u0d2f \u0d32\u0d4b\u0d15\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d06\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f \u0d30\u0d3e\u0d1c\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d02 ? ",
    "answer": "\u0d07\u0d02\u0d17\u0d4d\u0d32\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d4d",
    "status": "7"
  },
  {
    "id": "722",
    "question": "\u0d35\u0d46\u0d1f\u0d3f\u0d2e\u0d30\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d4d \u0d15\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d41 \u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d1f\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d30\u0d3e\u0d1c\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d ?",
    "answer": "\u0d1a\u0d48\u0d28",
    "status": "7"
  },
  {
    "id": "723",
    "question": "\u0d05\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d37\u0d30\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d32\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4d \u0d38\u0d4d\u0d35\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d37\u0d30\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d19\u0d33\u0d4d \u0d06\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d3f \u0d05\u0d35\u0d24\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d06\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d ?",
    "answer": "\u0d17\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d40\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d41\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d",
    "status": "7"
  },
  {
    "id": "724",
    "question": "\u0d1c\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d3e\u0d7b \u0d2a\u0d47\u0d7e \u0d39\u0d3e\u0d7c\u0d2c\u0d7c \u0d24\u0d41\u0d31\u0d2e\u0d41\u0d16\u0d02 \u0d05\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d2e\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a \u0d35\u0d7c\u0d37\u0d02 ? ",
    "answer": "1941",
    "status": "7"
  },
  {
    "id": "725",
    "question": "\u0d1a\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d15\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d02 \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d41 \u0d1a\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d24\u0d40\u0d24 \u0d15\u0d3e\u0d32\u0d18\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d47\u0d15\u0d24\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d ? ",
    "answer": " \u0d28\u0d35\u0d40\u0d28 \u0d36\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d17\u0d02",
    "status": "7"
  },
  {
    "id": "726",
    "question": "\u0d1a\u0d48\u0d28\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d7d \u0d0f\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d35\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d15\u0d42\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d24\u0d7d \u0d15\u0d3e\u0d32\u0d02 \u0d2d\u0d30\u0d23\u0d02 \u0d28\u0d1f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d30\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d30\u0d3e\u0d1c\u0d35\u0d02\u0d36\u0d02 ?",
    "answer": "\u0d2e\u0d1e\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d41 \u0d30\u0d3e\u0d1c \u0d35\u0d02\u0d36\u0d02",
    "status": "7"
  },
  {
    "id": "727",
    "question": "\u0d31\u0d37\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d7b \u0d35\u0d3f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d32\u0d35\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d38\u0d2e\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d24 \u0d28\u0d47\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d35\u0d4d ? ",
    "answer": "\u0d35\u0d4d\u0d32\u0d3e\u0d26\u0d3f\u0d2e\u0d30\u0d4d \u0d32\u0d46\u0d28\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d",
    "status": "7"
  },
  {
    "id": "728",
    "question": "\u0d38\u0d41\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d38\u0d3f\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d27\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d2f \u201d \u0d0e\u0d2e\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d3f \u201d \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d15\u0d43\u0d24\u0d3f \u0d06\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d \u0d0e\u0d34\u0d41\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d24\u0d4d ?",
    "answer": "\u0d31\u0d42\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d38\u0d4b",
    "status": "7"
  },
  {
    "id": "729",
    "question": "\u0d1c\u0d28\u0d3e\u0d27\u0d3f\u0d2a\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d06\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d27\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d41\u0d30 \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d24\u0d4d ?",
    "answer": "\u0d05\u0d2e\u0d47\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15",
    "status": "7"
  },
  {
    "id": "730",
    "question": "\u0d0f\u0d24\u0d41 \u0d2f\u0d41\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d27\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d2b\u0d32\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d \u0d1a\u0d48\u0d28\u0d40\u0d38\u0d4d \u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d35\u0d36\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d2f \u0d39\u0d4b\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4b\u0d02\u0d17\u0d4d \u0d2c\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d28\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d23\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4d \u0d06\u0d2f\u0d24\u0d41 ?",
    "answer": "\u0d15\u0d31\u0d41\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d4d \u0d2f\u0d41\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d27\u0d02",
    "status": "7"
  },
  {
    "id": "731",
    "question": "\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d2e\u0d42\u0d30\u0d4d \u0d07\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f \u0d06\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d2e\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a \u0d35\u0d30\u0d4d\u0d37\u0d02 ? ",
    "answer": "AD 1398\r\n",
    "status": "7"
  },
  {
    "id": "732",
    "question": "1492 \u0d07\u0d32\u0d4d \u0d05\u0d2e\u0d47\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15 \u0d15\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d46\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d06\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d ? ",
    "answer": "\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d2b\u0d30\u0d4d \u0d15\u0d4a\u0d33\u0d02\u0d2c\u0d38\u0d4d",
    "status": "7"
  },
  {
    "id": "733",
    "question": "\u0d21\u0d3f\u0d35\u0d48\u0d28\u0d4d \u0d15\u0d4b\u0d2e\u0d21\u0d3f \u0d30\u0d1a\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d06\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d ?",
    "answer": "\u0d21\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d4d\u200d\u0d31\u0d46",
    "status": "7"
  },
  {
    "id": "734",
    "question": "\u0d06\u0d2b\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4d \u0d06\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d2e\u0d46\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d2f \u0d2f\u0d42\u0d31\u0d4b\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d4d \u0d06\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d ?",
    "answer": "\u0d2a\u0d4b\u0d30\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d41\u0d17\u0d40\u0d38\u0d41\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d4d",
    "status": "7"
  },
  {
    "id": "735",
    "question": "\u0d1c\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d2a\u0d41\u0d37\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d3e\u0d32\u0d02\u0d15\u0d43\u0d24 \u0d30\u0d40\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4d \u0d2a\u0d31\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d2a\u0d47\u0d30\u0d4d ? ",
    "answer": "\u0d07\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d2c\u0d3e\u0d28",
    "status": "7"
  },
  {
    "id": "736",
    "question": "\u0d38\u0d30\u0d4d\u0d35\u0d4d\u0d35\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d1c\u0d4d\u0d2f \u0d38\u0d16\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d02 \u0d30\u0d42\u0d2a\u0d40\u0d15\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4d \u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d27\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d2a\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4d \u0d35\u0d39\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a \u0d05\u0d2e\u0d47\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d28\u0d4d \u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d38\u0d3f\u0d21\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d ? ",
    "answer": "\u0d35\u0d41\u0d21\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d4b \u0d35\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d38\u0d23\u0d4d\u200d",
    "status": "7"
  },
  {
    "id": "737",
    "question": "\u0d12\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d4b\u0d2c\u0d30\u0d4d \u0d35\u0d3f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d32\u0d35\u0d02 \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d41 \u0d35\u0d3f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d32\u0d35\u0d35\u0d41\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d3f \u0d2c\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d27\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d46\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d3f\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d41 ? ",
    "answer": "\u0d31\u0d37\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d28\u0d4d\u200d \u0d35\u0d3f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d32\u0d35\u0d02",
    "status": "7"
  },
  {
    "id": "738",
    "question": " \u0d2e\u0d28\u0d41\u0d37\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d28\u0d4d \u0d15\u0d43\u0d37\u0d3f \u0d06\u0d30\u0d02\u0d2d\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a \u0d15\u0d3e\u0d32\u0d18\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d02 ? ",
    "answer": "\u0d28\u0d35\u0d40\u0d28 \u0d36\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d17\u0d02",
    "status": "7"
  },
  {
    "id": "739",
    "question": "\u0d1a\u0d41\u0d35\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d4d \u0d15\u0d3e\u0d35\u0d32\u0d4d \u0d38\u0d47\u0d28 \u0d06\u0d30\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d38\u0d48\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d2f \u0d38\u0d02\u0d18\u0d1f\u0d28\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d ?",
    "answer": "\u0d32\u0d46\u0d28\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d",
    "status": "7"
  },
  {
    "id": "740",
    "question": "\u201c\u0d39\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d38\u0d4d \u201d \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d41 \u0d30\u0d3e\u0d1c\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d46 \u0d24\u0d40\u0d35\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d35\u0d3e\u0d26\u0d3f \u0d38\u0d02\u0d18\u0d1f\u0d28\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d ?",
    "answer": "\u0d2a\u0d3e\u0d32\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d40\u0d7b",
    "status": "7"
  },
  {
    "id": "741",
    "question": "\u0d07\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f \u0d15\u0d34\u0d3f\u0d1e\u0d4d\u0d1e\u0d3e\u0d32\u0d4d \u0d07\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d28\u0d4d \u0d35\u0d02\u0d36\u0d1c\u0d30\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4d \u0d2d\u0d42\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d2a\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d37\u0d2e\u0d41\u0d33\u0d4d\u0d33 \u0d32\u0d4b\u0d15\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d0f\u0d15 \u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d32\u0d02 ?",
    "answer": "\u0d2b\u0d3f\u0d1c\u0d3f",
    "status": "7"
  },
  {
    "id": "742",
    "question": "\u0d15\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d42\u0d23\u0d3f\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d \u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d3f\u0d2b\u0d46\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4b \u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d38\u0d3f\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d27\u0d40\u0d15\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a \u0d35\u0d30\u0d4d\u0d37\u0d02 ?",
    "answer": "1848",
    "status": "7"
  },
  {
    "id": "743",
    "question": "\u0d2e\u0d57 \u0d2e\u0d57 \u0d32\u0d39\u0d33 \u0d28\u0d1f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d06\u0d2b\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d28\u0d4d \u0d30\u0d3e\u0d1c\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d02 ? ",
    "answer": "\u0d15\u0d46\u0d28\u0d3f\u0d2f",
    "status": "7"
  },
  {
    "id": "744",
    "question": "\u0d17\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d47\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d \u0d07\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d7b\u0d38\u0d3f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d47\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d7c \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d05\u0d2a\u0d30\u0d28\u0d3e\u0d2e\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d7d \u0d05\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d46\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d24\u0d4d ?",
    "answer": "\u0d05\u0d2c\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d39\u0d3e\u0d02 \u0d32\u0d3f\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d28\u0d4d\u200d",
    "status": "7"
  },
  {
    "id": "745",
    "question": "\u0d05\u0d2e\u0d47\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d06\u0d26\u0d3f\u0d2e \u0d28\u0d3f\u0d35\u0d3e\u0d38\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d33\u0d46 \u0d31\u0d46\u0d21\u0d4d \u0d07\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d38\u0d4d \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d3e\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d02 \u0d35\u0d3f\u0d33\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d06\u0d30\u0d4d ?",
    "answer": "\u0d15\u0d4a\u0d33\u0d02\u0d2c\u0d38\u0d4d",
    "status": "7"
  },
  {
    "id": "746",
    "question": "\u0d2b\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d42\u0d21\u0d7d \u0d35\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d35\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25 \u0d06\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d3f \u0d28\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4d \u0d35\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d2d\u0d42\u0d16\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d21\u0d02 ?",
    "answer": "\u0d2f\u0d42\u0d31\u0d4b\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d4d",
    "status": "7"
  },
  {
    "id": "747",
    "question": "\u201d \u0d2c\u0d4d\u0d32\u0d42 \u0d2c\u0d41\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4d \u201d \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d3e\u0d32\u0d46\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d ? ",
    "answer": "\u0d2c\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d40\u0d37\u0d4d \u0d38\u0d30\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d14\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d4b\u0d17\u0d3f\u0d15 \u0d31\u0d3f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d4b\u0d30\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d4d",
    "status": "7"
  },
  {
    "id": "748",
    "question": "\u0d30\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d3e\u0d02 \u0d32\u0d4b\u0d15 \u0d2e\u0d39\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d27\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d41 \u0d06\u0d30\u0d02\u0d2d\u0d02 \u0d15\u0d41\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a \u0d38\u0d02\u0d2d\u0d35\u0d02 ? ",
    "answer": "\u0d1c\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d28\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d2a\u0d4b\u0d33\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d4d \u0d06\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d2e\u0d23\u0d02",
    "status": "7"
  },
  {
    "id": "749",
    "question": "\u0d2c\u0d46\u0d30\u0d4d\u0d32\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d \u0d2e\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4d \u0d2a\u0d42\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d\u0d23\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d2a\u0d4a\u0d33\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d41 \u0d28\u0d40\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3f\u0d2f \u0d35\u0d30\u0d4d\u0d37\u0d02 ? ",
    "answer": "1991",
    "status": "7"
  },
  {
    "id": "750",
    "question": "\u0d15\u0d41\u0d35\u0d48\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d46 \u0d07\u0d31\u0d3e\u0d16\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4d \u0d28\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d2e\u0d4b\u0d1a\u0d3f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d4d \u0d05\u0d2e\u0d47\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15 \u0d28\u0d1f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d2f \u0d38\u0d48\u0d28\u0d3f\u0d15 \u0d28\u0d1f\u0d2a\u0d1f\u0d3f ? ",
    "answer": "\u0d13\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d31\u0d46\u0d37\u0d28\u0d4d \u0d21\u0d38\u0d30\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d4d \u0d38\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4b\u0d02",
    "status": "7"
  },
  {
    "id": "751",
    "question": "\u0d12\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d3e\u0d02 \u0d32\u0d4b\u0d15 \u0d2e\u0d39\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d27\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d38\u0d48\u0d28\u0d3f\u0d15 \u0d1a\u0d47\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d2f \u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d37\u0d3f \u0d38\u0d4c\u0d39\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d4d\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d26\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4d \u0d09\u0d33\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d46\u0d1f\u0d3e\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24 \u0d30\u0d3e\u0d1c\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d02 ?",
    "answer": "\u0d1c\u0d30\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d28\u0d3f",
    "status": "7"
  },
  {
    "id": "752",
    "question": "\u0d07\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d1a\u0d48\u0d28\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d2a\u0d1e\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d36\u0d40\u0d32 \u0d24\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d35\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d19\u0d33\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4d \u0d12\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d4d \u0d35\u0d46\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a \u0d35\u0d30\u0d4d\u0d37\u0d02 ? ",
    "answer": "1954",
    "status": "7"
  },
  {
    "id": "753",
    "question": "\u0d06\u0d2b\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d15\u0d4b\u0d33\u0d28\u0d3f \u0d35\u0d3f\u0d30\u0d41\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d27 \u0d2f\u0d41\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d27\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d28\u0d47\u0d24\u0d43 \u0d30\u0d3e\u0d1c\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d3f \u0d05\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d46\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d24\u0d4d ? ",
    "answer": "\u0d18\u0d3e\u0d28\r\n",
    "status": "7"
  },
  {
    "id": "754",
    "question": "\u201c\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d27\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d3f\u0d27\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d2e\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4d\u0d32\u0d3e\u0d24\u0d46 \u0d28\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d41\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4d\u0d32 \u201d \u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d38\u0d3f\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d27\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d2f \u0d08 \u0d2e\u0d41\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d35\u0d3e\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d02 \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d41 \u0d35\u0d3f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d32\u0d35\u0d35\u0d41\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d3f \u0d2c\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d27\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d46\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d .?",
    "answer": "\u0d05\u0d2e\u0d47\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d28\u0d4d \u0d35\u0d3f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d32\u0d35\u0d02",
    "status": "7"
  },
  {
    "id": "755",
    "question": "\u201d \u0d15\u0d43\u0d37\u0d3f \u0d2d\u0d42\u0d2e\u0d3f \u0d15\u0d30\u0d4d\u0d37\u0d15\u0d28\u0d4d , \u0d2a\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d3f\u0d23\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4d \u0d2d\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d37\u0d23\u0d02 , \u0d05\u0d27\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d02 \u0d24\u0d4a\u0d34\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d3e\u0d33\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d33\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4d , \u0d0e\u0d32\u0d4d\u0d32\u0d3e\u0d35\u0d30\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d38\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d27\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d02 \u201d \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d41 \u0d35\u0d3f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d32\u0d35\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d2e\u0d41\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d35\u0d3e\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d30\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d41 ?",
    "answer": "\u0d31\u0d37\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d28\u0d4d\u200d \u0d35\u0d3f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d32\u0d35\u0d02\r\n",
    "status": "7"
  },
  {
    "id": "756",
    "question": "\u0d05\u0d31\u0d2c\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d33\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d06\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f \u0d07\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d3e \u0d06\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d2e\u0d23\u0d02 \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d41 ? ",
    "answer": "AD 712",
    "status": "7"
  },
  {
    "id": "757",
    "question": "\u0d2c\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d32\u0d4b\u0d2e\u0d3f\u0d2f \u0d21\u0d2f\u0d38\u0d4d \u0d36\u0d41\u0d2d \u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d24\u0d40\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d37\u0d3e\u0d2e\u0d41\u0d28\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4d \u0d0e\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d47\u0d30\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d35\u0d30\u0d4d\u0d37\u0d02 ?",
    "answer": "1488",
    "status": "7"
  },
  {
    "id": "758",
    "question": "\u0d0f\u0d37\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4d \u0d06\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d3f \u0d2c\u0d48\u0d2c\u0d3f\u0d33\u0d4d \u0d05\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d1f\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d46\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f \u0d2d\u0d3e\u0d37 ?",
    "answer": "\u0d24\u0d2e\u0d3f\u0d34\u0d4d",
    "status": "7"
  },
  {
    "id": "759",
    "question": "\u201d \u0d35\u0d3f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d32\u0d35\u0d02 \u0d24\u0d4b\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d \u0d15\u0d41\u0d34\u0d32\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d42\u0d1f\u0d46 \u201d \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d38\u0d3f\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d27\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d2f \u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d35\u0d28 \u0d06\u0d30\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d ?",
    "answer": "\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d35\u0d4b \u0d38\u0d46 \u0d24\u0d42\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d19\u0d4d",
    "status": "7"
  },
  {
    "id": "760",
    "question": "\u0d07\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d2f\u0d47\u0d32\u0d4d \u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d3e\u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d2f \u0d35\u0d30\u0d4d\u0d37\u0d02 ?",
    "answer": "1948",
    "status": "7"
  },
  {
    "id": "761",
    "question": "\u0d17\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d40\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4d \u0d26\u0d41\u0d30\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24 \u0d28\u0d3e\u0d1f\u0d15\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d19\u0d33\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d35\u0d4d \u0d06\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d ? ",
    "answer": "\u0d06\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d38\u0d4d",
    "status": "7"
  },
  {
    "id": "762",
    "question": "1863 \u0d05\u0d2e\u0d47\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4d \u0d05\u0d1f\u0d3f\u0d2e\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d02 \u0d28\u0d3f\u0d30\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d32\u0d3e\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d06\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d ? ",
    "answer": "\u0d05\u0d2c\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d39\u0d3e\u0d02 \u0d32\u0d3f\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d28\u0d4d",
    "status": "7"
  },
  {
    "id": "763",
    "question": "\u0d0e\u0d34\u0d41\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d35\u0d3f\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f \u0d35\u0d36\u0d2e\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4d\u0d32\u0d3e\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d30\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d1a\u0d40\u0d28 \u0d05\u0d2e\u0d47\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d28\u0d4d \u0d38\u0d02\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d02 ?",
    "answer": "\u0d07\u0d7b\u0d15",
    "status": "7"
  },
  {
    "id": "764",
    "question": "\u0d07\u0d02\u0d17\u0d4d\u0d32\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4d \u0d06\u0d2d\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d30 \u0d2f\u0d41\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d27\u0d02 \u0d06\u0d30\u0d02\u0d2d\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a \u0d35\u0d30\u0d4d\u0d37\u0d02 ?",
    "answer": "AD 1642",
    "status": "7"
  },
  {
    "id": "765",
    "question": "\u0d05\u0d2e\u0d47\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d28\u0d4d \u0d38\u0d4d\u0d35\u0d3e\u0d24\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d4d\u0d2f \u0d38\u0d2e\u0d30\u0d02 \u0d28\u0d1f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d35\u0d30\u0d4d\u0d37\u0d02 ? ",
    "answer": "AD 1776",
    "status": "7"
  },
  {
    "id": "766",
    "question": "\u0d08\u0d1c\u0d3f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d38\u0d3f\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d1a\u0d47\u0d30\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d41\u0d33\u0d4d\u0d33 \u0d2f\u0d41\u0d28\u0d48\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d21\u0d4d \u0d05\u0d31\u0d2c\u0d4d \u0d31\u0d3f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d2c\u0d4d\u0d32\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d \u0d28\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4d \u0d35\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d35\u0d30\u0d4d\u0d37\u0d02 ?",
    "answer": "1958",
    "status": "7"
  },
  {
    "id": "767",
    "question": "\u0d1a\u0d48\u0d28\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d7d \u0d38\u0d3e\u0d02\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d15 \u0d35\u0d3f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d32\u0d35\u0d02 \u0d28\u0d1f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d35\u0d7c\u0d37\u0d02 ? ",
    "answer": "1966",
    "status": "7"
  },
  {
    "id": "768",
    "question": "\u0d2b\u0d3e\u0d38\u0d3f\u0d38\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d09\u0d2a\u0d1c\u0d4d\u0d1e\u0d3e\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d35\u0d4d ?",
    "answer": "\u0d2e\u0d41\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d38\u0d4b\u0d33\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d3f",
    "status": "7"
  },
  {
    "id": "769",
    "question": "\u0d30\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d30\u0d39\u0d3f\u0d24 \u0d35\u0d3f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d32\u0d35\u0d02 \u0d28\u0d1f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d35\u0d7c\u0d37\u0d02 ?",
    "answer": "1688",
    "status": "7"
  },
  {
    "id": "770",
    "question": "\u0d2e\u0d41\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f \u0d2c\u0d3e\u0d39\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d3f \u201d \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d41 \u0d30\u0d3e\u0d1c\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d38\u0d4d\u0d35\u0d3e\u0d24\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d41 \u0d35\u0d47\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d3f \u0d2a\u0d4b\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d1f\u0d3f\u0d2f \u0d38\u0d02\u0d18\u0d1f\u0d28\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d ? ",
    "answer": "\u0d2c\u0d02\u0d17\u0d4d\u0d32\u0d3e\u0d26\u0d47\u0d36\u0d4d",
    "status": "7"
  },
  {
    "id": "771",
    "question": "\u0d1c\u0d30\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d28\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d09\u0d30\u0d41\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4d \u0d2e\u0d28\u0d41\u0d37\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d28\u0d4d \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d46\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d06\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d ? ",
    "answer": "\u0d2c\u0d3f\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4d",
    "status": "7"
  },
  {
    "id": "772",
    "question": "\u0d07\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d3e\u0d32\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d28\u0d4d \u0d26\u0d47\u0d36\u0d40\u0d2f\u0d24\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d35\u0d4d \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d46\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d06\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d ? ",
    "answer": "\u0d1c\u0d4b\u0d38\u0d2b\u0d4d \u0d2e\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d38\u0d40\u0d28\u0d3f",
    "status": "7"
  },
  {
    "id": "773",
    "question": "\u0d26\u0d36\u0d3e\u0d02\u0d36 \u0d38\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d26\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d02 \u0d15\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d41 \u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d1f\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d4d ?",
    "answer": "\u0d08\u0d1c\u0d3f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d4d\r\n",
    "status": "7"
  },
  {
    "id": "774",
    "question": "\u0d06\u0d27\u0d41\u0d28\u0d3f\u0d15 \u0d15\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4b \u0d2f\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4d \u0d38\u0d2e\u0d40\u0d2a\u0d02 \u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d3f \u0d1a\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d2e\u0d39\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d2f \u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d30\u0d2e\u0d3f\u0d21\u0d4d \u0d2a\u0d23\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d34\u0d3f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d06\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d ? ",
    "answer": "\u0d16\u0d41\u0d2b\u0d41",
    "status": "7"
  },
  {
    "id": "775",
    "question": "\u0d06\u0d27\u0d41\u0d28\u0d3f\u0d15 \u0d31\u0d37\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d35\u0d4d \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d46\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d06\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d ? ",
    "answer": "\u0d2a\u0d40\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d \u0d1a\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d35\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f",
    "status": "7"
  },
  {
    "id": "776",
    "question": "\u0d08\u0d1c\u0d3f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d30\u0d3e\u0d1c\u0d3e\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d4d \u0d05\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d46\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d3f\u0d30\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d2a\u0d47\u0d30\u0d4d ? ",
    "answer": "\u0d2b\u0d31\u0d35\u0d4b",
    "status": "7"
  },
  {
    "id": "777",
    "question": "\u0d24\u0d40\u0d30\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d3e\u0d1f\u0d15\u0d30\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d30\u0d3e\u0d1c\u0d15\u0d41\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d28\u0d4d \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d46\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d06\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d ? ",
    "answer": "\u0d39\u0d41\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d4d \u0d38\u0d3e\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d19\u0d4d",
    "status": "7"
  },
  {
    "id": "778",
    "question": "\u0d38\u0d57\u0d30 \u0d2a\u0d1e\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d3e\u0d02\u0d17\u0d02 \u0d15\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d41 \u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d1f\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d4d ?",
    "answer": "\u0d08\u0d1c\u0d3f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d41\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d4d\r\n",
    "status": "7"
  },
  {
    "id": "779",
    "question": "\u0d32\u0d4b\u0d15\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d0f\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d35\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d15\u0d42\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d24\u0d32\u0d4d \u0d1c\u0d28\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d19\u0d33\u0d4d \u0d38\u0d02\u0d38\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d2d\u0d3e\u0d37 ? ",
    "answer": "\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d21\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d",
    "status": "7"
  },
  {
    "id": "780",
    "question": "\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d32\u0d35\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d19\u0d33\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d35\u0d4d ? ",
    "answer": "\u0d2b\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d1e\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d4d \u0d35\u0d3f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d32\u0d35\u0d02",
    "status": "7"
  },
  {
    "id": "781",
    "question": "\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d42\u0d23\u0d3f\u0d2b\u0d4b\u0d02 \u0d32\u0d3f\u0d2a\u0d3f \u0d06\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d3f \u0d09\u0d2a\u0d2f\u0d4b\u0d17\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d06\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d ? ",
    "answer": "\u0d38\u0d41\u0d2e\u0d47\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d4d",
    "status": "7"
  },
  {
    "id": "782",
    "question": "\u0d28\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d30\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d32\u0d4d \u0d2e\u0d28\u0d41\u0d37\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d30\u0d4d \u0d1c\u0d40\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d3f\u0d30\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d3f \u0d15\u0d23\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d30\u0d3e\u0d1c\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d02 ?",
    "answer": "\u0d1c\u0d30\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d28\u0d3f",
    "status": "7"
  },
  {
    "id": "783",
    "question": "\u0d2c\u0d4b\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d7a \u0d1f\u0d40 \u0d2a\u0d3e\u0d7c\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d3f \u0d28\u0d1f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d35\u0d7c\u0d37\u0d02 ? ",
    "answer": "AD 1773",
    "status": "7"
  },
  {
    "id": "784",
    "question": "\u0d1a\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d2a\u0d1e\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d3e\u0d02\u0d17\u0d02 \u0d15\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d41 \u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d1f\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d4d ? ",
    "answer": "\u0d38\u0d41\u0d2e\u0d47\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d4d",
    "status": "7"
  },
  {
    "id": "785",
    "question": "\u0d2e\u0d24\u0d28\u0d35\u0d40\u0d15\u0d30\u0d23 \u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d35\u0d4d ? ",
    "answer": "\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d \u0d32\u0d42\u0d24\u0d30\u0d4d",
    "status": "7"
  },
  {
    "id": "786",
    "question": "\u201d\u0d36\u0d3e\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d19\u0d33\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d31\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d3f \u201d \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d46\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d24\u0d4d ?",
    "answer": "\u0d17\u0d23\u0d3f\u0d24 \u0d36\u0d3e\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d02",
    "status": "7"
  },
  {
    "id": "787",
    "question": "\u0d2e\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d4d\u0d21\u0d4d \u0d13\u0d2b\u0d4d \u0d13\u0d7c\u0d33\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d7b\u0d38\u0d4d \u2013 \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d2a\u0d46\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d4d ?",
    "answer": "\u0d1c\u0d4b\u0d35\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d4d \u0d13\u0d2b\u0d4d \u0d06\u0d30\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4d",
    "status": "7"
  },
  {
    "id": "788",
    "question": "\u0d1f\u0d46\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d40\u0d38\u0d4d \u0d15\u0d4b\u0d7c\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d4d \u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d1c\u0d4d\u0d1e \u0d28\u0d1f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d35\u0d7c\u0d37\u0d02 ?",
    "answer": "1789",
    "status": "7"
  },
  {
    "id": "789",
    "question": "\u0d1a\u0d48\u0d28\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d2c\u0d41\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d27\u0d7b \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d46\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f \u0d35\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f ?",
    "answer": "\u0d32\u0d35\u0d4b\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d38\u0d46",
    "status": "7"
  },
  {
    "id": "790",
    "question": "\u0d2b\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d1e\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d4d \u0d35\u0d3f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d32\u0d35\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d35\u0d4d \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d46\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d06\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d ? ",
    "answer": "\u0d35\u0d4b\u0d33\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d2f\u0d30\u0d4d",
    "status": "7"
  },
  {
    "id": "791",
    "question": "\u201c\u0d2e\u0d28\u0d41\u0d37\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d28\u0d4d \u0d38\u0d4d\u0d35\u0d24\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d28\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d \u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d31\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d24\u0d4d . \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d3e\u0d32\u0d4d \u0d05\u0d35\u0d28\u0d4d \u0d0e\u0d32\u0d4d\u0d32\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d1f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d1a\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d19\u0d32\u0d15\u0d33\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d\u201d \u2013 \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d4d \u0d2a\u0d31\u0d1e\u0d4d\u0d1e\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d4d ?",
    "answer": "\u0d31\u0d42\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d38\u0d4b",
    "status": "7"
  },
  {
    "id": "792",
    "question": "\u0d2b\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d1e\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d4d \u0d35\u0d3f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d32\u0d35\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d36\u0d3f\u0d36\u0d41 ? ",
    "answer": "\u0d28\u0d46\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d4b\u0d33\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d28\u0d4d",
    "status": "7"
  },
  {
    "id": "793",
    "question": "\u0d05\u0d2e\u0d47\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d38\u0d4b\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d \u0d2f\u0d42\u0d23\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d07\u0d1f\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4d \u0d30\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d3e\u0d02 \u0d32\u0d4b\u0d15 \u0d2e\u0d39\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d27\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d30\u0d02 \u0d28\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d28\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d3f\u0d30\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d24\u0d40\u0d35\u0d4d\u0d30 \u0d35\u0d48\u0d30\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d02 \u0d05\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d46\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d24\u0d4d ?",
    "answer": "\u0d15\u0d4b\u0d33\u0d4d\u200d\u0d21\u0d4d \u0d35\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d",
    "status": "7"
  },
  {
    "id": "794",
    "question": "\u0d2d\u0d42\u0d2e\u0d3f \u0d09\u0d30\u0d41\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d46\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d4d \u0d24\u0d46\u0d33\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a \u0d2a\u0d4b\u0d7c\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d41\u0d17\u0d40\u0d38\u0d4d \u0d28\u0d3e\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d7b ?",
    "answer": "\u0d2e\u0d17\u0d32\u0d4d\u0d32\u0d28\u0d4d",
    "status": "7"
  },
  {
    "id": "795",
    "question": "\u0d38\u0d1e\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d38\u0d7c\u0d35\u0d4d\u0d35\u0d15\u0d32\u0d3e\u0d36\u0d3e\u0d32 \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d46\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f \u0d35\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f ?",
    "answer": "\u0d05\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4b\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4d",
    "status": "7"
  },
  {
    "id": "796",
    "question": "\u0d28\u0d35\u0d4b\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d2d\u0d3e\u0d24 \u0d28\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d37\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d02 ?",
    "answer": "\u0d26\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d46",
    "status": "7"
  },
  {
    "id": "797",
    "question": "\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d2c\u0d4d\u0d32\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d06\u0d36\u0d2f\u0d02 \u0d32\u0d4b\u0d15\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d \u0d38\u0d02\u0d2d\u0d3e\u0d35\u0d28 \u0d1a\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d30\u0d3e\u0d1c\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d ?",
    "answer": "\u0d31\u0d4b\u0d02",
    "status": "7"
  },
  {
    "id": "798",
    "question": "\u2018\u0d26\u0d3f \u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d7b\u0d38\u0d4d\u2019 \u0d0e\u0d34\u0d41\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d ?",
    "answer": "\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d35\u0d32\u0d4d\u0d32\u0d3f",
    "status": "7"
  },
  {
    "id": "799",
    "question": "\u0d2b\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d1e\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d4d \u0d35\u0d3f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d32\u0d35\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d35\u0d3e\u0d1a\u0d15\u0d7b ?",
    "answer": "\u0d31\u0d42\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d38\u0d4b",
    "status": "7"
  },
  {
    "id": "800",
    "question": "\u0d2e\u0d4b\u0d23\u0d4b\u0d32\u0d3f\u0d38 \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d1a\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d38\u0d43\u0d37\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d3e\u0d35\u0d4d ?",
    "answer": "\u0d32\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d4d\u0d21\u0d4b \u0d21\u0d3e\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d1e\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d3f",
    "status": "7"
  },
  {
    "id": "801",
    "question": "\u0d32\u0d4b\u0d15\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d47\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d35\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d15\u0d42\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d24\u0d7d \u0d2e\u0d41\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d33\u0d40\u0d02\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d19\u0d7e \u0d09\u0d33\u0d4d\u0d33 \u0d30\u0d3e\u0d1c\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d02 ?",
    "answer": "\u0d07\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4b\u0d28\u0d47\u0d37\u0d4d\u0d2f",
    "status": "7"
  },
  {
    "id": "802",
    "question": "\u0d31\u0d37\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d3e\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d3f \u0d2a\u0d1e\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d35\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d38\u0d30 \u0d2a\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d27\u0d24\u0d3f \u0d28\u0d1f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d3e\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d4d ?",
    "answer": "\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d3e\u0d32\u0d3f",
    "status": "7"
  },
  {
    "id": "803",
    "question": "\u0d39\u0d4b\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d4d \u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d7b \u0d15\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d4d \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d4d\r\n \u0d15\u0d33\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d3f \u0d2c\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d27\u0d2a\u0d46\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d3f\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d41.?",
    "answer": "\u0d1f\u0d46\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d3f\u0d38\u0d4d",
    "status": "6"
  },
  {
    "id": "804",
    "question": "\u0d15\u0d47\u0d30\u0d33 \u0d2c\u0d4d\u0d32\u0d3e\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d47\u0d34\u0d4d\u0d38\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d08 \u0d15\u0d34\u0d3f\u0d1e\u0d4d\u0d1e ISL \u0d7d \u0d06\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d02.\u0d1f\u0d40\u0d02 \u0d2e\u0d3f\u0d7d \u0d17\u0d4b\u0d7d \u0d28\u0d47\u0d1f\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d06\u0d30\u0d4d?",
    "answer": "\u0d2e\u0d48\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3f\u0d7d \u0d1a\u0d4b\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d31",
    "status": "6"
  },
  {
    "id": "805",
    "question": "\u0d12\u0d33\u0d3f\u0d02\u0d2c\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d38\u0d4d \u0d26\u0d40\u0d2a\u0d02 \u0d06\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d02 \u0d24\u0d46\u0d33\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a \u0d35\u0d7c\u0d37\u0d02 ?",
    "answer": "1928",
    "status": "6"
  },
  {
    "id": "806",
    "question": "I0C ( \u0d07\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d7c \u0d28\u0d3e\u0d37\u0d23\u0d7d \u0d12\u0d33\u0d3f \u0d2c\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d \u0d15\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d3f\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d3f ) \u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d38\u0d3f\u0d21\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d15\u0d3e\u0d32\u0d3e\u0d35\u0d27\u0d3f ?",
    "answer": "8 \u0d35\u0d7c\u0d37\u0d02",
    "status": "6"
  },
  {
    "id": "807",
    "question": "\u0d06\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d3f \u0d2f\u0d42\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d12\u0d33\u0d3f\u0d02\u0d2c\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d38\u0d4d \u0d28\u0d1f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d35\u0d7c\u0d37\u0d02 ?",
    "answer": "2010 Singapore",
    "status": "6"
  },
  {
    "id": "808",
    "question": "\u0d15\u0d4b\u0d2e\u0d7a \u0d35\u0d46\u0d7d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d17\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d02\u0d38\u0d4d \u0d7d \u0d2e\u0d46\u0d21\u0d7d \u0d28\u0d47\u0d1f\u0d3f\u0d2f \u0d2b\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d \u0d2e\u0d32\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d33\u0d3f ?",
    "answer": "\u0d38\u0d41\u0d30\u0d47\u0d37\u0d4d \u0d2c\u0d3e\u0d2c\u0d41\r\n",
    "status": "6"
  },
  {
    "id": "809",
    "question": "\u0d0e\u0d37\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d7b \u0d17\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d02\u0d38\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d1a\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d06\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f \u0d30\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d24 \u0d38\u0d3e\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d37\u0d3f ?",
    "answer": "Kim Hwayang Chill(2006)",
    "status": "6"
  },
  {
    "id": "810",
    "question": "\u0d32\u0d4b\u0d15\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d0f\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d35\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d05\u0d27\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d02 \u0d30\u0d3e\u0d1c\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d19\u0d33\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d26\u0d47\u0d36\u0d3f\u0d2f \u0d15\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d15 \u0d35\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4b\u0d26\u0d02 ?",
    "answer": "\u0d2b\u0d41\u0d21\u0d4d \u0d2c\u0d3e\u0d7e",
    "status": "6"
  },
  {
    "id": "811",
    "question": "\u0d07\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d7b \u0d15\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d \u0d1f\u0d40\u0d02 \u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d06\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f \u0d2a\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d36\u0d40\u0d32\u0d15\u0d7b ?",
    "answer": "John right\r\n",
    "status": "6"
  },
  {
    "id": "812",
    "question": "Sudden death \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d41\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d3f \u0d2c\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d27\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d46\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d3f\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d41 ?",
    "answer": "\u0d2b\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d4d \u0d2c\u0d3e\u0d7e\r\n",
    "status": "6"
  },
  {
    "id": "813",
    "question": "\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d \u0d09\u0d1f\u0d32\u0d46\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24 \u0d30\u0d3e\u0d1c\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d02 ?",
    "answer": "\u0d07\u0d02\u0d17\u0d4d\u0d32\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d4d",
    "status": "6"
  },
  {
    "id": "814",
    "question": "\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d32\u0d3e\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4d \u0d17\u0d46\u0d7d \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d2a\u0d46\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d24\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d02 ?",
    "answer": "Nadiya komanechi\r\n",
    "status": "6"
  },
  {
    "id": "815",
    "question": "\u0d12\u0d33\u0d3f\u0d02\u0d2c\u0d3f\u0d02\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d38\u0d4d \u0d7d \u0d2b\u0d48\u0d28\u0d7d \u0d0e\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d2f \u0d06\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f \u0d07\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d7b \u0d35\u0d28\u0d3f\u0d24 ?",
    "answer": "\u0d2a\u0d3f.\u0d1f\u0d3f \u0d09\u0d37",
    "status": "6"
  },
  {
    "id": "816",
    "question": "\u0d35\u0d28\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d15\u0d7e \u0d06\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d3f \u0d2a\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d46\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24 \u0d12\u0d33\u0d3f\u0d02\u0d2c\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d38\u0d4d ?",
    "answer": "1900- \u0d2a\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d38\u0d4d\r\n",
    "status": "6"
  },
  {
    "id": "817",
    "question": "\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d4b\u0d7c\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d38\u0d4d \u0d15\u0d33\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d30\u0d3e\u0d1c\u0d3e\u0d35\u0d4d \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d46\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d38\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d4b\u0d7c\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d38\u0d4d ?",
    "answer": "\u0d39\u0d4b\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3f\r\n",
    "status": "6"
  },
  {
    "id": "818",
    "question": "\u0d32\u0d4b\u0d15\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d0f\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d35\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d35\u0d32\u0d3f\u0d2f \u0d39\u0d4b\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3f \u0d2e\u0d47\u0d33 \u0d28\u0d1f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d32\u0d02 ?",
    "answer": "\u0d15\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d15\u0d4d",
    "status": "6"
  },
  {
    "id": "819",
    "question": "\u0d32\u0d4b\u0d15\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d0f\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d35\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d35\u0d32\u0d3f\u0d2f \u0d15\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d \u0d38\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d47\u0d21\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d02 ?",
    "answer": "\u0d2e\u0d46\u0d7d\u0d2c\u0d7a",
    "status": "6"
  },
  {
    "id": "820",
    "question": "\u0d16\u0d47\u0d7d \u0d30\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d32\u0d2d\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a \u0d06\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d46 .\u0d2e\u0d32\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d33\u0d3f \u0d24\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d02 ?",
    "answer": "KM \u0d2c\u0d40\u0d28 \u0d2e\u0d4b\u0d7e",
    "status": "6"
  },
  {
    "id": "821",
    "question": "\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d2e\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15 \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d46\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d24\u0d4d ?",
    "answer": "\u0d32\u0d4b\u0d7c\u0d21\u0d4d",
    "status": "6"
  },
  {
    "id": "822",
    "question": " 2017 \u0d2b\u0d3f\u0d2b \u0d05\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d7c 17 \u0d32\u0d4b\u0d15\u0d15\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d4d \u0d2b\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d2c\u0d4b\u0d7e \u0d35\u0d47\u0d26\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d7d \u0d24\u0d3f\u0d30\u0d46\u0d1e\u0d4d\u0d1e\u0d46\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15 \u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d46\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d24\u0d4d ?",
    "answer": "\u0d15\u0d4a\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d3f",
    "status": "6"
  },
  {
    "id": "823",
    "question": "2016\u0d7d \u0d07\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d7d \u0d28\u0d1f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d15\u0d2c\u0d21\u0d3f \u0d32\u0d4b\u0d15\u0d15\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d7d \u0d35\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4d \u0d0f\u0d7c\u0d2a\u0d46\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d2f \u0d30\u0d3e\u0d1c\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d02 ?",
    "answer": "\u0d2a\u0d3e\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3f\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d3e\u0d7b",
    "status": "6"
  },
  {
    "id": "824",
    "question": "\u0d2a\u0d3f.\u0d1f\u0d3f \u0d09\u0d37\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4d \u0d36\u0d47\u0d37\u0d02 \u0d12\u0d33\u0d3f\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d38\u0d4d \u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d2b\u0d48\u0d28\u0d32\u0d3f\u0d7d \u0d0e\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d2f \u0d07\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d7b \u0d24\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d02 ?",
    "answer": "Lalita Babar",
    "status": "6"
  },
  {
    "id": "825",
    "question": " IAAF \u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d35\u0d47\u0d7e\u0d21\u0d4d \r\n\u0d05\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d32\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d \u0d13\u0d2b\u0d4d \u0d26\u0d3f \u0d07\u0d2f\u0d7c \u0d05\u0d35\u0d3e\u0d7c\u0d21\u0d4d 2016\u0d7d \u0d06\u0d7c\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d \u0d32\u0d2d\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d24\u0d4d ?",
    "answer": "\u0d09\u0d38\u0d48\u0d7b \u0d2c\u0d4b\u0d7e\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d4d",
    "status": "6"
  },
  {
    "id": "826",
    "question": "\u0d1f\u0d46\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d \u0d15\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d7d 10000 \u0d31\u0d7a\u0d38\u0d4d \u0d24\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a \u0d0f\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d35\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d02 \u0d15\u0d41\u0d31\u0d1e\u0d4d\u0d1e \u0d24\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d02 \u0d06\u0d30\u0d4d ?",
    "answer": "\u0d05\u0d32\u0d3f \u0d38\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d3e\u0d7c.\u0d15\u0d42\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4d",
    "status": "6"
  },
  {
    "id": "827",
    "question": " l AAF \u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d35\u0d47\u0d7e\u0d21\u0d4d \u0d05\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d32\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d \u0d13\u0d2b\u0d4d \u0d26\u0d3f \u0d07\u0d2f\u0d7c \u0d05\u0d35\u0d3e\u0d7c\u0d21\u0d4d \u0d2b\u0d40\u0d2e\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d7d \u0d15\u0d3e\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d17\u0d31\u0d3f 2016\u0d7d \u0d06\u0d7c\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d \u0d32\u0d2d\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d24\u0d4d ?",
    "answer": "\u0d0e\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d4b\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2f",
    "status": "6"
  },
  {
    "id": "828",
    "question": "\u0d09\u0d38\u0d48\u0d7b \u0d2c\u0d4b\u0d7e\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d \u0d35\u0d47\u0d7e\u0d21\u0d4d \u0d05\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d32\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d \u0d05\u0d35\u0d3e\u0d7c\u0d21\u0d4d \u0d0e\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d2e\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d46 \u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d36\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d \u0d32\u0d2d\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d24\u0d4d ?",
    "answer": "6",
    "status": "6"
  },
  {
    "id": "829",
    "question": "\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d7c \u0d12\u0d33\u0d3f\u0d2c\u0d3f\u0d17\u0d4d \u0d38\u0d4d \u0d28\u0d1f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d35\u0d7c\u0d37\u0d02 ?",
    "answer": "1924",
    "status": "6"
  },
  {
    "id": "830",
    "question": "\u0d31\u0d4b\u0d2e\u0d7b \u0d1a\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d35\u0d7c\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f Theodotius \u0d12\u0d33\u0d3f\u0d02\u0d2c\u0d3fo\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d38\u0d4d \u0d28\u0d3f\u0d30\u0d4b\u0d27\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d0e\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d4b\u0d7e ?",
    "answer": "AD 393",
    "status": "6"
  },
  {
    "id": "831",
    "question": "2011 \u0d07\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f \u0d15\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d \u0d35\u0d47\u0d7e\u0d21\u0d4d \u0d15\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d4d \u0d28\u0d47\u0d1f\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d4b\u0d7e. \u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d7b: \u0d13\u0d2b\u0d4d \u0d38\u0d3f\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d38\u0d4d \u0d06\u0d2f\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d06\u0d30\u0d4d ?",
    "answer": "\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d35\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d1c\u0d4d \u0d38\u0d3f\u0d02\u0d17\u0d4d",
    "status": "6"
  },
  {
    "id": "832",
    "question": "2010 \u0d15\u0d4b\u0d2e\u0d7a \u0d35\u0d46\u0d7d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d17\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d02\u0d38\u0d4d \u0d7d \u0d07\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d41 \u0d15\u0d3f\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d3f\u0d2f \u0d17\u0d4b\u0d7d\u0d21\u0d4d \u0d2e\u0d46\u0d21\u0d32\u0d41\u0d15\u0d33\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d0e\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d23\u0d02 ?",
    "answer": "38",
    "status": "6"
  },
  {
    "id": "833",
    "question": "\u0d39\u0d4b\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3f \u0d2f\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d09\u0d7d\u0d2d\u0d35\u0d02 \u0d0e\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d1f\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d ?\r\n",
    "answer": "\u0d2b\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d7b\u0d38\u0d4d\r\n",
    "status": "6"
  },
  {
    "id": "834",
    "question": "\u0d31\u0d38\u0d32\u0d3f\u0d02\u0d17\u0d4d \u0d28\u0d3e\u0d37\u0d23\u0d7d \u0d17\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d02 \u0d06\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d41\u0d33\u0d4d\u0d33 \u0d30\u0d3e\u0d1c\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d02 ?",
    "answer": "\u0d24\u0d41\u0d31\u0d41\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3f\r\n",
    "status": "6"
  },
  {
    "id": "835",
    "question": "\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d \u0d2c\u0d3e\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d \u0d28\u0d3f\u0d7c\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d24\u0d1f\u0d3f ?",
    "answer": "Willow wood",
    "status": "6"
  },
  {
    "id": "836",
    "question": "\u0d05\u0d2e\u0d47\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d0f\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d35\u0d41\u0d02 '\u0d2a\u0d4a\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d41\u0d32\u0d7c \u0d06\u0d2f \u0d17\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d02 ?",
    "answer": "\u0d2b\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d2c\u0d4b\u0d7e",
    "status": "6"
  },
  {
    "id": "837",
    "question": "\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d35\u0d7b\u0d15\u0d42\u0d7c \u0d15\u0d4a\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d3f \u0d15\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d46\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d \u0d05\u0d38\u0d4b\u0d38\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d47\u0d37\u0d7b \u0d24\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d19\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d06\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d ?",
    "answer": "GV \u0d30\u0d3e\u0d1c\u0d7b\r\n",
    "status": "6"
  },
  {
    "id": "838",
    "question": "KCA \u0d2f\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d07\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d4b\u0d34\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d46. \u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d38\u0d3f\u0d21\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d ?",
    "answer": "TC Mathew\r\n",
    "status": "6"
  },
  {
    "id": "839",
    "question": "\u0d35\u0d47\u0d7e\u0d21\u0d4d \u0d15\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d4d \u0d15\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d \u0d39\u0d48\u0d2f\u0d46\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d \u0d06\u0d35\u0d31\u0d47\u0d1c\u0d4d \u0d09\u0d33\u0d4d\u0d33 \u0d2c\u0d3e\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d7b ?",
    "answer": "V. V Richards",
    "status": "6"
  },
  {
    "id": "840",
    "question": "1900 \u0d12\u0d33\u0d3f\u0d02\u0d2c\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d38\u0d4d \u0d15\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d7d \u0d38\u0d3f\u0d7d\u0d35\u0d7c \u0d28\u0d47\u0d1f\u0d3f\u0d2f \u0d30\u0d3e\u0d1c\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d02 ?",
    "answer": "\u0d2b\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d7b\u0d38\u0d4d",
    "status": "6"
  },
  {
    "id": "841",
    "question": "KCA \u0d2f\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d39\u0d46\u0d21\u0d4d \u0d15\u0d4b\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d47\u0d34\u0d4d\u0d38\u0d4d \u0d0e\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d1f\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d ?",
    "answer": "\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d30\u0d41\u0d35\u0d28\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d2a\u0d41\u0d30\u0d02",
    "status": "6"
  },
  {
    "id": "842",
    "question": "\u0d15\u0d47\u0d30\u0d33\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d06\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f \u0d15\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d \u0d1f\u0d40\u0d02 \u0d0e\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d28\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d ?",
    "answer": "\u0d24\u0d32\u0d36\u0d4d\u0d36\u0d47\u0d30\u0d3f",
    "status": "6"
  },
  {
    "id": "843",
    "question": "ISL \u0d2b\u0d48\u0d28\u0d32\u0d3f\u0d7d \u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d7c \u0d13\u0d2b\u0d4d \u0d26\u0d3f \u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d4d \u0d06\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d30\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d41 ?",
    "answer": "\u0d2c\u0d46\u0d7d\u0d2b\u0d4b\u0d7c\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d4d",
    "status": "6"
  },
  {
    "id": "844",
    "question": "ISL \u0d1a\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d7c\u0d2a\u0d47\u0d34\u0d4d\u0d38\u0d7a \u0d06\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d ?",
    "answer": "\u0d28\u0d3f\u0d25\u0d3e \u0d05\u0d2c\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d3f",
    "status": "6"
  },
  {
    "id": "845",
    "question": "\u0d35\u0d4b\u0d33\u0d3f\u0d2c\u0d4b\u0d7e \u0d28\u0d3e\u0d37\u0d23\u0d7d \u0d17\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d02 \u0d06\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d33\u0d4d\u0d33 \u0d12\u0d30\u0d41 \u0d0f\u0d37\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d7b \u0d30\u0d3e\u0d1c\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d02 ?",
    "answer": "\u0d36\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d40\u0d32\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d15",
    "status": "6"
  },
  {
    "id": "846",
    "question": "\u0d12\u0d30\u0d41 Snooker \u0d2c\u0d4b\u0d7c\u0d21\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d2a\u0d4b\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d41\u0d15\u0d33\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d0e\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d23\u0d02 ?",
    "answer": "6",
    "status": "6"
  },
  {
    "id": "847",
    "question": "\u0d24\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d7c\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d3f 6 \u0d1f\u0d46\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d7d. \u0d38\u0d46\u0d1e\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d41\u0d31\u0d3f \u0d31\u0d46\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4b\u0d7c\u0d21\u0d4d \u0d09\u0d33\u0d4d\u0d33 \u0d2c\u0d3e\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d7b ?",
    "answer": "\u0d2c\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d21\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d7b",
    "status": "6"
  },
  {
    "id": "848",
    "question": "\u0d12\u0d30\u0d41 \u0d1a\u0d46\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d38\u0d4d \u0d2c\u0d4b\u0d7c\u0d21\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d2a\u0d1f\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d33\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d33\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d0e\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d23\u0d02 ?",
    "answer": "8",
    "status": "6"
  },
  {
    "id": "849",
    "question": "\u0d07\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d7d \u0d06\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d3f 20-20 \u0d35\u0d47\u0d7e\u0d21\u0d4d \u0d15\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d4d \u0d35\u0d3f\u0d1c\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a \u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d3f\u0d7d \u0d32\u0d3e\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d \u0d13\u0d35\u0d7c \u0d1a\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d06\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d ?",
    "answer": "Jogeendar sharma",
    "status": "6"
  },
  {
    "id": "850",
    "question": "\u0d32\u0d47\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d \u0d2b\u0d3f\u0d2b \u0d31\u0d3e\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3f\u0d7d \u0d07\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d02 ?",
    "answer": "97",
    "status": "6"
  },
  {
    "id": "851",
    "question": "2016 \u0d12\u0d33\u0d3f\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d38\u0d4d \u0d2e\u0d46\u0d21\u0d7d \u0d2a\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d7d \u0d07\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d02 ?",
    "answer": "67",
    "status": "6"
  },
  {
    "id": "852",
    "question": "\u0d1a\u0d46\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4b\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4d \u0d38\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d47\u0d21\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d02 \u0d0e\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d1f\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d ?",
    "answer": "\u0d1a\u0d46\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d48",
    "status": "6"
  },
  {
    "id": "853",
    "question": "\u0d07\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d7b \u0d2b\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d2c\u0d4b\u0d33\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d1e\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d46\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d7c ?\r\n",
    "answer": "\u0d05\u0d39\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d26\u0d3e\u0d2c\u0d3e\u0d26\u0d4d\r\n",
    "status": "6"
  },
  {
    "id": "854",
    "question": "\u0d0f\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d35\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d15\u0d42\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d24\u0d7d \u0d24\u0d35\u0d23 \u0d0e\u0d37\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d7b \u0d17\u0d46\u0d02 \u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d02\u0d38\u0d4d \u0d06\u0d25\u0d3f\u0d25\u0d47\u0d2f\u0d47\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d35\u0d02 \u0d35\u0d39\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a \u0d30\u0d3e\u0d1c\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d02 ?",
    "answer": "\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d\r\n",
    "status": "6"
  },
  {
    "id": "855",
    "question": "\u0d0f\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d35\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d15\u0d42\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d24\u0d7d \u0d17\u0d4b\u0d7d \u0d28\u0d47\u0d1f\u0d3f\u0d2f \u0d2e\u0d42\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d3e\u0d2e\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d46 \u0d07\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d7b \u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d7c ?",
    "answer": "I.M.Vijayan",
    "status": "6"
  },
  {
    "id": "856",
    "question": "\u0d15\u0d2c\u0d21\u0d3f .\u0d1f\u0d40\u0d02 \u0d2e\u0d3f\u0d7d \u0d0e\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30 \u0d15\u0d33\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d7c \u0d09\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d4d ?\r\n",
    "answer": "9",
    "status": "6"
  },
  {
    "id": "857",
    "question": "Polo \u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d7d \u0d0e\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30 \u0d15\u0d33\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d7c ?",
    "answer": "4",
    "status": "6"
  },
  {
    "id": "858",
    "question": "\u0d35\u0d3e\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d7c \u0d2a\u0d4b\u0d33\u0d4b\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d7d \u0d0e\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30 \u0d15\u0d33\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d7c ?",
    "answer": "7",
    "status": "6"
  },
  {
    "id": "859",
    "question": "\u0d35\u0d4b\u0d33\u0d3f' \u0d2c\u0d3e\u0d33\u0d3f\u0d7d \u0d0e\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30 \u0d15\u0d33\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d7c ?",
    "answer": "6",
    "status": "6"
  },
  {
    "id": "860",
    "question": "\u0d2e\u0d42\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d3e\u0d2e\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d46 cricket \u0d32\u0d4b\u0d15\u0d15\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d4d \u0d35\u0d3e\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d19\u0d3f\u0d2f \/ \u0d28\u0d47\u0d1f\u0d3f\u0d2f \u0d30\u0d3e\u0d1c\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d02 ?",
    "answer": "\u0d07\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f",
    "status": "6"
  },
  {
    "id": "861",
    "question": "2015 \u0d32\u0d4b\u0d15\u0d15\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d4d \u0d15\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d \u0d2f\u0d41 \u0d0e \u0d07 \u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d41 \u0d35\u0d47\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d3f \u0d15\u0d33\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a \u0d2e\u0d32\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d33\u0d3f ?",
    "answer": "\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d37\u0d4d\u0d23 \u0d1a\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d7b\r\n",
    "status": "6"
  },
  {
    "id": "862",
    "question": "\u0d38\u0d1a\u0d3f\u0d7b \u0d1f\u0d46\u0d7b\u0d21\u0d41\u0d7d\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d7c \u0d28\u0d46 \u0d2a\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d3f \u0d05\u0d1c\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d1f\u0d46\u0d7b\u0d21\u0d41\u0d7d\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d7c \u0d0e\u0d34\u0d41\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d2f \u0d2a\u0d41\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d15\u0d02 ?",
    "answer": "\u0d2e\u0d47\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3f\u0d02\u0d17\u0d4d \u0d13\u0d2b\u0d4d \u0d0e \u0d15\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d7c",
    "status": "6"
  },
  {
    "id": "863",
    "question": "20-20 \u0d24\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d02 \u0d15\u0d41\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d35\u0d7c\u0d37\u0d02 ?",
    "answer": "2003",
    "status": "6"
  },
  {
    "id": "864",
    "question": "\u0d06\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f IPL \u0d15\u0d3f\u0d30\u0d40\u0d1f\u0d02 \u0d28\u0d47\u0d1f\u0d3f\u0d2f \u0d1f\u0d40\u0d02 ?",
    "answer": "\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d1c\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d3e\u0d7b \u0d31\u0d4b\u0d2f\u0d7d\u0d38\u0d4d",
    "status": "6"
  },
  {
    "id": "865",
    "question": "Test \u0d15\u0d33\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a \u0d06\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d2e\u0d32\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d33\u0d3f ?\r\n",
    "answer": "\u0d1f\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d41 \u0d2f\u0d4b\u0d39\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d3e\u0d7b\r\n",
    "status": "6"
  },
  {
    "id": "866",
    "question": "\u0d1f\u0d46\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d \u0d15\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d7d \u0d39\u0d3e\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4d \u0d28\u0d47\u0d1f\u0d3f\u0d2f \u0d07\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d7b ?",
    "answer": "\u0d39\u0d7c\u0d2d\u0d1c\u0d7b \u0d38\u0d3f\u0d02\u0d17\u0d4d",
    "status": "6"
  },
  {
    "id": "867",
    "question": "ICC \u0d2f\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d06\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d02 ?",
    "answer": "\u0d26\u0d41\u0d2c\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d4d",
    "status": "6"
  },
  {
    "id": "868",
    "question": "\u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d19\u0d4d \u0d2a\u0d4b\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d19\u0d4d \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d46\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d15\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d15 \u0d07\u0d28o ?",
    "answer": "\u0d1f\u0d47\u0d2c\u0d3f\u0d7d \u0d1f\u0d46\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d40\u0d38\u0d4d",
    "status": "6"
  },
  {
    "id": "869",
    "question": "\u0d31\u0d4b \u0d35\u0d3f\u0d02\u0d17\u0d3f\u0d7d \u0d24\u0d41\u0d34\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d41\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d7c \u0d35\u0d1e\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d3f \u0d24\u0d41\u0d34\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d24\u0d4d ?",
    "answer": "\u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d4b\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d4d",
    "status": "6"
  },
  {
    "id": "870",
    "question": "\u0d38\u0d41\u0d2e\u0d4b \u0d17\u0d41\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d7b \u0d05\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d46\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d2a\u0d47\u0d30\u0d4d ?\r\n",
    "answer": "\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d37\u0d4d",
    "status": "6"
  },
  {
    "id": "871",
    "question": "\u0d05\u0d2f\u0d7a \u0d2c\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d7c\u0d2b\u0d4d\u0d32\u0d48 \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d4d \u0d05\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d46\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d15\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d15 \u0d24\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d02 ?\r\n",
    "answer": "\u0d38\u0d48\u0d28 \u0d28\u0d46\u0d39\u0d4d \u0d35\u0d3e\u0d7d",
    "status": "6"
  },
  {
    "id": "872",
    "question": "2013 \u0d38\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4b\u0d37\u0d4d \u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d4b\u0d2b\u0d3f \u0d2e\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d38\u0d30\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d19\u0d7e\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4d \u0d35\u0d47\u0d26\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d0e\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d1f\u0d46 ?",
    "answer": "\u0d15\u0d47\u0d30\u0d33\u0d02",
    "status": "6"
  },
  {
    "id": "873",
    "question": "\u0d0f\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d35\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d15\u0d42\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d24\u0d7d \u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d32\u0d02 \u0d35\u0d47\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d1f. \u0d15\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d15 \u0d35\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4b\u0d26\u0d02 ? ",
    "answer": "\u0d17\u0d4b\u0d7d\u0d2b\u0d4d",
    "status": "6"
  },
  {
    "id": "874",
    "question": "7 \u0d15\u0d1f\u0d32\u0d41\u0d02 5 \u0d2d\u0d42\u0d16\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d21\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d19\u0d33\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d28\u0d40\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f \u0d15\u0d1f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d07\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d7b \u0d35\u0d28\u0d3f\u0d24 ?",
    "answer": "\u0d2c\u0d41\u0d32\u0d3e \u0d1a\u0d57\u0d27\u0d30\u0d3f (\u0d1c\u0d32 \u0d31\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d3f )",
    "status": "6"
  },
  {
    "id": "875",
    "question": "\u0d07\u0d02\u0d17\u0d4d\u0d32\u0d40\u0d37\u0d4d \u0d1a\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d7d \u0d28\u0d40\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f \u0d15\u0d1f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d06\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f \u0d07\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d7b \u0d35\u0d28\u0d3f\u0d24 ?",
    "answer": "\u0d06\u0d30\u0d24\u0d3f \u0d38\u0d3e\u0d39",
    "status": "6"
  },
  {
    "id": "876",
    "question": "\u0d39\u0d4b\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3f \u0d17\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d57\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d28\u0d40\u0d33\u0d02 ?",
    "answer": "300 \u0d05\u0d1f\u0d3f",
    "status": "6"
  },
  {
    "id": "877",
    "question": "\u0d07\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d7d \u0d39\u0d4b\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3f \u0d28\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d38\u0d02\u0d18\u0d1f\u0d28 ?",
    "answer": "\u0d39\u0d4b\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3f \u0d07\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f",
    "status": "6"
  },
  {
    "id": "878",
    "question": "\u0d12\u0d33\u0d3f\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d38\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d1a\u0d3f\u0d39\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d02 ? ",
    "answer": "\u0d2a\u0d30\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d30\u0d02 \u0d15\u0d4b\u0d7c\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24 5 \u0d28\u0d3f\u0d31\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d19\u0d33\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d41\u0d33\u0d4d\u0d33 \u0d35\u0d33\u0d2f\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d19\u0d7e",
    "status": "6"
  },
  {
    "id": "879",
    "question": "\u0d12\u0d33\u0d3f\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d15\u0d4d\u0d37\u0d47\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d02 ? ",
    "answer": "\u0d39\u0d40\u0d30 \u0d26\u0d47\u0d35\u0d3e\u0d32\u0d2f\u0d02",
    "status": "6"
  },
  {
    "id": "880",
    "question": "\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d15 \u0d15\u0d47\u0d30\u0d33\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d35\u0d4d ?",
    "answer": "\u0d1c\u0d3f .\u0d35\u0d3f \u0d30\u0d3e\u0d1c",
    "status": "6"
  },
  {
    "id": "881",
    "question": "\u0d2c\u0d4d\u0d26\u0d2e\u0d32\u0d40\u0d28\u0d40\u0d15\u0d30\u0d23 \u0d2c\u0d4b\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d\u0d21\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d31\u0d3f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d4b\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d4d \u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d02 \u0d07\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4d\u200d \u0d36\u0d2c\u0d4d\u0d26\u0d2e\u0d32\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d40\u0d15\u0d30\u0d23\u0d02 \u0d28\u0d47\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d28\u0d17\u0d30\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d19\u0d33\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4d\u200d \u0d12\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d3e\u0d02 \u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d41\u0d33\u0d4d\u0d33\u0d24\u0d4d",
    "answer": "\u0d2e\u0d41\u0d02\u0d2c\u0d48",
    "status": "3"
  },
  {
    "id": "882",
    "question": "\u0d07\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d28\u0d4d\u200d \u0d38\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d3f\u0d2e\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d35\u0d4d \u0d26\u0d3e\u0d26\u0d3e \u0d38\u0d3e\u0d39\u0d3f\u0d2c\u0d4d \u0d2b\u0d3e\u0d32\u0d4d\u200d\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d38\u0d4d\u0d35\u0d26\u0d47\u0d36\u0d02",
    "answer": "\u0d2e\u0d41\u0d02\u0d2c\u0d48",
    "status": "3"
  },
  {
    "id": "883",
    "question": "\u0d2e\u0d41\u0d02\u0d2c\u0d48\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d27\u0d3e\u0d28 \u0d09\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d38\u0d35\u0d02",
    "answer": "\u0d17\u0d23\u0d47\u0d37\u0d4d \u0d1a\u0d24\u0d41\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d\u0d25\u0d3f",
    "status": "3"
  },
  {
    "id": "884",
    "question": "\u0d2e\u0d41\u0d02\u0d2c\u0d48\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d0f\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d35\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d27\u0d3e\u0d28 \u0d35\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d35\u0d38\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d02",
    "answer": "\u0d24\u0d41\u0d23\u0d3f\u0d35\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d35\u0d38\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d02",
    "status": "3"
  },
  {
    "id": "885",
    "question": "\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d30\u0d23\u0d36\u0d43\u0d02\u0d16\u0d32\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d05\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2d\u0d41\u0d24\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d3f \u0d32\u0d4b\u0d15\u0d02 \u0d35\u0d3f\u0d36\u0d47\u0d37\u0d3f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a \u0d21\u0d2c\u0d4d\u0d2c\u0d3e\u0d35\u0d3e\u0d32\u0d15\u0d33\u0d4d\u200d \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d41 \u0d28\u0d17\u0d30\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d38\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d36\u0d47\u0d37\u0d24\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d",
    "answer": "\u0d2e\u0d41\u0d02\u0d2c\u0d48",
    "status": "3"
  },
  {
    "id": "886",
    "question": "\u0d21\u0d2c\u0d4d\u0d2c\u0d3e\u0d35\u0d3e\u0d32\u0d15\u0d33\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d2a\u0d36\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d3e\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d32\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4d\u200d \u0d0b\u0d24\u0d47\u0d37\u0d4d \u0d2e\u0d3f\u0d36\u0d4d\u0d30 \u0d38\u0d02\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d27\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d02 \u0d1a\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d05\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d37\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d24\u0d32\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4d\u200d \u0d12\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d47\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d2a\u0d41\u0d30\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d19\u0d33\u0d4d\u200d \u0d15\u0d30\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3f\u0d2f \u0d2c\u0d4b\u0d33\u0d3f\u0d35\u0d41\u0d21\u0d4d \u0d1a\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d02",
    "answer": "\u0d32\u0d1e\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d2c\u0d4b\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d38\u0d4d",
    "status": "3"
  },
  {
    "id": "887",
    "question": "1981-\u0d32\u0d4d\u200d \u0d2e\u0d3f\u0d21\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d48\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d38\u0d4d \u0d1a\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4d\u200d\u0d21\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d28\u0d4d\u200d \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d28\u0d4b\u0d35\u0d32\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d42\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d2c\u0d41\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d48\u0d38\u0d4d \u0d28\u0d47\u0d1f\u0d3f\u0d2f \u0d2e\u0d41\u0d02\u0d2c\u0d48 \u0d38\u0d4d\u0d35\u0d26\u0d47\u0d36\u0d3f",
    "answer": "\u0d38\u0d32\u0d4d\u200d\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d4d\u200d \u0d31\u0d41\u0d37\u0d4d\u0d26\u0d3f",
    "status": "3"
  },
  {
    "id": "888",
    "question": "\u0d1c\u0d02\u0d17\u0d3f\u0d33\u0d4d\u200d\u0d2c\u0d41\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d0e\u0d34\u0d41\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d41\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d28\u0d4d\u200d \u0d31\u0d41\u0d21\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d\u0d21\u0d4d \u0d15\u0d3f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d32\u0d3f\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d19\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d1c\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d26\u0d47\u0d36\u0d02",
    "answer": "\u0d2e\u0d41\u0d02\u0d2c\u0d48",
    "status": "3"
  },
  {
    "id": "889",
    "question": "2008 \u0d28\u0d35\u0d02\u0d2c\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4d\u200d \u0d32\u0d37\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d-\u0d07-\u0d24\u0d4a\u0d2f\u0d4d\u0d2c\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d28\u0d47\u0d24\u0d43\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d35\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4d\u200d \u0d28\u0d1f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d2e\u0d41\u0d02\u0d2c\u0d48 \u0d06\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d2e\u0d23\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4d\u200d \u0d07\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d28\u0d4d\u200d \u0d38\u0d47\u0d28 \u0d1c\u0d40\u0d35\u0d28\u0d4b\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d1f\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d42\u0d1f\u0d3f\u0d2f \u0d2a\u0d3e\u0d15\u0d4d \u0d2d\u0d40\u0d15\u0d30\u0d28\u0d4d\u200d",
    "answer": "\u0d05\u0d1c\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d32\u0d4d\u200d \u0d15\u0d38\u0d2c\u0d4d",
    "status": "3"
  },
  {
    "id": "890",
    "question": "2008-\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d2e\u0d41\u0d02\u0d2c\u0d48 \u0d06\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d2e\u0d23\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4d\u200d \u0d15\u0d47\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d2a\u0d3e\u0d1f\u0d4d \u0d38\u0d02\u0d2d\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a \u0d1f\u0d3e\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d3e \u0d17\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d42\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d09\u0d1f\u0d2e\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d24\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d41\u0d33\u0d4d\u0d33 \u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d2e\u0d41\u0d16 \u0d2a\u0d1e\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d28\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d37\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d39\u0d4b\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d32\u0d4d\u200d",
    "answer": "\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d1c\u0d4d \u0d2e\u0d39\u0d32\u0d4d\u200d \u0d2a\u0d3e\u0d32\u0d38\u0d4d \u0d39\u0d4b\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d32\u0d4d\u200d",
    "status": "3"
  },
  {
    "id": "891",
    "question": "\u0d2c\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d3e-\u0d35\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d\u0d33\u0d3f \u0d38\u0d40 \u0d32\u0d3f\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4d \u0d14\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d4b\u0d17\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d3f \u0d05\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d46\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d2a\u0d47\u0d30\u0d4d",
    "answer": "\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d1c\u0d40\u0d35\u0d4d \u0d17\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d27\u0d3f \u0d38\u0d40 \u0d32\u0d3f\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4d",
    "status": "3"
  },
  {
    "id": "892",
    "question": "\u0d2e\u0d41\u0d02\u0d2c\u0d48\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d42\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d12\u0d34\u0d41\u0d15\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d0f\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d35\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d2e\u0d32\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d40\u0d15\u0d30\u0d23\u0d2d\u0d40\u0d37\u0d23\u0d3f \u0d28\u0d47\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d2e\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f \u0d28\u0d26\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d2e\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4a\u0d30\u0d41 \u0d2a\u0d47\u0d30\u0d4d",
    "answer": "\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d39\u0d3f\u0d02 \u0d28\u0d26\u0d3f",
    "status": "3"
  },
  {
    "id": "893",
    "question": "\u0d0f\u0d37\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d0f\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d35\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d2a\u0d34\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d2e\u0d47\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d2f \u0d38\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4b\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4d \u0d0e\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d47\u0d1e\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d4d",
    "answer": "\u0d2c\u0d4b\u0d02\u0d2c\u0d46 \u0d38\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4b\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4d \u0d0e\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d47\u0d1e\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d4d",
    "status": "3"
  },
  {
    "id": "894",
    "question": "\u0d1c\u0d35\u0d3e\u0d39\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d\u0d32\u0d3e\u0d32\u0d4d\u200d \u0d28\u0d46\u0d39\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d41 \u0d2a\u0d4b\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d4d \u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d2e\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4a\u0d30\u0d41 \u0d2a\u0d47\u0d30\u0d4d",
    "answer": "\u0d28\u0d3e\u0d35\u0d3e \u0d37\u0d47\u0d35\u0d3e \u0d2a\u0d4b\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d4d",
    "status": "3"
  },
  {
    "id": "895",
    "question": "2011-\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d15\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d \u0d32\u0d4b\u0d15\u0d15\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4d\u200d \u0d07\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f \u0d15\u0d3f\u0d30\u0d40\u0d1f\u0d02 \u0d28\u0d47\u0d1f\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d2e\u0d41\u0d02\u0d2c\u0d48\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d38\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d47\u0d21\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d30\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d41",
    "answer": "\u0d35\u0d3e\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d21\u0d46 \u0d38\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d47\u0d21\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d02",
    "status": "3"
  },
  {
    "id": "896",
    "question": "\u0d38\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u200d \u0d24\u0d46\u0d28\u0d4d\u200d\u0d21\u0d41\u0d32\u0d4d\u200d\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d \u0d24\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d15\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d \u0d15\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d05\u0d35\u0d38\u0d3e\u0d28 \u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d4d\u200c \u0d15\u0d33\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a \u0d38\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d47\u0d21\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d02",
    "answer": "\u0d35\u0d3e\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d21\u0d46 \u0d38\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d47\u0d21\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d02",
    "status": "3"
  },
  {
    "id": "897",
    "question": "\u0d38\u0d57\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d2e\u0d41\u0d02\u0d2c\u0d48\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4d\u200d \u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d32\u0d4b\u0d15\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d0f\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d35\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d06\u0d21\u0d02\u0d2c\u0d30\u0d2a\u0d42\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d\u0d23\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d2f \u0d38\u0d4d\u0d35\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d35\u0d38\u0d24\u0d3f",
    "answer": "\u0d06\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d3f\u0d2f",
    "status": "3"
  },
  {
    "id": "898",
    "question": "\u0d06\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d3f\u0d2f \u0d2a\u0d23\u0d3f \u0d15\u0d34\u0d3f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d06\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d",
    "answer": "\u0d2e\u0d41\u0d15\u0d47\u0d37\u0d4d \u0d05\u0d02\u0d2c\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d3f",
    "status": "3"
  },
  {
    "id": "899",
    "question": "1901-\u0d32\u0d4d\u200d \u0d2e\u0d41\u0d02\u0d2c\u0d48 \u0d38\u0d4d\u0d35\u0d26\u0d47\u0d36\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d2f \u0d06\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d \u0d12\u0d30\u0d41 \u0d15\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d \u0d38\u0d4d\u0d35\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3f\u0d2f \u0d06\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f \u0d07\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d28\u0d4d\u200d \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d28\u0d47\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d2e\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d24\u0d4d",
    "answer": "\u0d1c\u0d3e\u0d02\u0d37\u0d21\u0d4d\u0d1c\u0d3f \u0d28\u0d41\u0d38\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d\u0d35\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d4d\u200d\u0d1c\u0d3f \u0d1f\u0d3e\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31",
    "status": "3"
  },
  {
    "id": "900",
    "question": "\u0d2e\u0d41\u0d02\u0d2c\u0d48\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d2e\u0d41\u0d16 \u0d38\u0d3e\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2c\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d3e\u0d2a\u0d28\u0d38\u0d2e\u0d41\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d2f\u0d02",
    "answer": "\u0d2c\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d3e -\u0d15\u0d41\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d\u0d33 \u0d15\u0d4b\u0d02\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d32\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d38\u0d4d\r\n",
    "status": "3"
  },
  {
    "id": "901",
    "question": "\u0d2e\u0d41\u0d02\u0d2c\u0d48\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4d\u200d \u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d0f\u0d37\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d0f\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d35\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d35\u0d32\u0d3f\u0d2f \u0d1a\u0d47\u0d30\u0d3f ?",
    "answer": "\u0d27\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d35\u0d3f",
    "status": "3"
  },
  {
    "id": "902",
    "question": "\u0d27\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d2a\u0d36\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d3e\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d32\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4d\u200d \u0d21\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d3f \u0d2c\u0d4b\u0d2f\u0d46\u0d32\u0d4d\u200d \u0d38\u0d02\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d27\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d02 \u0d1a\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d0e\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d4d \u0d05\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d26\u0d2e\u0d3f \u0d2a\u0d41\u0d30\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d19\u0d33\u0d4d\u200d \u0d15\u0d30\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3f\u0d2f \u0d1a\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d02 ?",
    "answer": "\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d32\u0d02\u0d21\u0d4b\u0d17\u0d4d \u0d2e\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4d\u0d32\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d28\u0d2f\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d",
    "status": "3"
  },
  {
    "id": "903",
    "question": "\u0d2c\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d40\u0d37\u0d4d \u0d2d\u0d30\u0d23\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d32\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d \u0d27\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d35\u0d3f \u0d1a\u0d47\u0d30\u0d3f \u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d3e\u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d24\u0d4d. \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d41 \u0d35\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d\u0d37\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d30\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d41 \u0d05\u0d24\u0d4d ?",
    "answer": "1882",
    "status": "3"
  },
  {
    "id": "904",
    "question": "1988-\u0d32\u0d4d\u200d \u0d31\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d40\u0d38\u0d3e\u0d2f \u0d38\u0d32\u0d3e\u0d02\u0d2c\u0d4b\u0d02\u0d2c\u0d46 \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d1a\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d38\u0d02\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d27\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d15 \u0d06\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d ?",
    "answer": "\u0d2e\u0d40\u0d30\u0d3e \u0d28\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d",
    "status": "3"
  },
  {
    "id": "905",
    "question": "1995-\u0d32\u0d4d\u200d \u0d07\u0d31\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d19\u0d3f\u0d2f \u0d2c\u0d4b\u0d02\u0d2c\u0d46 \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d24\u0d2e\u0d3f\u0d34\u0d4d \u0d1a\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d38\u0d02\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d27\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d15\u0d28\u0d4d\u200d \u0d06\u0d30\u0d4d ?",
    "answer": "\u0d2e\u0d23\u0d3f\u0d30\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d02",
    "status": "3"
  },
  {
    "id": "906",
    "question": "\u0d07\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d26\u0d47\u0d36\u0d40\u0d2f \u0d15\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d15 \u0d35\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4b\u0d26\u0d02 ?",
    "answer": "\u0d39\u0d4b\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3f",
    "status": "3"
  },
  {
    "id": "907",
    "question": "\u0d07\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f \u0d07\u0d24\u0d41\u0d35\u0d30\u0d46 \u0d39\u0d4b\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4d \u0d0e\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30 \u0d12\u0d33\u0d3f\u0d02\u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d38\u0d4d \u0d38\u0d4d\u0d35\u0d30\u0d4d\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d23 \u0d2e\u0d46\u0d21\u0d32\u0d41\u0d15\u0d33\u0d4d \u0d28\u0d47\u0d1f\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d4d ?",
    "answer": "8",
    "status": "3"
  },
  {
    "id": "908",
    "question": "\u0d07\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d28\u0d4d \u0d39\u0d4b\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d38\u0d41\u0d35\u0d30\u0d4d\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d23 \u0d15\u0d3e\u0d32\u0d18\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d02 \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d4d \u0d2a\u0d31\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d35\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d15\u0d3e\u0d32\u0d18\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d02 ?",
    "answer": "1928-56",
    "status": "3"
  },
  {
    "id": "909",
    "question": "\u0d07\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d28\u0d4d \u0d39\u0d4b\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d28\u0d4d \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d46\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d06\u0d30\u0d4d ?",
    "answer": "\u0d27\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d26\u0d4d",
    "status": "3"
  },
  {
    "id": "910",
    "question": "\u0d06\u0d30\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d1c\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d2e \u0d26\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d \u0d07\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4d \u0d26\u0d47\u0d36\u0d40\u0d2f \u0d15\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d15 \u0d26\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d3f \u0d06\u0d1a\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d24\u0d4d ?",
    "answer": "\u0d27\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d26\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d46",
    "status": "3"
  },
  {
    "id": "911",
    "question": "\u0d07\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d26\u0d47\u0d36\u0d40\u0d2f\u0d2a\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d15 \u0d2d\u0d30\u0d23\u0d18\u0d1f\u0d28\u0d3e \u0d28\u0d3f\u0d30\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d38\u0d2e\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d3f \u0d05\u0d02\u0d17\u0d40\u0d15\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d4d ?",
    "answer": "1947 \u0d1c\u0d42\u0d32\u0d48 22",
    "status": "3"
  },
  {
    "id": "912",
    "question": "\u0d07\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d26\u0d47\u0d36\u0d40\u0d2f \u0d2a\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d15\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d28\u0d40\u0d33\u0d35\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d35\u0d40\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d24\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d41\u0d33\u0d4d\u0d33 \u0d05\u0d28\u0d41\u0d2a\u0d3e\u0d24\u0d02 ?",
    "answer": "3:2",
    "status": "3"
  },
  {
    "id": "913",
    "question": " \u0d26\u0d47\u0d36\u0d40\u0d2f\u0d2a\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d15\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d28\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d41\u0d33\u0d4d\u0d33 \u0d05\u0d36\u0d4b\u0d15 \u0d1a\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d06\u0d30\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d32\u0d41\u0d15\u0d33\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d0e\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d23\u0d02 ?",
    "answer": "24",
    "status": "3"
  },
  {
    "id": "914",
    "question": "\u0d07\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d26\u0d47\u0d36\u0d40\u0d2f\u0d2a\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d15 \u0d30\u0d42\u0d2a \u0d15\u0d32\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d28 \u0d1a\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d06\u0d30\u0d4d ?",
    "answer": "\u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d02\u0d17\u0d33 \u0d35\u0d46\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d2f\u0d4d\u0d2f",
    "status": "3"
  },
  {
    "id": "915",
    "question": "\u0d26\u0d47\u0d36\u0d40\u0d2f\u0d2a\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d15\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d28\u0d3f\u0d31\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d19\u0d33\u0d4d \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d46 \u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d3f\u0d27\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d02 \u0d1a\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d41 \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d4d \u0d35\u0d3f\u0d36\u0d26\u0d40\u0d15\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d24\u0d4d ?",
    "answer": "\u0d21\u0d4b. \u0d0e\u0d38\u0d4d .\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d27\u0d3e\u0d15\u0d43\u0d37\u0d4d\u0d23\u0d28\u0d4d",
    "status": "3"
  },
  {
    "id": "916",
    "question": "\u0d07\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d38\u0d02\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d38\u0d02\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d3e\u0d28 \u0d2a\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d37\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d \u0d2e\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4d ?",
    "answer": "\u0d12\u0d21\u0d40\u0d37",
    "status": "3"
  },
  {
    "id": "917",
    "question": "\u0d32\u0d4b\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d38\u0d4d \u0d1f\u0d46\u0d02\u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d33\u0d4d \u0d0e\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d3f \u0d1a\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d41 ?",
    "answer": "\u0d21\u0d32\u0d4d\u0d39\u0d3f",
    "status": "3"
  },
  {
    "id": "918",
    "question": "\u0d15\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d35 \u0d26\u0d47\u0d36\u0d40\u0d2f \u0d2e\u0d43\u0d17\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d33\u0d4d\u0d33 \u0d07\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d05\u0d2f\u0d32\u0d4d \u0d30\u0d3e\u0d1c\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d02 ?",
    "answer": "\u0d2c\u0d02\u0d17\u0d4d\u0d32\u0d3e\u0d26\u0d47\u0d36\u0d4d",
    "status": "3"
  },
  {
    "id": "919",
    "question": "\u0d05\u0d27\u0d3f\u0d35\u0d30\u0d4d\u0d37\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d19\u0d33\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4d \u0d26\u0d47\u0d36\u0d40\u0d2f \u0d15\u0d32\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d06\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d38\u0d02 \u0d06\u0d30\u0d02\u0d2d\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d26\u0d3f\u0d35\u0d38\u0d02 ?",
    "answer": "\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d4d 21",
    "status": "3"
  },
  {
    "id": "920",
    "question": "\u0d2e\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d46 \u0d26\u0d47\u0d36\u0d40\u0d2f \u0d2a\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d37\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d3f \u0d05\u0d02\u0d17\u0d40\u0d15\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a \u0d35\u0d30\u0d4d\u0d37\u0d02 ?",
    "answer": "1963",
    "status": "3"
  },
  {
    "id": "921",
    "question": "\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d19 \u0d26\u0d47\u0d36\u0d40\u0d2f \u0d2b\u0d32\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d2f \u0d07\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d05\u0d2f\u0d32\u0d4d \u0d30\u0d3e\u0d1c\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d02 ?",
    "answer": "\u0d2a\u0d3e\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3f\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d4d",
    "status": "3"
  },
  {
    "id": "922",
    "question": "1972 \u0d35\u0d30\u0d46 \u0d07\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d26\u0d47\u0d36\u0d40\u0d2f \u0d2e\u0d43\u0d17\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d30\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d24\u0d4d ?",
    "answer": "\u0d38\u0d3f\u0d02\u0d39\u0d02",
    "status": "3"
  },
  {
    "id": "923",
    "question": "\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d32\u0d3e\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d3f\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31 \u0d17\u0d02\u0d17\u0d3e\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d \u0d07\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d26\u0d47\u0d36\u0d40\u0d2f \u2026\u2026\u2026\u2026 \u0d06\u0d23\u0d4d ?",
    "answer": "\u0d1c\u0d32\u0d1c\u0d40\u0d35\u0d3f",
    "status": "3"
  },
  {
    "id": "924",
    "question": "\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d4b\u0d1c\u0d15\u0d4d \u0d0e\u0d32\u0d3f\u0d2b\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d \u0d2a\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d27\u0d24\u0d3f \u0d24\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d19\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d24\u0d46\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d4b\u0d33\u0d4d ?",
    "answer": "1991-92",
    "status": "3"
  },
  {
    "id": "925",
    "question": "\u0d07\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4d \u0d0e\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30 \u0d38\u0d02\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d19\u0d33\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d38\u0d02\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d3e\u0d28 \u0d2e\u0d43\u0d17\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d \u0d06\u0d28 ?",
    "answer": "4",
    "status": "3"
  },
  {
    "id": "926",
    "question": "\u0d09\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2d\u0d35 \u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d2f \u0d17\u0d02\u0d17\u0d4b\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4d \u0d17\u0d02\u0d17 \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d2a\u0d47\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d46\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d41 ?",
    "answer": "\u0d2d\u0d3e\u0d17\u0d40\u0d30\u0d25\u0d3f",
    "status": "3"
  },
  {
    "id": "927",
    "question": "\u0d26\u0d47\u0d36\u0d40\u0d2f \u0d1a\u0d3f\u0d39\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4d \u0d26\u0d43\u0d36\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d15\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d1c\u0d40\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d33\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d0e\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d23\u0d02 ?",
    "answer": "5",
    "status": "3"
  },
  {
    "id": "928",
    "question": "\u0d35\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d26\u0d47\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d24\u0d30\u0d02 \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d15\u0d43\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4d \u0d28\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d41\u0d2e\u0d41\u0d33\u0d4d\u0d33\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d ?",
    "answer": "\u0d06\u0d28\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d26\u0d2e\u0d20\u0d02",
    "status": "3"
  },
  {
    "id": "929",
    "question": "\u0d2d\u0d42\u0d2e\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d05\u0d30\u0d4d\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d27\u0d17\u0d4b\u0d33\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d \u0d07\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f \u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d3f \u0d1a\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d24\u0d4d ?",
    "answer": "\u0d09\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d4d\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d27\u0d17\u0d4b\u0d33\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4d",
    "status": "3"
  },
  {
    "id": "930",
    "question": "\u0d32\u0d4b\u0d15\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d35\u0d3f\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d43\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d0e\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d36\u0d24\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d \u0d07\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d47\u0d24\u0d4d ?",
    "answer": "2.42%",
    "status": "3"
  },
  {
    "id": "931",
    "question": "\u0d35\u0d32\u0d3f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4d \u0d32\u0d4b\u0d15\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d37\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d19\u0d33\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3f\u0d1f\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4d \u0d07\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d02 ?",
    "answer": "7",
    "status": "3"
  },
  {
    "id": "932",
    "question": "\u0d07\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f \u0d0e\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30 \u0d30\u0d3e\u0d1c\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d19\u0d33\u0d41\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d3f \u0d05\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d30\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24 \u0d2a\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3f\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d41 ?",
    "answer": "7",
    "status": "3"
  },
  {
    "id": "933",
    "question": "\u0d35\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d26\u0d47\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d24\u0d30\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d07\u0d17\u0d4d\u0d32\u0d40\u0d37\u0d4d \u0d2a\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d2d\u0d3e\u0d37 \u0d24\u0d2f\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d31\u0d3e\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d06\u0d30\u0d4d ?",
    "answer": "\u0d05\u0d30\u0d2c\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d26\u0d4b \u0d18\u0d4b\u0d37\u0d4d",
    "status": "3"
  },
  {
    "id": "934",
    "question": "\u0d07\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d28\u0d4d \u0d05\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d30\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4d \u0d0f\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d35\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d1a\u0d46\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d2f \u0d30\u0d3e\u0d1c\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d02 ?",
    "answer": "\u0d2d\u0d42\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d4d",
    "status": "3"
  },
  {
    "id": "935",
    "question": "\u0d0f\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d35\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d15\u0d42\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d24\u0d32\u0d4d \u0d38\u0d02\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d19\u0d33\u0d41\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d3f \u0d05\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d30\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f \u0d2a\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3f\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d38\u0d02\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d02 ?",
    "answer": "\u0d09\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d30\u0d4d \u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d26\u0d47\u0d36\u0d4d (8)",
    "status": "3"
  },
  {
    "id": "936",
    "question": "\u0d0f\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d35\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d15\u0d42\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d24\u0d32\u0d4d \u0d30\u0d3e\u0d1c\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d19\u0d33\u0d41\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d3f \u0d05\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d30\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f \u0d2a\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3f\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d07\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d28\u0d4d \u0d38\u0d02\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d02 ?",
    "answer": "\u0d1c\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d41 \u0d15\u0d3e\u0d36\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d40\u0d30\u0d4d",
    "status": "3"
  },
  {
    "id": "937",
    "question": "\u0d07\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4d \u0d0e\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30 \u0d38\u0d02\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d19\u0d33\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4d \u0d15\u0d1f\u0d32\u0d4d \u0d24\u0d40\u0d30\u0d2e\u0d41\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d4d ?",
    "answer": "9",
    "status": "3"
  },
  {
    "id": "938",
    "question": "\u0d07\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f \u0d0f\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d35\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d15\u0d41\u0d31\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d4d \u0d28\u0d40\u0d33\u0d02 \u0d05\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d30\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f \u0d2a\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3f\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d30\u0d3e\u0d1c\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d35\u0d41\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d ?",
    "answer": "\u0d05\u0d2b\u0d4d\u0d17\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d3f\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d4d",
    "status": "3"
  },
  {
    "id": "939",
    "question": "\u0d07\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d28\u0d4d \u0d38\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d21\u0d47\u0d30\u0d4d\u0d21\u0d4d \u0d1f\u0d48\u0d02 \u0d28\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4d \u0d35\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d41 \u0d2e\u0d41\u0d24\u0d32\u0d4d ?",
    "answer": "1906 \u0d1c\u0d28\u0d41\u0d35\u0d30\u0d3f 1",
    "status": "3"
  },
  {
    "id": "940",
    "question": "\u0d2c\u0d02\u0d17\u0d3e\u0d33\u0d4d \u0d09\u0d33\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d1f\u0d32\u0d4d \u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d1a\u0d40\u0d28\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d32\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d05\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d46\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d3f\u0d30\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d24\u0d4d ?",
    "answer": "\u0d1a\u0d4b\u0d33\u0d24\u0d1f\u0d3e\u0d15\u0d02",
    "status": "3"
  },
  {
    "id": "941",
    "question": "\u0d2a\u0d42\u0d30\u0d4d\u0d35\u0d4d\u0d35\u0d18\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d02 \u0d2a\u0d36\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d3f\u0d2e\u0d18\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d35\u0d41\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d3f \u0d38\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d27\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d32\u0d02",
    "answer": "\u0d28\u0d40\u0d32\u0d17\u0d30\u0d3f",
    "status": "3"
  },
  {
    "id": "942",
    "question": "\u0d07\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d28\u0d4d \u0d38\u0d02\u0d18\u0d02 \u0d06\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d3f \u0d0e\u0d35\u0d31\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d \u0d15\u0d40\u0d34\u0d1f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d4d ?",
    "answer": "1965 \u0d32\u0d4d",
    "status": "3"
  },
  {
    "id": "943",
    "question": "\u0d05\u0d31\u0d2c\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d1f\u0d32\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4d \u0d2a\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d0f\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d35\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d35\u0d32\u0d3f\u0d2f \u0d28\u0d26\u0d3f ?",
    "answer": "\u0d38\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d27\u0d41",
    "status": "3"
  },
  {
    "id": "944",
    "question": "\u0d06\u0d30\u0d35\u0d32\u0d4d\u0d32\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d0f\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d35\u0d41 \u0d09\u0d2f\u0d30\u0d02 \u0d15\u0d42\u0d1f\u0d3f\u0d2f \u0d2a\u0d30\u0d4d\u0d35\u0d4d\u0d35\u0d24\u0d02 ?",
    "answer": "\u0d17\u0d41\u0d30\u0d41\u0d36\u0d3f\u0d16\u0d3f\u0d30\u0d02",
    "status": "3"
  },
  {
    "id": "945",
    "question": "\u0d2e\u0d57\u0d38\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d02 \u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d15\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d4d ?",
    "answer": "\u0d16\u0d3e\u0d38\u0d3f",
    "status": "3"
  },
  {
    "id": "946",
    "question": "\u0d2a\u0d36\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d3f\u0d2e\u0d18\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d28\u0d40\u0d33\u0d02 \u0d0e\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30 ?",
    "answer": "1600 \u0d15\u0d3f.\u0d2e\u0d40.",
    "status": "3"
  },
  {
    "id": "947",
    "question": "\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d1e\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d1c\u0d02\u0d17 \u0d15\u0d4a\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d2e\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d3f \u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d3f \u0d1a\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d38\u0d02\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d02 ?",
    "answer": "\u0d38\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3f\u0d02",
    "status": "3"
  },
  {
    "id": "948",
    "question": "\u0d07\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4d \u0d0f\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d35\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d09\u0d2f\u0d30\u0d2e\u0d41\u0d33\u0d4d\u0d33 \u0d15\u0d4a\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d2e\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d3f \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d41 \u0d38\u0d02\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d ?",
    "answer": "\u0d1c\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d41-\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d36\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d40\u0d30\u0d4d",
    "status": "3"
  },
  {
    "id": "949",
    "question": "\u0d2a\u0d36\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d3f\u0d2e\u0d18\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d35\u0d1f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d46 \u0d05\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d41\u0d33\u0d4d\u0d33 \u0d28\u0d26\u0d3f ?",
    "answer": "\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f",
    "status": "3"
  },
  {
    "id": "950",
    "question": "\u0d2a\u0d36\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d3f\u0d2e\u0d18\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d2e\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4a\u0d30\u0d41 \u0d2a\u0d47\u0d30\u0d4d ?",
    "answer": "\u0d38\u0d39\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d3f",
    "status": "3"
  },
  {
    "id": "951",
    "question": "\u0d39\u0d3f\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d1a\u0d32\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d26\u0d47\u0d36\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d27\u0d3e\u0d28 \u0d1a\u0d41\u0d30\u0d02 ?",
    "answer": "\u0d31\u0d4b\u0d39\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d19\u0d4d",
    "status": "3"
  },
  {
    "id": "952",
    "question": "\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d27\u0d4d\u0d2f \u2013 \u0d38\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d41\u0d30 \u0d15\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d41\u0d15\u0d33\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3f\u0d1f\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d42\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d12\u0d34\u0d41\u0d15\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d28\u0d26\u0d3f ?",
    "answer": "\u0d28\u0d30\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d26",
    "status": "3"
  },
  {
    "id": "953",
    "question": "\u0d17\u0d02\u0d17 \u0d28\u0d26\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d28\u0d40\u0d33\u0d02 ?",
    "answer": "2525 \u0d15\u0d3f.\u0d2e\u0d40",
    "status": "3"
  },
  {
    "id": "954",
    "question": "\u0d17\u0d02\u0d17 \u2013 \u0d2f\u0d2e\u0d41\u0d28 \u0d38\u0d02\u0d17\u0d2e\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d32\u0d02 ?",
    "answer": "\u0d05\u0d32\u0d39\u0d3e\u0d2c\u0d3e\u0d26",
    "status": "3"
  },
  {
    "id": "955",
    "question": " \u0d36\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d40 \u0d2c\u0d41\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d27\u0d28\u0d4d\u200d \u0d24\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d06\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f \u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d2d\u0d3e\u0d37\u0d23\u0d02 \u0d28\u0d1f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d2f \u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d32\u0d02 ?",
    "answer": "\u0d38\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d3e\u0d25\u0d4d",
    "status": "2"
  },
  {
    "id": "956",
    "question": "\u0d1a\u0d4b\u0d33\u0d35\u0d02\u0d36\u0d02 \u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d3e\u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d4d ?",
    "answer": "\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d1c\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d32\u0d2f",
    "status": "2"
  },
  {
    "id": "957",
    "question": "\u0d2e\u0d39\u0d3e\u0d35\u0d40\u0d30\u0d28\u0d4d\u200d \u0d0e\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d2e\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d46 \u0d24\u0d40\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d3e\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d30\u0d28\u0d4d\u200d \u0d06\u0d23\u0d4d ?",
    "answer": "24",
    "status": "2"
  },
  {
    "id": "958",
    "question": "\u0d2c\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d40\u0d37\u0d41\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d 1857 \u2013 \u0d32\u0d4d\u200d \u0d28\u0d3e\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d15\u0d1f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d2f \u0d2e\u0d41\u0d17\u0d33\u0d4d\u200d \u0d30\u0d3e\u0d1c\u0d3e\u0d35\u0d4d ?",
    "answer": "\u0d2c\u0d39\u0d26\u0d42\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d \u0d37\u0d3e II",
    "status": "2"
  },
  {
    "id": "959",
    "question": "\u0d2c\u0d41\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d27\u0d2e\u0d24\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d1a\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d23\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d3f \u0d05\u0d36\u0d4b\u0d15\u0d28\u0d4d\u200d \u0d28\u0d47\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d3e\u0d33\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d47\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4d \u0d05\u0d2f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d24\u0d4d ?",
    "answer": "\u0d1a\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d2e\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d46",
    "status": "2"
  },
  {
    "id": "960",
    "question": "\u0d05\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d2c\u0d31\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d24\u0d32\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d02 ?",
    "answer": "\u0d2b\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d47\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d42\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d \u0d38\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d3f29. \u0d09\u0d34\u0d35\u0d41\u0d1a\u0d3e\u0d32\u0d4d\u200d \u0d2a\u0d3e\u0d1f\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d19\u0d33\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d05\u0d35\u0d36\u0d3f\u0d37\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d19\u0d33\u0d4d\u200d \u0d15\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d24\u0d4d ?\r\n\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d33\u0d3f\u0d2c\u0d02\u0d17\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d",
    "status": "2"
  },
  {
    "id": "961",
    "question": "\u0d07\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d24\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24 \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d46\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d06\u0d30\u0d4d ?",
    "answer": "\u0d05\u0d2e\u0d40\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d \u0d16\u0d41\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d41",
    "status": "2"
  },
  {
    "id": "962",
    "question": "\u0d12\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d3e\u0d02 \u0d15\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d23\u0d3e\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d \u0d2f\u0d41\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d27\u0d02 \u0d06\u0d30\u0d02\u0d2d\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a \u0d35\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d\u0d37\u0d02 ?",
    "answer": "1744",
    "status": "2"
  },
  {
    "id": "963",
    "question": "\u0d12\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d3e\u0d02 \u0d2a\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d3f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d2f\u0d41\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d27\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4d\u200d \u0d2a\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d1c\u0d2f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d46\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d06\u0d30\u0d4d ?",
    "answer": "\u0d07\u0d2c\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d39\u0d3f\u0d02 \u0d32\u0d4b\u0d27\u0d3f",
    "status": "2"
  },
  {
    "id": "964",
    "question": "\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d26\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d\u0d36\u0d3f\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d1c \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d46\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d4d ?",
    "answer": "\u0d05\u0d36\u0d4b\u0d15\u0d28\u0d4d\u200d",
    "status": "2"
  },
  {
    "id": "965",
    "question": "\u0d05\u0d35\u0d38\u0d3e\u0d28 \u0d16\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4d\u200d\u0d1c\u0d3f \u0d35\u0d02\u0d36 \u0d30\u0d3e\u0d1c\u0d3e\u0d35\u0d4d \u0d06\u0d30\u0d4d ?",
    "answer": "\u0d2e\u0d41\u0d2c\u0d3e\u0d31\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4d \u0d37\u0d3e",
    "status": "2"
  },
  {
    "id": "966",
    "question": "\u0d05\u0d32\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d38\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d30\u0d3e\u0d1c\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d30\u0d3e\u0d1c\u0d3e\u0d35\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d ?",
    "answer": "\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d38\u0d3f\u0d21\u0d4b\u0d23\u0d3f\u0d2f",
    "status": "2"
  },
  {
    "id": "967",
    "question": "\u0d2a\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d47\u0d34\u0d41\u0d24\u0d35\u0d23 \u0d07\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d2f\u0d46 \u0d06\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d2e\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a \u0d2e\u0d41\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d32\u0d3f\u0d02 \u0d2d\u0d30\u0d23\u0d3e\u0d27\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d3f ?",
    "answer": "\u0d2e\u0d41\u0d39\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d26\u0d4d \u0d17\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d3f",
    "status": "2"
  },
  {
    "id": "968",
    "question": "\u0d30\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d3e\u0d02 \u0d1c\u0d48\u0d28\u0d2e\u0d24 \u0d38\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d47\u0d33\u0d28\u0d02 \u0d28\u0d1f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d32\u0d02 ?",
    "answer": "\u0d35\u0d32\u0d4d\u0d32\u0d3e\u0d2d\u0d3f",
    "status": "2"
  },
  {
    "id": "969",
    "question": "\u0d39\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d\u0d37\u0d35\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d\u0d27\u0d28\u0d28\u0d4d\u200d \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d41 \u0d30\u0d3e\u0d1c\u0d35\u0d02\u0d36\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d41\u0d33\u0d4d\u200d\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d46\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d41 ?",
    "answer": "\u0d2a\u0d41\u0d37\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d2d\u0d42\u0d24\u0d3f",
    "status": "2"
  },
  {
    "id": "970",
    "question": "\u0d06\u0d28\u0d15\u0d33\u0d46 \u0d2a\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d\u0d35\u0d4d\u0d35\u0d24 \u0d2e\u0d41\u0d15\u0d33\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4d\u200d\u0d28\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d4d \u0d24\u0d3e\u0d34\u0d47\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4d \u0d24\u0d33\u0d4d\u0d33\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d4d \u0d30\u0d38\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d3f\u0d30\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d39\u0d42\u0d23\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d1c\u0d3e\u0d35\u0d4d ?",
    "answer": "\u0d2e\u0d3f\u0d39\u0d3f\u0d30\u0d15\u0d41\u0d32\u0d28\u0d4d\u200d",
    "status": "2"
  },
  {
    "id": "971",
    "question": "\u0d28\u0d35\u0d30\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d19\u0d33\u0d4d\u200d \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d17\u0d41\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d1c\u0d3e\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d38\u0d26\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d38\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d ?",
    "answer": "\u0d1a\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d17\u0d41\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d28\u0d4d\u200d II",
    "status": "2"
  },
  {
    "id": "972",
    "question": "\u0d36\u0d15\u0d35\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d\u0d37\u0d02 \u0d06\u0d30\u0d02\u0d2d\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d06\u0d30\u0d4d ?",
    "answer": "\u0d15\u0d28\u0d3f\u0d37\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d28\u0d4d\u200d, AD 78",
    "status": "2"
  },
  {
    "id": "973",
    "question": "\u0d1a\u0d47\u0d30\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d30\u0d3e\u0d1c\u0d15\u0d40\u0d2f \u0d2e\u0d41\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d30 ?",
    "answer": "\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4d\u0d32\u0d4d",
    "status": "2"
  },
  {
    "id": "974",
    "question": "\u0d36\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d40 \u0d2c\u0d41\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d27\u0d28\u0d4d\u200d \u0d1c\u0d28\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a \u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d32\u0d02 ?",
    "answer": "\u0d32\u0d41\u0d02\u0d2c\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d3f, BC 563",
    "status": "2"
  },
  {
    "id": "975",
    "question": "\u0d05\u0d2e\u0d41\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d32\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d24 \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d15\u0d43\u0d24\u0d3f \u0d30\u0d1a\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d4d ?",
    "answer": "\u0d15\u0d43\u0d37\u0d4d\u0d23\u0d26\u0d47\u0d35\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d",
    "status": "2"
  },
  {
    "id": "976",
    "question": "\u0d07\u0d2c\u0d28\u0d41\u0d2c\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d42\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24 \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d30\u0d3e\u0d1c\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d41\u0d28\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d41\u0d33\u0d4d\u0d33 \u0d38\u0d1e\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d ?",
    "answer": "\u0d2e\u0d4a\u0d31\u0d4b\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4b",
    "status": "2"
  },
  {
    "id": "977",
    "question": "\u0d1c\u0d40\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d3f\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d38\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d38\u0d3f \u0d06\u0d30\u0d4d ?",
    "answer": "\u0d14\u0d31\u0d02\u0d17\u0d38\u0d40\u0d2c\u0d4d",
    "status": "2"
  },
  {
    "id": "978",
    "question": "\u0d05\u0d32\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d38\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d \u0d05\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d0e\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d35\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d4d ?",
    "answer": "\u0d2c\u0d2c\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4b\u0d23\u0d3f\u0d2f",
    "status": "2"
  },
  {
    "id": "979",
    "question": "\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d2e\u0d1a\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d38\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d15\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d35\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d4d ?",
    "answer": "\u0d24\u0d41\u0d33\u0d38\u0d40\u0d26\u0d3e\u0d38\u0d4d",
    "status": "2"
  },
  {
    "id": "980",
    "question": "\u0d38\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d27\u0d41 \u0d28\u0d3e\u0d17\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d15 \u0d15\u0d3e\u0d32\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d46 \u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d2f\u0d27\u0d3e\u0d28 \u0d24\u0d41\u0d31\u0d2e\u0d41\u0d16\u0d02 ?",
    "answer": "\u0d32\u0d4b\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d32\u0d4d\u200d",
    "status": "2"
  },
  {
    "id": "981",
    "question": "\u0d06\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d3f \u0d07\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4d\u200d \u0d2a\u0d40\u0d30\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d1f \u0d09\u0d2a\u0d2f\u0d4b\u0d17\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d06\u0d30\u0d4d ?",
    "answer": "\u0d2c\u0d3e\u0d2c\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d",
    "status": "2"
  },
  {
    "id": "982",
    "question": "\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d32\u0d3e\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d38\u0d3f \u0d2f\u0d41\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d27\u0d02 \u0d28\u0d1f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d35\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d\u0d37\u0d02 ?",
    "answer": "1757",
    "status": "2"
  },
  {
    "id": "983",
    "question": "\u0d06\u0d17\u0d4d\u0d30 \u0d28\u0d17\u0d30\u0d02 \u0d2a\u0d23\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d34\u0d3f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d4d ?",
    "answer": "\u0d38\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d \u0d32\u0d4b\u0d27\u0d3f",
    "status": "2"
  },
  {
    "id": "984",
    "question": "\u0d0f\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d2e\u0d41\u0d17\u0d33\u0d4d\u200d \u0d30\u0d3e\u0d1c\u0d3e\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d2a\u0d47\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d \u0d2d\u0d3e\u0d17\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d35\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d4d\u200d \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d02 \u0d35\u0d30\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d24\u0d4d ?",
    "answer": "\u0d39\u0d41\u0d2e\u0d2f\u0d42\u0d23\u0d4d\u200d",
    "status": "2"
  },
  {
    "id": "985",
    "question": "\u0d05\u0d32\u0d3e\u0d35\u0d41\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d26\u0d40\u0d28\u0d4d\u200d \u0d16\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4d\u200d\u0d1c\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d38\u0d47\u0d28\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d15\u0d28\u0d4d\u200d \u0d06\u0d30\u0d4d ?",
    "answer": "\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d32\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d \u0d15\u0d2b\u0d42\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d\r\n",
    "status": "2"
  },
  {
    "id": "986",
    "question": "\u0d39\u0d21\u0d3e\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d38\u0d4d \u0d2f\u0d41\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d27\u0d02 \u0d28\u0d1f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d06\u0d30\u0d46\u0d32\u0d4d\u0d32\u0d3e\u0d02 \u0d24\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4d\u200d ?",
    "answer": "\u0d05\u0d32\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d38\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d, \u0d2a\u0d4b\u0d31\u0d38\u0d4d",
    "status": "2"
  },
  {
    "id": "987",
    "question": "\u0d07\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4d\u200d \u0d2e\u0d41\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d32\u0d3f\u0d02 \u0d38\u0d3e\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d1c\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d02 \u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d3e\u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d4d\u200d \u0d38\u0d39\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a \u0d2f\u0d41\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d27\u0d2e\u0d47\u0d24\u0d4d, \u0d35\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d\u0d37\u0d2e\u0d47\u0d24\u0d4d ?\r\n\u0d30\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d3e\u0d02 \u0d24\u0d31\u0d48\u0d28\u0d4d\u200d, 119257. \u0d2e\u0d42\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d3e\u0d02 \u0d2c\u0d41\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d27\u0d2e\u0d24\u0d38\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d47\u0d33\u0d28\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d05\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d27\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d37\u0d28\u0d4d\u200d \u0d06\u0d30\u0d4d ?",
    "answer": "\u0d2e\u0d4a\u0d17\u0d3e\u0d32\u0d3f\u0d2a\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d24\u0d40\u0d38",
    "status": "2"
  },
  {
    "id": "988",
    "question": "\u0d09\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d30\u0d47\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d05\u0d35\u0d38\u0d3e\u0d28 \u0d39\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d26\u0d41 \u0d30\u0d3e\u0d1c\u0d3e\u0d35\u0d4d \u0d06\u0d30\u0d4d ?",
    "answer": "\u0d39\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d\u0d37\u0d35\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d27\u0d28\u0d28\u0d4d\u200d",
    "status": "2"
  },
  {
    "id": "989",
    "question": "\u0d2c\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d2d\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d28\u0d4d\u200d \u0d05\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d46\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d2e\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4a\u0d30\u0d41 \u0d2a\u0d47\u0d30\u0d4d ?",
    "answer": "\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d37\u0d4d\u0d23\u0d41\u0d17\u0d4b\u0d2a\u0d28\u0d4d\u200d",
    "status": "2"
  },
  {
    "id": "990",
    "question": "\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d26\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d30\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d3e\u0d02 \u0d24\u0d32\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d02 ?\r\n",
    "answer": "\u0d09\u0d1c\u0d4d\u0d1c\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d3f",
    "status": "2"
  },
  {
    "id": "991",
    "question": "2010 \u0d36\u0d15\u0d35\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d\u0d37\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d02 \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d35\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d\u0d37\u0d02 ?",
    "answer": "1932",
    "status": "2"
  },
  {
    "id": "992",
    "question": "\u0d1a\u0d47\u0d30\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d24\u0d32\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d02 ?",
    "answer": "\u0d35\u0d3e\u0d1e\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d3f",
    "status": "2"
  },
  {
    "id": "993",
    "question": "\u0d36\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d40 \u0d2c\u0d41\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d27\u0d28\u0d4d\u200d \u0d38\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d27\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d2f \u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d32\u0d02 ?",
    "answer": "\u0d15\u0d41\u0d36\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d17\u0d30\u0d02, BC 483",
    "status": "2"
  },
  {
    "id": "994",
    "question": "\u0d24\u0d33\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4b\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f \u0d2f\u0d41\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d27\u0d02 \u0d28\u0d1f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d35\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d\u0d37\u0d02 ?",
    "answer": "1565",
    "status": "2"
  },
  {
    "id": "995",
    "question": "\u0d36\u0d24\u0d35\u0d3e\u0d39\u0d28\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d3e\u0d2a\u0d15\u0d28\u0d4d\u200d ?",
    "answer": "\u0d38\u0d3f\u0d2e\u0d41\u0d16\u0d28\u0d4d\u200d",
    "status": "2"
  },
  {
    "id": "996",
    "question": "\u0d1c\u0d38\u0d3f\u0d2f \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d28\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d41\u0d24\u0d3f \u0d2a\u0d41\u0d28\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d02\u0d2d\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a \u0d2e\u0d41\u0d17\u0d33\u0d4d\u200d \u0d30\u0d3e\u0d1c\u0d3e\u0d35\u0d4d ?",
    "answer": "\u0d14\u0d31\u0d02\u0d17\u0d38\u0d40\u0d2c\u0d4d",
    "status": "2"
  },
  {
    "id": "997",
    "question": "\u0d05\u0d36\u0d4b\u0d15 \u0d36\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d3e\u0d38\u0d28\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4d\u200d \u0d0f\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d35\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d35\u0d32\u0d41\u0d24\u0d4d ?",
    "answer": "13",
    "status": "2"
  },
  {
    "id": "998",
    "question": "\u0d1c\u0d38\u0d3f\u0d2f \u0d28\u0d3f\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d32\u0d3e\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d4d ?",
    "answer": "\u0d05\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d2c\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d",
    "status": "2"
  },
  {
    "id": "999",
    "question": "\u0d2e\u0d39\u0d3e\u0d1c\u0d28\u0d2a\u0d26\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d19\u0d33\u0d4d\u200d \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d46\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d30\u0d3e\u0d1c\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d19\u0d33\u0d4d\u200d \u0d0e\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30 ?",
    "answer": "16",
    "status": "2"
  },
  {
    "id": "1000",
    "question": "\u0d12\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d3e\u0d02 \u0d2a\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d3f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d2f\u0d41\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d27\u0d02 \u0d28\u0d1f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d35\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d\u0d37\u0d02 ?",
    "answer": "1526",
    "status": "2"
  },
  {
    "id": "1001",
    "question": "\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d32\u0d3e\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d38\u0d3f \u0d2f\u0d41\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d27\u0d02 \u0d28\u0d1f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d06\u0d30\u0d46\u0d32\u0d4d\u0d32\u0d3e\u0d02 \u0d24\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4d\u200d ?",
    "answer": "\u0d31\u0d4b\u0d2c\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d4d \u0d15\u0d4d\u0d32\u0d48\u0d35\u0d4d, \u0d38\u0d3f\u0d31\u0d3e\u0d1c\u0d4d \u0d09\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d26\u0d57\u0d33",
    "status": "2"
  },
  {
    "id": "1002",
    "question": "\u0d32\u0d4b\u0d27\u0d3f \u0d35\u0d02\u0d36\u0d02 \u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d3e\u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d4d ?",
    "answer": "\u0d2c\u0d39\u0d32\u0d42\u0d32\u0d4d\u200d \u0d32\u0d4b\u0d27\u0d3f",
    "status": "2"
  },
  {
    "id": "1003",
    "question": "\u0d2e\u0d4b\u0d39\u0d28\u0d4d\u200d \u0d1c\u0d26\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d4b \u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d28\u0d26\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d30\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4d\u200d ?",
    "answer": "\u0d38\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d27\u0d41",
    "status": "2"
  },
  {
    "id": "1004",
    "question": "\u0d07\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4d\u200d \u0d06\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d3f \u0d15\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d4b\u0d33 \u0d28\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d23\u0d35\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d35\u0d3f\u0d32 \u0d28\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d23\u0d35\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d0f\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d46\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d06\u0d30\u0d4d ?",
    "answer": "\u0d05\u0d32\u0d3e\u0d35\u0d41\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d26\u0d40\u0d28\u0d4d\u200d \u0d16\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4d\u200d\u0d1c\u0d3f",
    "status": "2"
  },
  {
    "id": "1005",
    "question": "\u0d07\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4d \u0d2a\u0d41\u0d31\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d24\u0d32\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3f \u0d2d\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a \u0d30\u0d3e\u0d1c\u0d3e\u0d35\u0d4d ?",
    "answer": "\u0d15\u0d28\u0d3f\u0d37\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d28\u0d4d\u200d",
    "status": "2"
  },
  {
    "id": "1006",
    "question": "\u0d07\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d2f\u0d46 \u0d06\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d2e\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a \u0d06\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f \u0d05\u0d31\u0d2c\u0d4d \u0d2d\u0d30\u0d23\u0d3e\u0d27\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d3f ?",
    "answer": "\u0d2e\u0d41\u0d39\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d26\u0d4d \u0d2c\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u200d \u0d15\u0d3e\u0d38\u0d3f\u0d02",
    "status": "2"
  },
  {
    "id": "1007",
    "question": "\u0d12\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d3e\u0d02 \u0d2c\u0d41\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d27\u0d2e\u0d24\u0d38\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d47\u0d33\u0d28\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d05\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d27\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d37\u0d28\u0d4d\u200d \u0d06\u0d30\u0d4d ?",
    "answer": "\u0d2e\u0d39\u0d3e\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d36\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d2a\u0d28\u0d4d\u200d",
    "status": "2"
  },
  {
    "id": "1008",
    "question": "\u0d39\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d\u0d37\u0d35\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d27\u0d28\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d2d\u0d30\u0d23\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d32\u0d18\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d02 ?",
    "answer": "606 \u2013 647",
    "status": "2"
  },
  {
    "id": "1009",
    "question": "\u0d1a\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d3e\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d3f \u0d12\u0d30\u0d41 \u0d39\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d26\u0d41 \u0d30\u0d3e\u0d1c\u0d15\u0d41\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d46 \u0d35\u0d3f\u0d35\u0d3e\u0d39\u0d02 \u0d1a\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d4d\u0d24 \u0d2e\u0d41\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d32\u0d40\u0d02 \u0d2d\u0d30\u0d23\u0d3e\u0d27\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d3f ?",
    "answer": "\u0d05\u0d32\u0d3e\u0d35\u0d41\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d26\u0d40\u0d28\u0d4d\u200d \u0d16\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4d\u200d\u0d1c\u0d3f",
    "status": "2"
  },
  {
    "id": "1010",
    "question": "\u0d15\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d1c\u0d28\u0d4d\u200d \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d46\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d06\u0d30\u0d4d ?",
    "answer": "\u0d38\u0d2e\u0d41\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d30 \u0d17\u0d41\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d28\u0d4d\u200d",
    "status": "2"
  },
  {
    "id": "1011",
    "question": "\u0d30\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d3e\u0d02 \u0d05\u0d36\u0d4b\u0d15\u0d28\u0d4d\u200d ?",
    "answer": "\u0d15\u0d28\u0d3f\u0d37\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d28\u0d4d\u200d",
    "status": "2"
  },
  {
    "id": "1012",
    "question": "\u0d2a\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d21\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d30\u0d3e\u0d1c\u0d15\u0d40\u0d2f \u0d2e\u0d41\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d30 ?",
    "answer": "\u0d15\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d2e\u0d40\u0d28\u0d4d\u200d",
    "status": "2"
  },
  {
    "id": "1013",
    "question": "\u0d12\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d3e\u0d02 \u0d2c\u0d41\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d27\u0d2e\u0d24 \u0d38\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d47\u0d33\u0d28\u0d02 \u0d28\u0d1f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d32\u0d02 ?",
    "answer": "\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d1c\u0d17\u0d43\u0d39\u0d02, BC 483",
    "status": "2"
  },
  {
    "id": "1014",
    "question": "\u0d06\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d27\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d2d\u0d4b\u0d1c\u0d28\u0d4d\u200d \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d46\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d4d ?",
    "answer": "\u0d15\u0d43\u0d37\u0d4d\u0d23\u0d26\u0d47\u0d35\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d",
    "status": "2"
  },
  {
    "id": "1015",
    "question": "\u0d36\u0d24\u0d35\u0d3e\u0d39\u0d28\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d \u0d05\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d46\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d3f\u0d30\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d24\u0d4d ?",
    "answer": "\u0d06\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d27\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d1c\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d",
    "status": "2"
  },
  {
    "id": "1016",
    "question": "\u0d14\u0d31\u0d02\u0d17\u0d38\u0d40\u0d2c\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d36\u0d35\u0d15\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d40\u0d30\u0d02 \u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d24\u0d4d ?",
    "answer": "\u0d26\u0d57\u0d32\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d2c\u0d3e\u0d26\u0d4d",
    "status": "2"
  },
  {
    "id": "1017",
    "question": "\u0d16\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d35\u0d47\u0d32\u0d28\u0d41\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d3f \u0d2c\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d27\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d46\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f \u0d36\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d3e\u0d32\u0d47\u0d16 ?",
    "answer": "\u0d39\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d15\u0d41\u0d02\u0d2d \u0d36\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d3e\u0d32\u0d47\u0d16",
    "status": "2"
  },
  {
    "id": "1018",
    "question": "\u0d05\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d2c\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d \u0d28\u0d3e\u0d2e \u0d30\u0d1a\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d4d ?",
    "answer": "\u0d05\u0d2c\u0d41\u0d33\u0d4d\u200d \u0d2b\u0d48\u0d38\u0d32\u0d4d\u200d",
    "status": "2"
  },
  {
    "id": "1019",
    "question": "\u0d2c\u0d41\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d27\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d2e\u0d39\u0d3e\u0d35\u0d40\u0d30\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d38\u0d3e\u0d2e\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d32\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d28\u0d3e\u0d2f \u0d30\u0d3e\u0d1c\u0d3e\u0d35\u0d4d ?",
    "answer": "\u0d2c\u0d3f\u0d02\u0d2c\u0d3f\u0d38\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d28\u0d4d\u200d",
    "status": "2"
  },
  {
    "id": "1020",
    "question": "\u0d38\u0d42\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d \u0d35\u0d02\u0d36\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d05\u0d35\u0d38\u0d3e\u0d28 \u0d30\u0d3e\u0d1c\u0d3e\u0d35\u0d4d \u0d06\u0d30\u0d4d ?",
    "answer": "\u0d06\u0d26\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4d\u200d\u0d37\u0d3e \u0d38\u0d42\u0d30\u0d3f",
    "status": "2"
  },
  {
    "id": "1021",
    "question": "\u0d38\u0d46\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d \u0d1c\u0d4b\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d\u0d1c\u0d4d\u0d1c\u0d4d \u0d15\u0d4b\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f \u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d3f \u0d1a\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d24\u0d4d ?",
    "answer": "\u0d1a\u0d46\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d48",
    "status": "2"
  },
  {
    "id": "1022",
    "question": "\u0d05\u0d35\u0d38\u0d3e\u0d28 \u0d38\u0d2f\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d26\u0d4d \u0d30\u0d3e\u0d1c\u0d3e\u0d35\u0d4d \u0d06\u0d30\u0d4d ?",
    "answer": "\u0d05\u0d32\u0d3e\u0d35\u0d41\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d26\u0d40\u0d28\u0d4d\u200d \u0d06\u0d32\u0d02 \u0d37\u0d3e",
    "status": "2"
  },
  {
    "id": "1023",
    "question": "\u0d39\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a \u0d15\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d46\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d24\u0d4d ?",
    "answer": "\u0d26\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d31\u0d3e\u0d02 \u0d38\u0d3e\u0d39\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d3f",
    "status": "2"
  },
  {
    "id": "1024",
    "question": "\u0d05\u0d35\u0d38\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d46 \u0d05\u0d1f\u0d3f\u0d2e\u0d35\u0d02\u0d36 \u0d30\u0d3e\u0d1c\u0d3e\u0d35\u0d4d \u0d06\u0d30\u0d4d ?",
    "answer": "\u0d15\u0d48\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4b\u0d2c\u0d3e\u0d26\u0d4d",
    "status": "2"
  },
  {
    "id": "1025",
    "question": "\u0d2a\u0d41\u0d30\u0d41\u0d37\u0d2a\u0d41\u0d30\u0d02 \u0d07\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d4d \u0d05\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d46\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d24\u0d4d ?",
    "answer": "\u0d2a\u0d46\u0d37\u0d35\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d",
    "status": "2"
  },
  {
    "id": "1026",
    "question": "\u0d24\u0d31\u0d48\u0d28\u0d4d\u200d \u0d2f\u0d41\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d27\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4d\u200d \u0d0f\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d46\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f \u0d2d\u0d30\u0d23\u0d3e\u0d27\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d33\u0d4d\u200d ?",
    "answer": "\u0d17\u0d4b\u0d31\u0d3f, \u0d2a\u0d43\u0d25\u0d4d\u0d35\u0d40\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d1c\u0d4d \u0d1a\u0d57\u0d39\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d4d\u200d",
    "status": "2"
  },
  {
    "id": "1027",
    "question": "\u0d24\u0d25\u0d3e\u0d17\u0d24\u0d28\u0d4d\u200d \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d46\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d4d ?",
    "answer": "\u0d36\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d40 \u0d2c\u0d41\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d27\u0d28\u0d4d\u200d",
    "status": "2"
  },
  {
    "id": "1028",
    "question": "\u0d35\u0d3e\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d1f \u0d35\u0d02\u0d36 \u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d3e\u0d2a\u0d15\u0d28\u0d4d\u200d ?",
    "answer": "\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d27\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d36\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f",
    "status": "2"
  },
  {
    "id": "1029",
    "question": "\u0d05\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d2c\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d46 \u0d2d\u0d30\u0d23\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d19\u0d33\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4d\u200d \u0d38\u0d39\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d06\u0d30\u0d4d ?",
    "answer": "\u0d2c\u0d48\u0d31\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d4d\u200d\u0d16\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d4d\u200d",
    "status": "2"
  },
  {
    "id": "1030",
    "question": "\u0d38\u0d2e\u0d41\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d30 \u0d17\u0d41\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d2e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d30\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d2c\u0d41\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d27\u0d2a\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d21\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d28\u0d4d\u200d \u0d06\u0d30\u0d4d ?",
    "answer": "\u0d35\u0d38\u0d41\u0d2c\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d27\u0d41",
    "status": "2"
  },
  {
    "id": "1063",
    "question": "\u0d17\u0d23\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d36\u0d3e\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30 \u0d35\u0d7c\u0d37\u0d02",
    "answer": "2012",
    "status": "5"
  },
  {
    "id": "1064",
    "question": "\u0d17\u0d23\u0d3f\u0d24 \u0d36\u0d3e\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d26\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d02",
    "answer": "\u0d21\u0d3f\u0d38\u0d02\u0d2c\u0d7c22",
    "status": "5"
  },
  {
    "id": "1065",
    "question": "\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d41\u0d1c\u0d7b \u0d1c\u0d28\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d35\u0d7c\u0d37\u0d02",
    "answer": "887 Dec:22",
    "status": "5"
  },
  {
    "id": "1066",
    "question": "\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d41\u0d1c\u0d7b \u0d38\u0d16\u0d4d\u0d2f",
    "answer": "1729",
    "status": "5"
  },
  {
    "id": "1067",
    "question": "\u0d17\u0d23\u0d3f\u0d24 \u0d36\u0d3e\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d35\u0d4d",
    "answer": "\u0d2a\u0d48\u0d25\u0d17\u0d4b\u0d31\u0d38\u0d4d",
    "status": "5"
  },
  {
    "id": "1068",
    "question": "\u0d06\u0d27\u0d41\u0d28\u0d3f\u0d15 \u0d17\u0d23\u0d3f\u0d24 \u0d36\u0d3e\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d35\u0d4d",
    "answer": "\u0d31\u0d46\u0d28\u0d46 \u0d26\u0d46\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d7c\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d46",
    "status": "5"
  },
  {
    "id": "1069",
    "question": "\u0d1c\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d2e\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d35\u0d4d",
    "answer": "\u0d2f\u0d42\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d32\u0d3f\u0d21\u0d4d",
    "status": "5"
  },
  {
    "id": "1070",
    "question": "\u0d2f\u0d42\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d32\u0d3f\u0d21\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d17\u0d23\u0d3f\u0d24 \u0d36\u0d3e\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30 \u0d17\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d02",
    "answer": "\u0d0e\u0d32\u0d2e\u0d46\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d38\u0d4d",
    "status": "5"
  },
  {
    "id": "1071",
    "question": "\u0d17\u0d23\u0d3f\u0d24 \u0d36\u0d3e\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d2c\u0d48\u0d2c\u0d3f\u0d7e",
    "answer": "\u0d0e\u0d32\u0d2e\u0d46\u0d7b\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d38\u0d4d",
    "status": "5"
  },
  {
    "id": "1072",
    "question": "\u0d2d\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d24\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d2f\u0d42\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d32\u0d3f\u0d21\u0d4d",
    "answer": "\u0d2d\u0d3e\u0d38\u0d15\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d1a\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d7b ",
    "status": "5"
  },
  {
    "id": "1073",
    "question": "\u0d17\u0d23\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d02 \u0d09\u0d2a\u0d2f\u0d4b\u0d17\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d41\u0d33\u0d4d\u0d33 \u0d1a\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30 \u0d2a\u0d20\u0d28 \u0d36\u0d3e\u0d16",
    "answer": "\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d32\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d4b\u0d2e\u0d46\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d38\u0d4d",
    "status": "5"
  },
  {
    "id": "1074",
    "question": "\u0d2d\u0d42\u0d2e\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d1a\u0d41\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d33\u0d35\u0d4d \u0d15\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d41 \u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d1f\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d4d?",
    "answer": "\u0d07\u0d31\u0d3e\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4b \u0d38\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d28\u0d40\u0d38\u0d4d",
    "status": "5"
  },
  {
    "id": "1075",
    "question": "\u0d07\u0d31\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4b \u0d38\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d28\u0d40\u0d38\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d05\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d41\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d3f \u0d2c\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d27\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d46\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d3f\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d24\u0d4d",
    "answer": "\u0d05\u0d2d\u0d3e\u0d1c\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d38\u0d02\u0d16\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d15\u0d7e",
    "status": "5"
  },
  {
    "id": "1076",
    "question": "\u0d17\u0d23\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d06\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d19\u0d7e",
    "answer": "\u0d05\u0d2d\u0d3e\u0d1c\u0d4d\u0d2f \u0d38\u0d02\u0d16\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d15\u0d7e",
    "status": "5"
  },
  {
    "id": "1077",
    "question": "\u0d2a\u0d42\u0d1c\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d02 \u0d15\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d41 \u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d1f\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d24\u0d4d",
    "answer": "\u0d07\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d7c",
    "status": "5"
  },
  {
    "id": "1078",
    "question": "\u0d2a\u0d42\u0d1c\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d46 \u0d2a\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d3f \u0d06\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d3f \u0d2a\u0d20\u0d28\u0d02 \u0d28\u0d1f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d2f \u0d2d\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d24\u0d40\u0d2f \u0d17\u0d23\u0d3f\u0d24 \u0d36\u0d3e\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d1c\u0d4d\u0d1e\u0d7b?",
    "answer": "\u0d2c\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d39\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d2a\u0d41\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d7b",
    "status": "5"
  },
  {
    "id": "1079",
    "question": "\u0d38\u0d3e\u0d39\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d \u0d28\u0d4b\u0d2c\u0d7d \u0d38\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d02 \u0d28\u0d47\u0d1f\u0d3f\u0d2f \u0d17\u0d23\u0d3f\u0d24 \u0d36\u0d3e\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d1c\u0d4d\u0d1e\u0d7b",
    "answer": "\u0d2c\u0d7c\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d \u0d31\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d38\u0d7d",
    "status": "5"
  },
  {
    "id": "1080",
    "question": "\u0d17\u0d23\u0d02 \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d06\u0d36\u0d2f\u0d02 \u0d06\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d37\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d24\u0d4d",
    "answer": "\u0d1c\u0d4b\u0d7c\u0d1c\u0d4d \u0d15\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d7c",
    "status": "5"
  },
  {
    "id": "1081",
    "question": "\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4b\u0d23\u0d2e\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d3f \u0d15\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d41 \u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d1f\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d24\u0d4d",
    "answer": "\u0d39\u0d3f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d3e\u0d7c\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d38\u0d4d",
    "status": "5"
  },
  {
    "id": "1082",
    "question": "\u0d38\u0d2e\u0d1a\u0d3f\u0d39\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d02 \u0d15\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d41 \u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d1f\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d24\u0d4d",
    "answer": "\u0d31\u0d4b\u0d2c\u0d7c\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d4d \u0d31\u0d46\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4b\u0d7c\u0d21\u0d46",
    "status": "5"
  },
  {
    "id": "1083",
    "question": "\u0d05\u0d27\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d02(+),\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d42\u0d28\u0d02(-)\u0d1a\u0d3f\u0d39\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d19\u0d7e \u0d15\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d41 \u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d1f\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d24\u0d4d",
    "answer": "\u0d1c\u0d4b\u0d39\u0d7b \u0d35\u0d3f\u0d21\u0d4d\u0d21\u0d4d \u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d7b",
    "status": "5"
  },
  {
    "id": "1084",
    "question": "\u0d17\u0d23\u0d3f\u0d24 \u0d36\u0d3e\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d30\u0d3e\u0d1c\u0d15\u0d41\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d7b",
    "answer": "\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d31\u0d7d \u0d2b\u0d46\u0d21\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d \u0d17\u0d57\u0d38\u0d4d",
    "status": "5"
  },
  {
    "id": "1085",
    "question": "\u0d17\u0d23\u0d3f\u0d24 \u0d36\u0d3e\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d2d\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d24\u0d40\u0d2f \u0d30\u0d3e\u0d1c\u0d15\u0d41\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d7b",
    "answer": "\u0d06\u0d30\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d2d\u0d1f\u0d7b",
    "status": "5"
  },
  {
    "id": "1086",
    "question": "\u0d12\u0d30\u0d41 \u0d2d\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d2f \u0d17\u0d23\u0d3f\u0d24 \u0d36\u0d3e\u0d38\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d1c\u0d4d\u0d1e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31 \u0d28\u0d3e\u0d2e\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d41\u0d33\u0d4d\u0d33 \u0d15\u0d43\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d2e \u0d09\u0d2a\u0d17\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d39\u0d02",
    "answer": "\u0d06\u0d30\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d2d\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f",
    "status": "5"
  },
  {
    "id": "1087",
    "question": "\u0d2e\u0d28\u0d41\u0d37\u0d4d\u0d2f \u0d15\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d42\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d7c \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d2a\u0d47\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d46\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d35\u0d28\u0d3f\u0d24",
    "answer": "\u0d36\u0d15\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d33\u0d3e \u0d26\u0d47\u0d35\u0d3f",
    "status": "5"
  },
  {
    "id": "1088",
    "question": "\u0d38\u0d02\u0d16\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d15\u0d33\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d2a\u0d41\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d15\u0d02 \u0d0e\u0d34\u0d41\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d24\u0d4d",
    "answer": "\u0d36\u0d15\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d33\u0d3e \u0d26\u0d47\u0d35\u0d3f",
    "status": "5"
  },
  {
    "id": "1089",
    "question": "\u0d12\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4b\u0d1f\u0d4a\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d02 100 \u0d2a\u0d42\u0d1c\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d02 \u0d1a\u0d47\u0d7c\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d41 \u0d35\u0d30\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d38\u0d02\u0d16\u0d4d\u0d2f",
    "answer": "\u0d17\u0d42\u0d17\u0d4b\u0d7e",
    "status": "5"
  },
  {
    "id": "1090",
    "question": "1\u0d28\u0d41\u0d02 100 \u0d28\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d07\u0d1f\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d41\u0d33\u0d4d\u0d33 \u0d05\u0d2d\u0d3e\u0d1c\u0d4d\u0d2f \u0d38\u0d02\u0d16\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d15\u0d33\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d0e\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d23\u0d02",
    "answer": "25",
    "status": "5"
  },
  {
    "id": "1091",
    "question": "10 \u0d35\u0d30\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d33\u0d4d\u0d33 \u0d0e\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d23\u0d7d \u0d38\u0d02\u0d16\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d15\u0d33\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d24\u0d41\u0d15",
    "answer": "55 ( \u0d28\u0d42\u0d31\u0d4d \u0d35\u0d30\u0d46 5050)\r\n",
    "status": "5"
  },
  {
    "id": "1092",
    "question": "\u0d28\u0d42\u0d31\u0d4d \u0d35\u0d30\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d33\u0d4d\u0d33 \u0d38\u0d02\u0d16\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d15\u0d33\u0d3f\u0d7d \u0d0e\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30 9\u0d15\u0d7e \u0d09\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d4d",
    "answer": "20",
    "status": "5"
  },
  {
    "id": "1093",
    "question": "\u0d31\u0d4b\u0d2e\u0d7b \u0d30\u0d40\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d7d \u0d0e\u0d34\u0d41\u0d24\u0d41\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d4b\u0d7e \u0d09\u0d2a\u0d2f\u0d4b\u0d17\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24 \u0d38\u0d02\u0d16\u0d4d\u0d2f",
    "answer": "\u0d2a\u0d42\u0d1c\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d02",
    "status": "5"
  },
  {
    "id": "1094",
    "question": "\u0d2a\u0d48 (\u03c0)\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d2e\u0d42\u0d32\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d02",
    "answer": " 3.14 ( 22\/7)",
    "status": "5"
  },
  {
    "id": "1095",
    "question": "\u0d17\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d2b\u0d4d \u0d15\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d46\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d24\u0d4d",
    "answer": "\u0d26\u0d46\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d7c\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d46",
    "status": "5"
  },
  {
    "id": "1096",
    "question": "10 \u0d05\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d19\u0d33\u0d41\u0d33\u0d4d\u0d33 \u0d38\u0d02\u0d16\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d38\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d26\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d02 ",
    "answer": "\u0d26\u0d36\u0d3e\u0d02\u0d36 \u0d38\u0d02\u0d16\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d38\u0d2c\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d26\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d02",
    "status": "5"
  },
  {
    "id": "1097",
    "question": "2 \u0d05\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d19\u0d7e \u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d2e\u0d41\u0d33\u0d4d\u0d33 \u0d38\u0d02\u0d16\u0d4d\u0d2f \u0d38\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d26\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d02 \u2018 ",
    "answer": "\u0d2c\u0d48\u0d28\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d38\u0d02\u0d16\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d38\u0d2c\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d26\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d02",
    "status": "5"
  },
  {
    "id": "1098",
    "question": "\u0d2c\u0d48\u0d28\u0d31\u0d3f \u0d38\u0d02\u0d16\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d38\u0d2c\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d26\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d05\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d19\u0d7e",
    "answer": "0 & 1",
    "status": "5"
  },
  {
    "id": "1099",
    "question": "\"Mathematics\" \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d35\u0d3e\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4d \u0d30\u0d42\u0d2a\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d46\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d24\u0d4d ?\r\n",
    "answer": "\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31 (\u0d17\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d40\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4d) ( \u0d2a\u0d20\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a \u0d38\u0d02\u0d17\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d33\u0d4d\u200d \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d02 )\r\n",
    "status": "5"
  },
  {
    "id": "1100",
    "question": "\u0d32\u0d4b\u0d17\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d02 \u0d2a\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d09\u0d2a\u0d1c\u0d4d\u0d1e\u0d3e\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d35\u0d4d ?",
    "answer": "\u0d1c\u0d4b\u0d23\u0d4d\u200d \u0d28\u0d47\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d",
    "status": "5"
  },
  {
    "id": "1101",
    "question": "\u0d12\u0d30\u0d41 \u0d38\u0d2e\u0d1a\u0d24\u0d41\u0d30\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u200d\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d35\u0d3f\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d40\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d23\u0d35\u0d41\u0d02, \u0d1a\u0d41\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d33\u0d35\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d24\u0d41\u0d32\u0d43\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d3f \u0d35\u0d30\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d0f\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d35\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d1a\u0d46\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d2f \u0d38\u0d02\u0d16\u0d43 ?",
    "answer": "16",
    "status": "5"
  },
  {
    "id": "1102",
    "question": "\" \u0d32\u0d41\u0d21\u0d4b\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d\u0d2b\u0d4d \u0d28\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d\" \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d46\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d38\u0d02\u0d16\u0d43 ?",
    "answer": "\u0d2a\u0d48",
    "status": "5"
  },
  {
    "id": "1103",
    "question": "\u0d2a\u0d48 \u0d26\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d02 \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d4d ?",
    "answer": "\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d4d 14",
    "status": "5"
  },
  {
    "id": "1104",
    "question": "\u0d2e\u0d28\u0d41\u0d37\u0d43 \u0d15\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d43\u0d42\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d46\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d2d\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d24\u0d40\u0d2f \u0d17\u0d23\u0d3f\u0d24 \u0d36\u0d3e\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d1c\u0d4d\u0d1e ?",
    "answer": "\u0d36\u0d15\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d33 \u0d26\u0d47\u0d35\u0d3f",
    "status": "5"
  },
  {
    "id": "1105",
    "question": "\u0d32\u0d4b\u0d15\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d06\u0d26\u0d43 \u0d17\u0d23\u0d3f\u0d24 \u0d36\u0d3e\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d1c\u0d4d\u0d1e ?",
    "answer": "\u0d39\u0d3f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d47\u0d37\u0d43",
    "status": "5"
  },
  {
    "id": "1106",
    "question": "\u0d17\u0d23\u0d3f\u0d24 \u0d36\u0d3e\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30 \u0d28\u0d4a\u0d2c\u0d47\u0d32\u0d4d\u200d ?\r\n",
    "answer": "\u0d2b\u0d40\u0d32\u0d4d\u200d\u0d21\u0d4d\u0d38\u0d4d \u0d2e\u0d46\u0d21\u0d32\u0d4d\u200d\r\n",
    "status": "5"
  },
  {
    "id": "1107",
    "question": " \"Zeero\" \u0d07\u0d32\u0d4d\u0d32\u0d3e\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24 \u0d38\u0d02\u0d16\u0d43\u0d28\u0d41 \u0d38\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d26\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d02 ?",
    "answer": "\u0d31\u0d4b\u0d2e\u0d28\u0d4d\u200d \u0d38\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d26\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d02\r\n",
    "status": "5"
  },
  {
    "id": "1108",
    "question": "\u0d17\u0d23\u0d3f\u0d24 \u0d36\u0d3e\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d30\u0d3e\u0d1c\u0d15\u0d41\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d28\u0d4d\u200d ?",
    "answer": "\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d33\u0d4d\u200d \u0d2b\u0d46\u0d21\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d \u0d17\u0d4b\u0d38\u0d4d\r\n",
    "status": "5"
  },
  {
    "id": "1109",
    "question": "Google \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d46\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d38\u0d02\u0d16\u0d43 ?",
    "answer": " 10 race to 100\r\n",
    "status": "5"
  },
  {
    "id": "1110",
    "question": "\u0d38\u0d2e\u0d41\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d30 \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d46\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d38\u0d02\u0d16\u0d43 ?",
    "answer": "10 race to 9",
    "status": "5"
  },
  {
    "id": "1111",
    "question": "\u0d39\u0d30\u0d23 \u0d1a\u0d3f\u0d39\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d35\u0d41\u0d02, \u0d17\u0d41\u0d23\u0d28 \u0d1a\u0d3f\u0d39\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d35\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d06\u0d26\u0d43\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d3f \u0d09\u0d2a\u0d2f\u0d4b\u0d17\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a \u0d36\u0d3e\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d1c\u0d4d\u0d1e\u0d28\u0d4d\u200d ?",
    "answer": "\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4d\u0d32\u0d43\u0d02 \u0d13\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d47\u0d21\u0d4d ",
    "status": "5"
  },
  {
    "id": "1112",
    "question": "\u0d2d\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d24\u0d40\u0d2f \u0d17\u0d23\u0d3f\u0d24 \u0d36\u0d3e\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u200d\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d35\u0d4d ?",
    "answer": "\u0d2d\u0d3e\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d1a\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d43",
    "status": "5"
  },
  {
    "id": "1113",
    "question": "\u0d2a\u0d3e\u0d32\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u200d\u0d21\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d4b\u0d02 \u0d38\u0d02\u0d16\u0d43",
    "answer": "\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d46\u0d34\u0d41\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d32\u0d41\u0d02, \u0d2e\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d46\u0d34\u0d41\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d32\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d12\u0d30\u0d47 \u0d38\u0d02\u0d16\u0d43.....\r\ni.e, 525, 323, 848.....",
    "status": "5"
  },
  {
    "id": "1114",
    "question": "\"\u0d38\u0d48\u0d2b\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d\" \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d46\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d38\u0d02\u0d16\u0d43 ?",
    "answer": "\u0d2a\u0d42\u0d1c\u0d43\u0d02",
    "status": "5"
  },
  {
    "id": "1115",
    "question": "\u0d2d\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d24\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d2f\u0d42\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d32\u0d3f\u0d21\u0d4d ?",
    "answer": "\u0d2d\u0d3e\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d1a\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d43",
    "status": "5"
  },
  {
    "id": "1116",
    "question": "Binomial \u0d38\u0d02\u0d16\u0d43\u0d28\u0d41 \u0d38\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d26\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u200d\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d35\u0d4d ?",
    "answer": "\u0d26\u0d3e\u0d32\u0d02\u0d2c\u0d47\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d",
    "status": "5"
  },
  {
    "id": "1117",
    "question": "\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4b\u0d23\u0d02-\u0d15\u0d4b\u0d23\u0d41\u0d15\u0d33\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d05\u0d33\u0d35\u0d41\u0d15\u0d33\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d24\u0d41\u0d15",
    "answer": "180\u00b0",
    "status": "5"
  },
  {
    "id": "1118",
    "question": "\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4b\u0d23\u0d02-\u0d1a\u0d41\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d33\u0d35\u0d4d?",
    "answer": " a + b + c ",
    "status": "5"
  },
  {
    "id": "1119",
    "question": "\u0d38\u0d2e\u0d2d\u0d41\u0d1c \u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4b\u0d23\u0d02.- \u0d1a\u0d41\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d33\u0d35\u0d4d =?",
    "answer": "3a ",
    "status": "5"
  },
  {
    "id": "1120",
    "question": " \u0d1a\u0d24\u0d41\u0d30\u0d02- \u0d1a\u0d41\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d33\u0d35\u0d4d =?",
    "answer": "2(\u0d28\u0d40\u0d33\u0d02+\u0d35\u0d40\u0d24\u0d3f)",
    "status": "5"
  },
  {
    "id": "1121",
    "question": "\u0d1a\u0d24\u0d41\u0d30\u0d02- \u0d35\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d7c\u0d23\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d19\u0d33\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d28\u0d40\u0d33\u0d02=?",
    "answer": " _____________--\r\n\u221a\u0d28\u0d40\u0d33\u0d02\u00b2+\u0d35\u0d40\u0d24\u0d3f\u00b2",
    "status": "5"
  },
  {
    "id": "1122",
    "question": "\u0d38\u0d2e\u0d1a\u0d24\u0d41\u0d30\u0d02-\u0d1a\u0d41\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d33\u0d35\u0d4d =?",
    "answer": "4a",
    "status": "5"
  },
  {
    "id": "1123",
    "question": "\u0d38\u0d2e\u0d1a\u0d24\u0d41\u0d30\u0d02-\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d7c\u0d23\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d19\u0d33\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d28\u0d40\u0d33\u0d02=?",
    "answer": "\u221a2a",
    "status": "5"
  },
  {
    "id": "1124",
    "question": "\u0d38\u0d3e\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24 \u0d30\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d02 (Parallogram)-\u0d1a\u0d41\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d33\u0d35\u0d4d =?",
    "answer": "2 (a+b) ",
    "status": "5"
  },
  {
    "id": "1125",
    "question": "\u0d32\u0d02\u0d2c\u0d15\u0d02(Trapezium)-\u0d1a\u0d41\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d33\u0d35\u0d4d=?",
    "answer": "Sum of Total Sides.",
    "status": "5"
  },
  {
    "id": "1126",
    "question": "\u0d35\u0d43\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d02 (Circle)-\u0d1a\u0d41\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d33\u0d35\u0d4d=?",
    "answer": "2\u03c0r",
    "status": "5"
  },
  {
    "id": "1127",
    "question": "\u0d35\u0d43\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d42\u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d15 (Cone)-\u0d35\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d02=?",
    "answer": "\u2153\u03c0r\u00b2h",
    "status": "5"
  },
  {
    "id": "1128",
    "question": "\u0d35\u0d43\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d02\u0d2d\u0d02(Cylinder) -\u0d35\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d02=?",
    "answer": "\u03c0r\u00b2h",
    "status": "5"
  },
  {
    "id": "1129",
    "question": "\u0d17\u0d4b\u0d33\u0d02 (Sphere).\u0d35\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d02=?",
    "answer": " \u2074\u2044\u2083\u03c0r\u00b3",
    "status": "5"
  },
  {
    "id": "1130",
    "question": "\u0d05\u0d7c\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d27\u0d17\u0d4b\u0d33\u0d02 (Hemisphere)-\u0d35\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d02=?",
    "answer": "\u00b2\u2044\u2083 \u03c0r\u00b3",
    "status": "5"
  },
  {
    "id": "1131",
    "question": "\u0d1a\u0d24\u0d41\u0d30\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f (Cuboid)-\u0d35\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d02=?",
    "answer": "\u0d28\u0d40\u0d33\u0d02x\u0d35\u0d40\u0d24\u0d3fx \u0d09\u0d2f\u0d30\u0d02",
    "status": "5"
  },
  {
    "id": "1132",
    "question": "\u0d1a\u0d24\u0d41\u0d30\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f (Cuboid)-\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d7c\u0d23\u0d02=?",
    "answer": "\u221a\u0d28\u0d40\u0d33\u0d02\u00b2+\u0d35\u0d40\u0d24\u0d3f\u00b2+\u0d09\u0d2f\u0d30\u0d02\u00b2",
    "status": "5"
  },
  {
    "id": "1133",
    "question": "\u0d38\u0d2e\u0d1a\u0d24\u0d41\u0d30\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f (Cube)-a \u0d35\u0d36\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d2f \u0d15\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d42\u0d2c\u0d41\u0d15\u0d7e:\u0d35\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d02=?",
    "answer": "a\u00b3",
    "status": "5"
  },
  {
    "id": "1134",
    "question": "\u0d38\u0d2e\u0d1a\u0d24\u0d41\u0d30\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f (Cube)- a \u0d2a\u0d3e\u0d26\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d2f \u0d15\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d42\u0d2c\u0d41\u0d15\u0d7e:\u0d35\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d02=?",
    "answer": "a\u00b2h",
    "status": "5"
  },
  {
    "id": "1135",
    "question": "\u0d10\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d37\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d30 \u0d38\u0d2d\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d47\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d41\u0d33\u0d4d\u0d33 \u0d06\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f \u0d07\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d7b \u0d38\u0d02\u0d18\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d46 \u0d05\u0d2f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a \u0d06\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f \u0d2e\u0d32\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d33\u0d3f ?",
    "answer": "\u0d38\u0d7c\u0d26\u0d3e\u0d7c \u0d15\u0d46 \u0d0e\u0d02 \u0d2a\u0d23\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d7c ",
    "status": "10"
  },
  {
    "id": "1136",
    "question": "\u0d15\u0d4a\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d3f\u0d2e\u0d39\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d1c\u0d3e\u0d35\u0d4d \u0d15\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d15\u0d7b \u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d02 \u0d28\u0d7d\u0d15\u0d3f\u0d2f \u0d1c\u0d4d\u0d1e\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d2a\u0d40\u0d20\u0d02 \u0d1c\u0d47\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d35\u0d4d ?",
    "answer": "\u0d1c\u0d3f \u0d36\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d30\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d41\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d4d ",
    "status": "10"
  },
  {
    "id": "1137",
    "question": "\u0d07\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d7d [ \u0d15\u0d4a\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d3f\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d1c\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d24\u0d4d ] \u0d05\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d36\u0d4d\u0d35\u0d3e\u0d38 \u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d40\u0d2e\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d02 \u0d35\u0d34\u0d3f \u0d2a\u0d41\u0d31\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d41\u0d2a\u0d4b\u0d2f \u0d06\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d46 \u0d24\u0d3f\u0d30\u0d1e\u0d4d\u0d1e\u0d46\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d46\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f \u0d2e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d3f ?",
    "answer": "\u0d21\u0d4b \u0d0e \u0d06\u0d7c \u0d2e\u0d47\u0d28\u0d4b\u0d7b",
    "status": "10"
  },
  {
    "id": "1138",
    "question": "\u0d06\u0d32\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d41\u0d34 \u0d24\u0d41\u0d31\u0d2e\u0d41\u0d16\u0d02 \u0d35\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d38\u0d3f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a \u0d24\u0d3f\u0d30\u0d41\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d02\u0d15\u0d42\u0d7c \u0d26\u0d3f\u0d35\u0d3e\u0d7b ?",
    "answer": "\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d1c\u0d3e \u0d15\u0d47\u0d36\u0d35\u0d26\u0d3e\u0d38\u0d4d ",
    "status": "10"
  },
  {
    "id": "1139",
    "question": "\u0d15\u0d4a\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d3f \u0d2b\u0d4b\u0d7c\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d4d \u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d \u0d28\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d7d \u0d35\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d35\u0d30\u0d4d\u0d37\u0d02 ?",
    "answer": "1964",
    "status": "10"
  },
  {
    "id": "1140",
    "question": "\u0d1f\u0d3f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d41 \u0d28\u0d46\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4b\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f \u0d06\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d2e\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d35\u0d30\u0d4d\u0d37\u0d02 ?",
    "answer": "\u0d0e \u0d21\u0d3f.1789 \r\n",
    "status": "10"
  },
  {
    "id": "1141",
    "question": "\u0d1c\u0d28\u0d15\u0d40\u0d2f \u0d15\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d36\u0d41\u0d15\u0d28\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d37\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d2e\u0d46\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d4d \u0d28\u0d3f\u0d30\u0d42\u0d2a\u0d15\u0d7c \u0d35\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d30\u0d41\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d2f \u0d15\u0d35\u0d3f ?",
    "answer": "\u0d15\u0d41\u0d1e\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d7b \u0d28\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d7c ",
    "status": "10"
  },
  {
    "id": "1142",
    "question": "\u0d15\u0d4a\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d3f \u0d38\u0d7c\u0d35\u0d15\u0d32\u0d3e\u0d36\u0d3e\u0d32\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d25\u0d2e \u0d35\u0d48\u0d38\u0d4d \u0d1a\u0d3e\u0d7b\u0d38\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d7c ?",
    "answer": "\u0d1c\u0d4b\u0d38\u0d2b\u0d4d \u0d2e\u0d41\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d36\u0d4d\u0d36\u0d47\u0d30\u0d3f ",
    "status": "10"
  },
  {
    "id": "1143",
    "question": "\u0d15\u0d47\u0d30\u0d33\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d06\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d46 \u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d47\u0d21\u0d4d \u0d2f\u0d42\u0d23\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d7b \u0d28\u0d47\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d35\u0d4d ?",
    "answer": "\u0d1c\u0d41\u0d2c\u0d4d\u0d2c \u0d30\u0d3e\u0d2e\u0d15\u0d43\u0d37\u0d4d\u0d23\u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d33\u0d4d\u0d33 ",
    "status": "10"
  },
  {
    "id": "1144",
    "question": "\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d4b\u0d38\u0d2b\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d7d \u0d38\u0d4a\u0d38\u0d48\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d06\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f \u0d36\u0d3e\u0d16 \u0d15\u0d47\u0d30\u0d33\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d7d \u0d06\u0d30\u0d02\u0d2d\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a \u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d32\u0d02 ?",
    "answer": "\u0d2a\u0d3e\u0d32\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d1f\u0d4d ",
    "status": "10"
  },
  {
    "id": "1145",
    "question": "\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d7c\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d21\u0d35\u0d7c\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2e \u0d21\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d7c \u0d24\u0d4b\u0d7d\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a \u0d2f\u0d41\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d27\u0d02 ?",
    "answer": "\u0d15\u0d41\u0d33\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d7d ",
    "status": "10"
  },
  {
    "id": "1146",
    "question": "\u0d15\u0d47\u0d30\u0d33\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d7d \u0d0f\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d35\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d15\u0d42\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d24\u0d7d \u0d15\u0d3e\u0d32\u0d3e\u0d35\u0d27\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d41\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d30\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d28\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d2e\u0d38\u0d2d ?",
    "answer": "\u0d28\u0d3e\u0d32\u0d3e\u0d02 \u0d28\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d2e\u0d38\u0d2d",
    "status": "10"
  },
  {
    "id": "1147",
    "question": "\u0d15\u0d47\u0d30\u0d33\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d7d \u0d0f\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d35\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d15\u0d42\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d24\u0d7d \u0d15\u0d3e\u0d32\u0d02 \u0d2e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d3f \u0d06\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d30\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d35\u0d28\u0d3f\u0d24 ?",
    "answer": "\u0d15\u0d46 \u0d06\u0d7c \u0d17\u0d57\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2e ",
    "status": "10"
  },
  {
    "id": "1148",
    "question": "\u0d15\u0d47\u0d30\u0d33\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d0f\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d35\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d24\u0d46\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d47\u0d2f\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d46 \u0d28\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d2e\u0d38\u0d2d\u0d3e\u0d2e\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d21\u0d32\u0d02 ?",
    "answer": "\u0d28\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d7b\u0d15\u0d30 ",
    "status": "10"
  },
  {
    "id": "1149",
    "question": "\u0d15\u0d47\u0d30\u0d33\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d7d \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d35\u0d7c\u0d37\u0d02 \u0d28\u0d1f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d24\u0d3f\u0d30\u0d1e\u0d4d\u0d1e\u0d46\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d7d \u0d0f\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d35\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d15\u0d42\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d24\u0d7d \u0d2a\u0d4b\u0d33\u0d3f\u0d19\u0d4d \u0d36\u0d24\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d02 \u0d30\u0d47\u0d16\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d46\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d33\u0d4d\u0d33\u0d24\u0d4d ?",
    "answer": "1960",
    "status": "10"
  },
  {
    "id": "1150",
    "question": "\u0d15\u0d47\u0d30\u0d33\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d06\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f \u0d28\u0d43\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24-\u0d28\u0d3e\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d2f \u0d2a\u0d41\u0d30\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d \u0d05\u0d7c\u0d39\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d24\u0d4d ?",
    "answer": "\u0d15\u0d32\u0d3e\u0d2e\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d21\u0d32\u0d02 \u0d38\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d2d\u0d3e\u0d2e",
    "status": "10"
  },
  {
    "id": "1151",
    "question": "\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d30\u0d41\u0d35\u0d28\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d2a\u0d41\u0d30\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d1c\u0d28\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d41\u0d15\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d1c\u0d7c\u0d2e\u0d28\u0d3f \u0d15\u0d47\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d3f \u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d35\u0d7c\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d41\u0d15\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d1a\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d4d\u0d24 \u0d35\u0d3f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d32\u0d35\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d3f ?",
    "answer": "\u0d21\u0d4b\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d7c \u0d1a\u0d46\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d15\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d2e\u0d7b\u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d33\u0d4d\u0d33",
    "status": "10"
  },
  {
    "id": "1152",
    "question": "\u0d15\u0d47\u0d30\u0d33\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d7d \u0d0f\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d35\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d15\u0d42\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d24\u0d7d \u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d35\u0d36\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d02 \u0d2e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d3f \u0d38\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d1c\u0d4d\u0d1e \u0d1a\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d4d\u0d24 \u0d28\u0d47\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d35\u0d4d ?",
    "answer": "\u0d15\u0d46\u0d0e\u0d02 \u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d3f",
    "status": "10"
  },
  {
    "id": "1153",
    "question": "\u0d15\u0d47\u0d30\u0d33\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d7d \u0d0f\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d35\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d15\u0d42\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d24\u0d7d \u0d15\u0d3e\u0d32\u0d02 \u0d2e\u0d41\u0d16\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d2e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d3f \u0d06\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d30\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d24\u0d4d ?",
    "answer": "\u0d05\u0d35\u0d41\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d26\u0d7c \u0d15\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d3f \u0d28\u0d39",
    "status": "10"
  },
  {
    "id": "1154",
    "question": "\u0d15\u0d47\u0d30\u0d33\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d7d \u0d1c\u0d28\u0d15\u0d40\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d38\u0d42\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d23\u0d02 \u0d09\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d18\u0d3e\u0d1f\u0d28\u0d02 \u0d1a\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d46\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f \u0d24\u0d40\u0d2f\u0d24\u0d3f ?",
    "answer": "1996 \u0d06\u0d17\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d 17",
    "status": "10"
  },
  {
    "id": "1155",
    "question": "\u0d15\u0d4a\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d05\u0d1f\u0d3f\u0d2e\u0d15\u0d7e\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4d \u0d38\u0d4d\u0d35\u0d3e\u0d24\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d02 \u0d32\u0d2d\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d35\u0d7c\u0d37\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d7d ?",
    "answer": "\u0d0e \u0d21\u0d3f 1854",
    "status": "10"
  },
  {
    "id": "1156",
    "question": "\u0d15\u0d47\u0d30\u0d33\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d7d \u0d2c\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d40\u0d37\u0d4d \u0d07\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d05\u0d1f\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d31 \u0d09\u0d32\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a \u0d35\u0d3f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d32\u0d35\u0d02 ?",
    "answer": "\u0d2a\u0d34\u0d36\u0d4d\u0d36\u0d3f \u0d35\u0d3f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d32\u0d35\u0d02",
    "status": "10"
  },
  {
    "id": "1157",
    "question": "\u0d15\u0d47\u0d30\u0d33\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d7d \u0d1c\u0d28\u0d15\u0d40\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d38\u0d42\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d23\u0d02 \u0d24\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d19\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d0e\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d02 \u0d2a\u0d1e\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d35\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d38\u0d30 \u0d2a\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d27\u0d24\u0d3f ?",
    "answer": "\u0d12\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d02",
    "status": "10"
  },
  {
    "id": "1158",
    "question": "\u0d15\u0d47\u0d30\u0d33\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d06\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d46 \u0d21\u0d3f\u0d1c\u0d3f\u0d2a\u0d3f \u0d06\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d30\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d41 ?",
    "answer": "\u0d1f\u0d3f \u0d05\u0d28\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24 \u0d36\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d30 \u0d05\u0d2f\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d7c",
    "status": "10"
  },
  {
    "id": "1159",
    "question": "\u0d15\u0d4a\u0d32\u0d4d\u0d32\u0d35\u0d7c\u0d37\u0d02 \u0d06\u0d30\u0d02\u0d2d\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d06\u0d30\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d15\u0d3e\u0d32\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d ?",
    "answer": "\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d1c\u0d36\u0d47\u0d16\u0d30 \u0d35\u0d7c\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2e",
    "status": "10"
  },
  {
    "id": "1160",
    "question": "\u0d1f\u0d3f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d41\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d7b\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d2d\u0d30\u0d23\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d32\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d35\u0d47\u0d23\u0d3e\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d30\u0d3e\u0d1c\u0d3e\u0d35\u0d4d \u0d06\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d30\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d41 ?",
    "answer": "\u0d27\u0d7c\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d1c\u0d3e\u0d35\u0d4d",
    "status": "10"
  },
  {
    "id": "1161",
    "question": "\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d30\u0d41\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d02\u0d15\u0d42\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d05\u0d35\u0d38\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d46 \u0d35\u0d28\u0d3f\u0d24 \u0d2d\u0d30\u0d23\u0d3e\u0d27\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d3f ?",
    "answer": "\u0d38\u0d47\u0d24\u0d41\u0d32\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d37\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d3f \u0d2d\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d4d",
    "status": "10"
  },
  {
    "id": "1162",
    "question": "\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d35\u0d3e\u0d2e\u0d3f \u0d1a\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d26\u0d7b \u0d31\u0d46 \u0d2a\u0d42\u0d7c\u0d35\u0d3e\u0d36\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d2e\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d2a\u0d47\u0d30\u0d4d ?",
    "answer": "\u0d2c\u0d3e\u0d32\u0d15\u0d43\u0d37\u0d4d\u0d23 \u0d2e\u0d47\u0d28\u0d4b\u0d7b",
    "status": "10"
  },
  {
    "id": "1163",
    "question": "\u0d15\u0d47\u0d30\u0d33\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d06\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d46 \u0d38\u0d4d\u0d35\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d4d\u0d2f \u0d2e\u0d46\u0d21\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d7d \u0d15\u0d4b\u0d33\u0d47\u0d1c\u0d4d ?",
    "answer": "\u0d1f\u0d3f \u0d21\u0d3f \u0d2e\u0d46\u0d21\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d7d \u0d15\u0d4b\u0d33\u0d47\u0d1c\u0d4d ,\u0d06\u0d32\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d41\u0d34",
    "status": "10"
  },
  {
    "id": "1164",
    "question": "\u0d15\u0d47\u0d30\u0d33\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d06\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d46 \u0d1f\u0d42\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d38\u0d02 \u0d35\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4d\u0d32\u0d47\u0d1c\u0d4d ?",
    "answer": "\u0d15\u0d41\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d33\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d19\u0d3f",
    "status": "10"
  },
  {
    "id": "1165",
    "question": "\u0d15\u0d47\u0d30\u0d33\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d06\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f \u0d2a\u0d4a\u0d24\u0d41\u0d24\u0d46\u0d30\u0d1e\u0d4d\u0d1e\u0d46\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d7d \u0d15\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d42\u0d23\u0d3f\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d \u0d2a\u0d3e\u0d7c\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d3f \u0d0e\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30 \u0d38\u0d40\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d \u0d28\u0d47\u0d1f\u0d3f ?",
    "answer": "60",
    "status": "10"
  },
  {
    "id": "1166",
    "question": "\u0d15\u0d47\u0d30\u0d33\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d06\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f \u0d2e\u0d46\u0d21\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d7d \u0d15\u0d4b\u0d33\u0d47\u0d1c\u0d4d ?",
    "answer": "\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d30\u0d41\u0d35\u0d28\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d2a\u0d41\u0d30\u0d02",
    "status": "10"
  },
  {
    "id": "1167",
    "question": "\u0d35\u0d3e\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4b\u0d21\u0d17\u0d3e\u0d2e \u0d06\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d02 \u0d07\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d7d \u0d35\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d35\u0d7c\u0d37\u0d02 ?",
    "answer": "\u0d0e \u0d21\u0d3f 1489",
    "status": "10"
  },
  {
    "id": "1168",
    "question": "\u0d0f\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d36\u0d24\u0d15\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d \u0d15\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d7b \u0d2e\u0d3f\u0d37\u0d23\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d7c \u0d15\u0d47\u0d30\u0d33\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d7d \u0d35\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d24\u0d4d ?",
    "answer": "\u0d0e \u0d21\u0d3f \u0d12\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d3e\u0d02 \u0d36\u0d24\u0d15\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d7d",
    "status": "10"
  },
  {
    "id": "1169",
    "question": "\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d30\u0d1e\u0d4d\u0d1e\u0d46\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d42\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d2e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d3f \u0d2a\u0d26\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d2f \u0d06\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f \u0d2e\u0d32\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d33\u0d3f ?",
    "answer": "\u0d15\u0d4b\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d19\u0d3e\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d4d \u0d2e\u0d7b\u0d2e\u0d47\u0d28\u0d4b\u0d7b",
    "status": "10"
  },
  {
    "id": "1170",
    "question": "\u0d2e\u0d2f\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d34\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d7d \u0d2b\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d1e\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d41\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d7c \u0d24\u0d3e\u0d35\u0d33\u0d2e\u0d41\u0d31\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d35\u0d7c\u0d37\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d7d ?",
    "answer": "\u0d0e \u0d21\u0d3f 1725",
    "status": "10"
  },
  {
    "id": "1171",
    "question": "\u0d15\u0d47\u0d30\u0d33\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d \u0d2e\u0d42\u0d32\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d35\u0d7c\u0d27\u0d3f\u0d24 \u0d28\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d41\u0d24\u0d3f \u0d28\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d2e\u0d02 \u0d28\u0d1f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d7d \u0d35\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d4d ?",
    "answer": "2005 \u0d0f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d7d 1",
    "status": "10"
  },
  {
    "id": "1172",
    "question": "\u0d2e\u0d42\u0d37\u0d15\u0d35\u0d02\u0d36\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d7d \u0d2a\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d2e\u0d7c\u0d36\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d15\u0d47\u0d30\u0d33\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d32\u0d02 ?",
    "answer": "\u0d15\u0d4b\u0d32\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d41\u0d28\u0d3e\u0d1f\u0d4d",
    "status": "10"
  },
  {
    "id": "1173",
    "question": "\u0d05\u0d2e\u0d47\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d7b \u0d2e\u0d4b\u0d21\u0d7d \u0d2d\u0d30\u0d23 \u0d38\u0d02\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d27\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d02 \u0d35\u0d3f\u0d2d\u0d3e\u0d35\u0d28\u0d02 \u0d1a\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d4d\u0d24 \u0d24\u0d3f\u0d30\u0d41\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d02\u0d15\u0d42\u0d7c \u0d26\u0d3f\u0d35\u0d3e\u0d7b ?",
    "answer": "\u0d38\u0d3f \u0d2a\u0d3f \u0d30\u0d3e\u0d2e\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d35\u0d3e\u0d2e\u0d3f \u0d05\u0d2f\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d7c",
    "status": "10"
  },
  {
    "id": "1174",
    "question": "\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d40\u0d15\u0d33\u0d47\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d7e \u0d2a\u0d41\u0d30\u0d41\u0d37\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d7c \u0d0e\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d23\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d7d \u0d15\u0d41\u0d31\u0d35\u0d41\u0d33\u0d4d\u0d33 \u0d07\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d7b \u0d38\u0d02\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d02 ?",
    "answer": "\u0d15\u0d47\u0d30\u0d33\u0d02",
    "status": "10"
  },
  {
    "id": "1175",
    "question": "\u0d0e \u0d21\u0d3f 644 \u0d15\u0d47\u0d30\u0d33\u0d02 \u0d38\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d26\u0d7c\u0d36\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a \u0d05\u0d31\u0d2c\u0d3f \u0d38\u0d1e\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d3f ?",
    "answer": "\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d32\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d \u0d2c\u0d3f\u0d7b \u0d26\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d3e\u0d7c",
    "status": "10"
  },
  {
    "id": "1176",
    "question": "\u0d0e\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d46 \u0d30\u0d3e\u0d1c\u0d3e\u0d35\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d30\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d36\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d7b \u0d24\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d41\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d7b ?",
    "answer": "\u0d15\u0d4a\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d3f",
    "status": "10"
  },
  {
    "id": "1177",
    "question": "\u0d17\u0d41\u0d30\u0d41\u0d35\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d42\u0d7c \u0d38\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d17\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d39 \u0d15\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d3f\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d38\u0d46\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d31\u0d3f \u0d06\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d30\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d41 ?",
    "answer": "\u0d15\u0d46 \u0d15\u0d47\u0d33\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d7b",
    "status": "10"
  },
  {
    "id": "1178",
    "question": "\u0d38\u0d41\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d40\u0d02 \u0d15\u0d4b\u0d1f\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d06\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d46 \u0d2e\u0d32\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d33\u0d3f \u0d1c\u0d21\u0d4d\u0d1c\u0d3f ?",
    "answer": "\u0d2a\u0d3e\u0d31\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d41\u0d33\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d19\u0d30 \u0d17\u0d4b\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d26\u0d2e\u0d47\u0d28\u0d4b\u0d7b",
    "status": "10"
  },
  {
    "id": "1179",
    "question": "\u0d15\u0d47\u0d30\u0d33\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d7d \u0d2a\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d37\u0d3f \u0d17\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d2e\u0d02 \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d46\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d24\u0d4d ?",
    "answer": "\u0d28\u0d42\u0d31\u0d28\u0d3e\u0d1f\u0d4d",
    "status": "10"
  },
  {
    "id": "1180",
    "question": "\u0d15\u0d47\u0d30\u0d33\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d7d \u0d17\u0d4d\u0d32\u0d3e\u0d38\u0d4d \u0d28\u0d3f\u0d7c\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d \u0d2a\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d2f \u0d35\u0d46\u0d33\u0d41\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24 \u0d2e\u0d23\u0d7d \u0d32\u0d2d\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d32\u0d02 ?",
    "answer": "\u0d06\u0d32\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d41\u0d34",
    "status": "10"
  },
  {
    "id": "1181",
    "question": "\u0d38\u0d41\u0d7d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d7b \u0d2c\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d47\u0d30\u0d3f \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d32 \u0d28\u0d3e\u0d2e\u0d02 \u0d06\u0d30\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d2a\u0d47\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d7d \u0d28\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d \u0d30\u0d42\u0d2a\u0d02 \u0d15\u0d4a\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d24\u0d4d ?",
    "answer": "\u0d1f\u0d3f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d41 \u0d38\u0d41\u0d7d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d7b",
    "status": "10"
  },
  {
    "id": "1182",
    "question": "\u0d2a\u0d31\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3f \u0d2a\u0d1f\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d33\u0d3f \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d15\u0d43\u0d24\u0d3f \u0d30\u0d1a\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d24\u0d4d ?",
    "answer": "\u0d38\u0d7c\u0d26\u0d3e\u0d7c \u0d15\u0d46 \u0d0e\u0d02 \u0d2a\u0d23\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d7c",
    "status": "10"
  },
  {
    "id": "1183",
    "question": "\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d26\u0d42\u0d30\u0d2a\u0d41\u0d30\u0d02 \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d4d \u0d38\u0d02\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d43\u0d24\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d7d \u0d2a\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d2e\u0d7c\u0d36\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d32\u0d02 ?",
    "answer": "\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d30\u0d41\u0d35\u0d28\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d2a\u0d41\u0d30\u0d02",
    "status": "10"
  },
  {
    "id": "1184",
    "question": "2011\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d38\u0d46\u0d7b\u0d38\u0d38\u0d4d \u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d02 \u0d15\u0d47\u0d30\u0d33\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d0f\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d35\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d15\u0d42\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d24\u0d7d \u0d1c\u0d28\u0d38\u0d02\u0d16\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d33\u0d4d\u0d33 \u0d1c\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4d\u0d32 ?",
    "answer": "\u0d2e\u0d32\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d41\u0d31\u0d02",
    "status": "10"
  },
  {
    "id": "1185",
    "question": "\u0d15\u0d47\u0d30\u0d33\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d7d \u0d0f\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d35\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d15\u0d42\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d24\u0d7d \u0d15\u0d41\u0d30\u0d41\u0d2e\u0d41\u0d33\u0d15\u0d4d \u0d09\u0d32\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d3e\u0d26\u0d3f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d1c\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4d\u0d32 ?",
    "answer": "\u0d07\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3f",
    "status": "10"
  },
  {
    "id": "1186",
    "question": "\u0d38\u0d3f\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d30\u0d4d \u0d05\u0d7d\u0d2b\u0d4b\u0d7a\u0d38\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d2d\u0d57\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d35\u0d36\u0d3f\u0d37\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d02 \u0d38\u0d42\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d37\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d24\u0d4d ?",
    "answer": "\u0d2d\u0d30\u0d23\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d19\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d02",
    "status": "10"
  },
  {
    "id": "1187",
    "question": "\u0d38\u0d7c\u0d26\u0d3e\u0d7c \u0d15\u0d46 \u0d0e\u0d02 \u0d2a\u0d23\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d30\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d2e\u0d41\u0d34\u0d41\u0d35\u0d7b \u0d2a\u0d47\u0d30\u0d4d ?",
    "answer": "\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d35\u0d3e\u0d32\u0d02 \u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d27\u0d35\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d23\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d7c",
    "status": "10"
  },
  {
    "id": "1188",
    "question": "\u0d17\u0d35\u0d7c\u0d23\u0d31\u0d3e\u0d2f \u0d06\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f \u0d2e\u0d32\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d33\u0d3f ?",
    "answer": "\u0d35\u0d3f \u0d2a\u0d3f \u0d2e\u0d47\u0d28\u0d4b\u0d7b",
    "status": "10"
  },
  {
    "id": "1189",
    "question": "\u0d26\u0d48\u0d35\u0d26\u0d36\u0d15\u0d02 \u0d30\u0d1a\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d24\u0d4d ?",
    "answer": "\u0d36\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d40\u0d28\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d23\u0d17\u0d41\u0d30\u0d41",
    "status": "10"
  },
  {
    "id": "1190",
    "question": "\u0d24\u0d46\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d7b \u0d24\u0d3f\u0d30\u0d41\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d02\u0d15\u0d42\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d1a\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d3e\u0d7c \u0d38\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d40\u0d15\u0d7e\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4d \u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d31\u0d41\u0d2e\u0d31\u0d2f\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d7b \u0d38\u0d4d\u0d35\u0d24\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30 \u0d28\u0d7d\u0d15\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d24\u0d4d ?",
    "answer": "\u0d09\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d02 \u0d24\u0d3f\u0d30\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d3e\u0d7e",
    "status": "10"
  },
  {
    "id": "1191",
    "question": "\u0d2a\u0d4b\u0d7c\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d41\u0d17\u0d40\u0d38\u0d41\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d46 \u0d07\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d06\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f \u0d2b\u0d3e\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d31\u0d3f \u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d3e\u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a \u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d32\u0d02 ?",
    "answer": "\u0d15\u0d4a\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d3f",
    "status": "10"
  },
  {
    "id": "1192",
    "question": "\u0d15\u0d47\u0d30\u0d33\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d7d \u0d15\u0d4b\u0d1f\u0d24\u0d3f \u0d35\u0d3f\u0d27\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d42\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d28\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d2e\u0d38\u0d2d\u0d3e\u0d02\u0d17\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d35\u0d02 \u0d28\u0d37\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d46\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f \u0d06\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f \u0d35\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f ?",
    "answer": "\u0d31\u0d4b\u0d38\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2e \u0d2a\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d42\u0d38\u0d4d",
    "status": "10"
  },
  {
    "id": "1193",
    "question": "\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d30\u0d41-\u0d15\u0d4a\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d3f \u0d30\u0d3e\u0d1c\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d2e\u0d41\u0d16 \u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d02 \u0d35\u0d39\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d3f\u0d30\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d30\u0d3e\u0d1c\u0d3e\u0d35\u0d4d ?",
    "answer": "\u0d1a\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d30 \u0d24\u0d3f\u0d30\u0d41\u0d28\u0d3e\u0d7e",
    "status": "10"
  },
  {
    "id": "1194",
    "question": "\u0d38\u0d16\u0d3e\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d33\u0d46 \u0d2e\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d4b\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d4d \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d38\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d26\u0d47\u0d36\u0d02 \u0d28\u0d7d\u0d15\u0d3f\u0d2f \u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d36\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d28\u0d3e\u0d2f \u0d15\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d42\u0d23\u0d3f\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d \u0d28\u0d47\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d35\u0d4d ?",
    "answer": "\u0d2a\u0d3f \u0d15\u0d43\u0d37\u0d4d\u0d23\u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d33\u0d4d\u0d33",
    "status": "10"
  },
  {
    "id": "1195",
    "question": "\u0d38\u0d3e\u0d39\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d35\u0d7c\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d15 \u0d38\u0d39\u0d15\u0d30\u0d23 \u0d38\u0d02\u0d18\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d7b\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d06\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f \u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d38\u0d3f\u0d21\u0d7b\u0d31\u0d4d ?",
    "answer": "\u0d0e\u0d02 \u0d2a\u0d3f \u0d2a\u0d4b\u0d7e",
    "status": "10"
  },
  {
    "id": "1196",
    "question": "\u0d07\u0d02\u0d17\u0d4d\u0d32\u0d40\u0d37\u0d41\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d7c \u0d24\u0d32\u0d36\u0d4d\u0d36\u0d47\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d7d \u0d15\u0d4b\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f \u0d28\u0d3f\u0d7c\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d35\u0d7c\u0d37\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d7d ?",
    "answer": "\u0d0e \u0d21\u0d3f 1708",
    "status": "10"
  },
  {
    "id": "1197",
    "question": "\u0d15\u0d3f\u0d34\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d35\u0d46\u0d28\u0d40\u0d38\u0d4d \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d46\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d24\u0d4d ?",
    "answer": "\u0d06\u0d32\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d41\u0d34",
    "status": "10"
  },
  {
    "id": "1198",
    "question": "\u0d15\u0d47\u0d30\u0d33\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d38\u0d41\u0d17\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d27\u0d35\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d1e\u0d4d\u0d1c\u0d28 \u0d38\u0d02\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d02 \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d46\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d24\u0d4d ?",
    "answer": "\u0d15\u0d47\u0d30\u0d33\u0d02",
    "status": "10"
  },
  {
    "id": "1199",
    "question": "\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d1c\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d38\u0d2d\u0d3e\u0d02\u0d17\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d46 \u0d15\u0d47\u0d30\u0d33 \u0d2e\u0d41\u0d16\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d2e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d2f \u0d30\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d3e\u0d2e\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d46 \u0d35\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f ?",
    "answer": "\u0d0e \u0d15\u0d46 \u0d06\u0d7b\u0d31\u0d23\u0d3f",
    "status": "10"
  },
  {
    "id": "1200",
    "question": "\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d1c\u0d47\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d1a\u0d4b\u0d33\u0d7b red \u0d15\u0d47\u0d30\u0d33 \u0d06\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d2e\u0d23\u0d02 \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d35\u0d7c\u0d37\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d7d ?",
    "answer": "\u0d0e \u0d21\u0d3f 1019",
    "status": "10"
  },
  {
    "id": "1201",
    "question": "\u0d15\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d28\u0d3e\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d15\u0d25\u0d3e\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d7b \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d46\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d24\u0d4d ?",
    "answer": "\u0d24\u0d15\u0d34\u0d3f",
    "status": "10"
  },
  {
    "id": "1202",
    "question": "\u0d15\u0d41\u0d1e\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d7b \u0d28\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d7c \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d41 \u0d30\u0d3e\u0d1c\u0d27\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d7d \u0d06\u0d23\u0d4d \u0d15\u0d34\u0d3f\u0d1e\u0d4d\u0d1e\u0d3f\u0d30\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d24\u0d4d ?",
    "answer": "\u0d05\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d32\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d41\u0d34",
    "status": "10"
  },
  {
    "id": "1203",
    "question": "\u0d15\u0d47\u0d30\u0d33\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d06\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f \u0d2c\u0d3e\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4d ?",
    "answer": "\u0d28\u0d46\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d19\u0d3e\u0d1f\u0d3f \u0d2c\u0d3e\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4d (1899)",
    "status": "10"
  },
  {
    "id": "1204",
    "question": "\u0d15\u0d47\u0d30\u0d33\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d06\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d46 \u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d32\u0d47\u0d38\u0d4d \u0d15\u0d4b\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d2f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d3e\u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d24\u0d4d ?",
    "answer": "\u0d2c\u0d46\u0d1e\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d2e\u0d3f\u0d7b \u0d2c\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d4d\u200c\u0d32\u0d3f",
    "status": "10"
  },
  {
    "id": "1205",
    "question": "\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d35\u0d7b\u0d15\u0d42\u0d7c \u0d1f\u0d48\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d02 \u0d2b\u0d3e\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d31\u0d3f \u0d0e\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d1f\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d ?",
    "answer": "\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d30\u0d41\u0d35\u0d28\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d2a\u0d41\u0d30\u0d02",
    "status": "10"
  },
  {
    "id": "1206",
    "question": "\u0d38\u0d41\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d40\u0d02 \u0d15\u0d4b\u0d1f\u0d24\u0d3f \u0d1a\u0d40\u0d2b\u0d4d \u0d1c\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d38\u0d4d \u0d06\u0d2f \u0d06\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f \u0d2e\u0d32\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d33\u0d3f ?",
    "answer": "\u0d15\u0d46 \u0d1c\u0d3f \u0d2c\u0d3e\u0d32\u0d15\u0d43\u0d37\u0d4d\u0d23\u0d7b",
    "status": "10"
  },
  {
    "id": "1207",
    "question": "\u0d15\u0d47\u0d30\u0d33 \u0d28\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d2e\u0d38\u0d2d\u0d2f\u0d46 \u0d05\u0d2d\u0d3f\u0d38\u0d02\u0d2c\u0d4b\u0d27\u0d28 \u0d1a\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d4d\u0d24 \u0d06\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f \u0d30\u0d3e\u0d37\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d2a\u0d24\u0d3f ?",
    "answer": "\u0d15\u0d46 \u0d06\u0d7c \u0d28\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d23\u0d7b",
    "status": "10"
  },
  {
    "id": "1208",
    "question": "\u0d15\u0d47\u0d30\u0d33 \u0d2e\u0d41\u0d16\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d2e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d7d \u0d17\u0d35\u0d7c\u0d23\u0d31\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d3f \u0d28\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d2e\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d28\u0d3e\u0d2f \u0d0f\u0d15 \u0d35\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f ?",
    "answer": "\u0d2a\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d02 \u0d24\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d41\u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d33\u0d4d\u0d33",
    "status": "10"
  },
  {
    "id": "1209",
    "question": "\u0d15\u0d47\u0d30\u0d33 \u0d2e\u0d41\u0d16\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d2e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d7d \u0d2a\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4a\u0d7b\u0d2a\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d02 \u0d28\u0d42\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d3f\u0d7d \u0d1c\u0d28\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a \u0d0f\u0d15 \u0d35\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f ?",
    "answer": "\u0d2a\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d02\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d41\u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d33\u0d4d\u0d33",
    "status": "10"
  },
  {
    "id": "1210",
    "question": "\u0d15\u0d47\u0d30\u0d33 \u0d38\u0d46\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d47\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d \u0d2e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d26\u0d3f\u0d30\u0d02 \u0d2a\u0d23\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d34\u0d3f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d26\u0d3f\u0d35\u0d3e\u0d7b ?",
    "answer": "\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d27\u0d35\u0d31\u0d3e\u0d35\u0d41",
    "status": "10"
  },
  {
    "id": "1211",
    "question": "\u0d15\u0d47\u0d30\u0d33 \u0d2a\u0d4b\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d7d \u0d38\u0d7c\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3f\u0d7e \u0d28\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d7d \u0d35\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d35\u0d7c\u0d37\u0d02 ?",
    "answer": "1961",
    "status": "10"
  },
  {
    "id": "1212",
    "question": "\u0d15\u0d47\u0d30\u0d33\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d06\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f \u0d35\u0d28\u0d3f\u0d24 \u0d15\u0d4b\u0d33\u0d47\u0d1c\u0d4d \u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d3e\u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d0e\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d1f\u0d46 ?",
    "answer": "\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d30\u0d41\u0d35\u0d28\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d2a\u0d41\u0d30\u0d02",
    "status": "10"
  },
  {
    "id": "1213",
    "question": "\u0d17\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d27\u0d3f\u0d1c\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d46 \u0d15\u0d41\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d4d \u0d0e\u0d7b\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d17\u0d41\u0d30\u0d41\u0d28\u0d3e\u0d25\u0d7b \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d15\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d24 \u0d30\u0d1a\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d24\u0d4d ?",
    "answer": "\u0d35\u0d33\u0d4d\u0d33\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4b\u0d7e",
    "status": "10"
  },
  {
    "id": "1214",
    "question": "\u0d36\u0d3e\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d02\u0d15\u0d4b\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f \u0d24\u0d1f\u0d3e\u0d15\u0d02 \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d1c\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4d\u0d32\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d \u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d3f \u0d1a\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d24\u0d4d ?",
    "answer": "\u0d15\u0d4a\u0d32\u0d4d\u0d32\u0d02",
    "status": "10"
  },
  {
    "id": "1215",
    "question": "\u0d35\u0d3e\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d41 \u0d35\u0d3f\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d3e \u0d17\u0d41\u0d30\u0d41\u0d15\u0d41\u0d32\u0d02 \u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d24\u0d4d ?",
    "answer": "\u0d06\u0d31\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d41\u0d33",
    "status": "10"
  },
  {
    "id": "1216",
    "question": "\u0d15\u0d47\u0d30\u0d33\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d7d \u0d24\u0d46\u0d30\u0d1e\u0d4d\u0d1e\u0d46\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d42\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d38\u0d40\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d \u0d28\u0d47\u0d1f\u0d3f\u0d2f \u0d06\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f \u0d05\u0d02\u0d17\u0d02 ?",
    "answer": "\u0d31\u0d4b\u0d38\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2e \u0d2a\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d42\u0d38\u0d4d",
    "status": "10"
  },
  {
    "id": "1217",
    "question": "\u0d15\u0d47\u0d30\u0d33\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d7d \u0d32\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d37\u0d02\u0d35\u0d40\u0d1f\u0d4d \u0d2a\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d27\u0d24\u0d3f \u0d06\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d37\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d24\u0d4d ?",
    "answer": "\u0d0e\u0d02 \u0d0e\u0d7b \u0d17\u0d4b\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d26\u0d7b \u0d28\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d7c",
    "status": "10"
  },
  {
    "id": "1218",
    "question": "\u0d07\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d7d \u0d15\u0d1f\u0d7d\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d7c\u0d17\u0d02 \u0d35\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d06\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d46 \u0d35\u0d3f\u0d26\u0d47\u0d36\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d7e ?",
    "answer": "\u0d05\u0d31\u0d2c\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d7e",
    "status": "10"
  },
  {
    "id": "1219",
    "question": "\u0d15\u0d47\u0d30\u0d33\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d06\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d46 \u0d2a\u0d41\u0d15\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d32 \u0d35\u0d3f\u0d30\u0d41\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d27 \u0d1c\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4d\u0d32 ?",
    "answer": "\u0d15\u0d4b\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d2f\u0d02",
    "status": "10"
  },
  {
    "id": "1220",
    "question": "\u0d30\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d3e\u0d02 \u0d1a\u0d47\u0d30 \u0d38\u0d3e\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d1c\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d \u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d3e\u0d2a\u0d15\u0d7b ?",
    "answer": "\u0d15\u0d41\u0d32\u0d36\u0d47\u0d16\u0d30 \u0d35\u0d7c\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2e",
    "status": "10"
  },
  {
    "id": "1221",
    "question": "\u0d15\u0d41\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d28\u0d3e\u0d36\u0d3e\u0d7b\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d1c\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d32\u0d02 ?",
    "answer": "\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d30",
    "status": "10"
  },
  {
    "id": "1222",
    "question": "\u0d2a\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d2e\u0d42\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d3e\u0d02 \u0d36\u0d24\u0d15\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d7d \u0d15\u0d47\u0d30\u0d33\u0d02 \u0d38\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d26\u0d7c\u0d36\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a \u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d7c\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4b\u0d2a\u0d4b\u0d33\u0d4b \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d30\u0d3e\u0d1c\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d28\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d30\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d41 ?",
    "answer": "\u0d07\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d32\u0d3f",
    "status": "10"
  },
  {
    "id": "1223",
    "question": "\u0d07\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d25\u0d2e\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d3f \u0d12\u0d30\u0d41 \u0d35\u0d28\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d2f\u0d46 \u0d28\u0d3e\u0d2e\u0d28\u0d3f\u0d7c\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d26\u0d47\u0d36\u0d02 \u0d1a\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d05\u0d02\u0d17\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3f\u0d2f \u0d28\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d2e\u0d38\u0d2d\u0d3e \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d30\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d41 ?",
    "answer": "\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d30\u0d41\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d02\u0d15\u0d42\u0d7c",
    "status": "10"
  },
  {
    "id": "1224",
    "question": "\u0d28\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d7c\u0d38\u0d3e\u0d7b \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d46\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d3f\u0d30\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d24\u0d4d ?",
    "answer": "\u0d0e \u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d27\u0d35\u0d7b \u0d28\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d7c",
    "status": "10"
  },
  {
    "id": "1225",
    "question": "\u0d15\u0d47\u0d30\u0d33\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d0f\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d35\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d1c\u0d28\u0d38\u0d02\u0d16\u0d4d\u0d2f \u0d15\u0d41\u0d31\u0d1e\u0d4d\u0d1e \u0d24\u0d3e\u0d32\u0d42\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4d \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d4d? ",
    "answer": "\u0d2e\u0d32\u0d4d\u0d32\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d33\u0d4d\u0d33\u0d3f",
    "status": "10"
  },
  {
    "id": "1226",
    "question": "\u0d0f\u0d37\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d0f\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d35\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d35\u0d32\u0d3f\u0d2f \u0d15\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d41\u0d2e\u0d24 \u0d38\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d47\u0d33\u0d28\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d2f \u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d2e\u0d23\u0d4d \u0d15\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d35\u0d46\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d37\u0d28\u0d4d \u0d28\u0d1f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d1c\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4d\u0d32: ",
    "answer": "\u0d2a\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d28\u0d02\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f",
    "status": "10"
  },
  {
    "id": "1227",
    "question": "\u0d0f\u0d37\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d0f\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d35\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d35\u0d32\u0d3f\u0d2f \u0d15\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d41\u0d2e\u0d24 \u0d38\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d47\u0d33\u0d28\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d2e\u0d23\u0d4d \u0d15\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d35\u0d46\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d37\u0d28\u0d4d \u0d28\u0d1f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d0e\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d1f\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d? ",
    "answer": "\u0d15\u0d4b\u0d34\u0d1e\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d47\u0d30\u0d3f",
    "status": "10"
  },
  {
    "id": "1228",
    "question": "\u0d0f\u0d37\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d0f\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d35\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d35\u0d32\u0d3f\u0d2f \u0d15\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d41\u0d2e\u0d24 \u0d38\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d47\u0d33\u0d28\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d2f \u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d2e\u0d23\u0d4d \u0d15\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d35\u0d46\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d37\u0d28\u0d4d \u0d28\u0d1f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d28\u0d26\u0d40\u0d24\u0d40\u0d30\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d? ",
    "answer": "\u0d2a\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2a",
    "status": "10"
  },
  {
    "id": "1229",
    "question": ". \u0d15\u0d43\u0d37\u0d4d\u0d23\u0d2a\u0d41\u0d30\u0d02 \u0d15\u0d4a\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d02 \u0d2a\u0d23\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d34\u0d3f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d4d? ",
    "answer": "\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d21 \u0d35\u0d30\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2e",
    "status": "10"
  },
  {
    "id": "1230",
    "question": "\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d1c\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d35\u0d3f \u0d35\u0d30\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2e \u0d15\u0d4b\u0d33\u0d47\u0d1c\u0d4d \u0d13\u0d2b\u0d4d \u0d2b\u0d48\u0d28\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d38\u0d4d \u0d0e\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d1f\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d? ",
    "answer": "\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d35\u0d47\u0d32\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d30",
    "status": "10"
  },
  {
    "id": "1231",
    "question": "\u0d15\u0d47\u0d30\u0d33\u0d3e \u0d38\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d47\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d \u0d35\u0d3e\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d30\u0d4d \u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d4b\u0d30\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d4d \u0d15\u0d4b\u0d30\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d31\u0d47\u0d37\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d06\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d02 \u0d0e\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d1f\u0d46? ",
    "answer": "\u0d06\u0d32\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d41\u0d34",
    "status": "10"
  },
  {
    "id": "1232",
    "question": "\u0d15\u0d41\u0d1e\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d28\u0d4d \u0d28\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d4d \u0d38\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d15\u0d02 \u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d3f \u0d1a\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d24\u0d46\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d1f\u0d46? ",
    "answer": "\u0d05\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d32\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d41\u0d34",
    "status": "10"
  },
  {
    "id": "1233",
    "question": "\u0d28\u0d46\u0d39\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d4b\u0d2b\u0d3f \u0d35\u0d33\u0d4d\u0d33\u0d02\u0d15\u0d33\u0d3f \u0d28\u0d1f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d15\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d32\u0d4d \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d4d? ",
    "answer": "\u0d2a\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d2e\u0d1f \u0d15\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d32\u0d4d",
    "status": "10"
  },
  {
    "id": "1234",
    "question": "\u0d38\u0d2e\u0d41\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d24\u0d40\u0d30\u0d02 \u0d07\u0d32\u0d4d\u0d32\u0d3e\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d24\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d15\u0d47\u0d30\u0d33\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d1c\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4d\u0d32\u0d15\u0d33\u0d41\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d3f \u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d02 \u0d05\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d30\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f \u0d2a\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3f\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d24\u0d41\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d2f \u0d0f\u0d15 \u0d1c\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4d\u0d32 \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d4d? ",
    "answer": "\u0d15\u0d4b\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d2f\u0d02",
    "status": "10"
  },
  {
    "id": "1235",
    "question": "\u0d15\u0d4b\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d2f\u0d02 \u0d2a\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d23\u0d02 \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d28\u0d26\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d24\u0d40\u0d30\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d \u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d24\u0d4d? ",
    "answer": "\u0d2e\u0d40\u0d28\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4d \u0d06\u0d31\u0d4d",
    "status": "10"
  },
  {
    "id": "1236",
    "question": "\u0d38\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d42\u0d30\u0d4d\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d23 \u0d38\u0d3e\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d37\u0d30\u0d24 \u0d28\u0d47\u0d1f\u0d3f\u0d2f \u0d07\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d06\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f \u0d2a\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d23\u0d02 \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d4d? ",
    "answer": "\u0d15\u0d4b\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d2f\u0d02",
    "status": "10"
  },
  {
    "id": "1237",
    "question": "\u0d15\u0d47\u0d30\u0d33\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d06\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f \u0d2a\u0d41\u0d15\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d32 \u0d35\u0d3f\u0d30\u0d41\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d27 \u0d1c\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4d\u0d32 \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d4d? ",
    "answer": "\u0d15\u0d4b\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d2f\u0d02",
    "status": "10"
  },
  {
    "id": "1238",
    "question": "\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d43\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4d \u0d30\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d3e\u0d02 \u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d28\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d1c\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4d\u0d32 \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d4d? ",
    "answer": "\u0d07\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3f",
    "status": "10"
  },
  {
    "id": "1239",
    "question": "\u0d07\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3f \u0d1c\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4d\u0d32\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d06\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d28\u0d02: ",
    "answer": "\u0d2a\u0d48\u0d28\u0d3e\u0d35\u0d4d",
    "status": "10"
  },
  {
    "id": "1240",
    "question": "\u0d15\u0d47\u0d30\u0d33\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d38\u0d41\u0d17\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d27 \u0d35\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d1e\u0d4d\u0d1c\u0d28\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d19\u0d33\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d15\u0d32\u0d35\u0d31 \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d46\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d1c\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4d\u0d32: ",
    "answer": "\u0d07\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3f",
    "status": "10"
  },
  {
    "id": "1241",
    "question": "\u0d0e\u0d31\u0d23\u0d3e\u0d15\u0d41\u0d33\u0d02 \u0d1c\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4d\u0d32\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d06\u0d28\u0d2a\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d36\u0d40\u0d32\u0d28 \u0d15\u0d47\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d02 \u0d0e\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d1f\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d? ",
    "answer": "\u0d15\u0d4b\u0d1f\u0d28\u0d3e\u0d1f\u0d4d",
    "status": "10"
  },
  {
    "id": "1242",
    "question": ". \u0d0e\u0d31\u0d23\u0d3e\u0d15\u0d41\u0d33\u0d02 \u0d1c\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4d\u0d32\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d06\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d02 \u0d0e\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d1f\u0d46? ",
    "answer": "\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d28\u0d3e\u0d1f\u0d4d",
    "status": "10"
  },
  {
    "id": "1243",
    "question": "\u0d15\u0d47\u0d30\u0d33\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d0f\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d35\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d35\u0d32\u0d3f\u0d2f \u0d15\u0d4b\u0d30\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d31\u0d47\u0d37\u0d28\u0d4d \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d4d? ",
    "answer": "\u0d15\u0d4a\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d3f",
    "status": "10"
  },
  {
    "id": "1244",
    "question": ". \u0d15\u0d47\u0d30\u0d33\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4d \u0d06\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d02 \u0d15\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d42\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d30\u0d4d \u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d3e\u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d0e\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d1f\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d? ",
    "answer": "\u0d15\u0d4a\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d3f",
    "status": "10"
  },
  {
    "id": "1245",
    "question": "\u0d0f\u0d37\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d0f\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d35\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d09\u0d2f\u0d30\u0d02 \u0d15\u0d42\u0d1f\u0d3f\u0d2f \u0d15\u0d43\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d28\u0d4d \u0d26\u0d47\u0d35\u0d3e\u0d32\u0d2f\u0d02 \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d? ",
    "answer": "\u0d2a\u0d41\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d28\u0d4d \u0d2a\u0d33\u0d4d\u0d33\u0d3f",
    "status": "10"
  },
  {
    "id": "1246",
    "question": "\u0d36\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d40\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d2e\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d37\u0d47\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d2f \u0d24\u0d43\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d4d \u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d3f \u0d1a\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d1c\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4d\u0d32: ",
    "answer": "\u0d24\u0d43\u0d36\u0d42\u0d30\u0d4d",
    "status": "10"
  },
  {
    "id": "1247",
    "question": "\u0d2d\u0d30\u0d24\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d37\u0d47\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d2f \u0d15\u0d42\u0d1f\u0d32\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d02 \u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d3f \u0d1a\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d1c\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4d\u0d32: ",
    "answer": "\u0d24\u0d43\u0d36\u0d42\u0d30\u0d4d",
    "status": "10"
  },
  {
    "id": "1248",
    "question": "\u0d24\u0d43\u0d36\u0d42\u0d30\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d42\u0d30\u0d02 \u0d28\u0d1f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d2e\u0d48\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d02 \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d4d? ",
    "answer": "\u0d24\u0d47\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d1f\u0d4d",
    "status": "10"
  },
  {
    "id": "1249",
    "question": "\u0d15\u0d47\u0d30\u0d33\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d06\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f \u0d2e\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d38\u0d3f\u0d2a\u0d3e\u0d32\u0d3f\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d3f: ",
    "answer": "\u0d17\u0d41\u0d30\u0d41\u0d35\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d42\u0d30\u0d4d",
    "status": "10"
  },
  {
    "id": "1250",
    "question": "\u0d15\u0d47\u0d30\u0d33\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d0f\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d35\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d35\u0d32\u0d3f\u0d2f \u0d1c\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4d\u0d32 \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d4d? ",
    "answer": "\u0d2a\u0d3e\u0d32\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d1f\u0d4d",
    "status": "10"
  },
  {
    "id": "1251",
    "question": "\u0d15\u0d47\u0d30\u0d33\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4d \u0d15\u0d3e\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4d \u0d28\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d35\u0d48\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d24\u0d3f \u0d09\u0d32\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d3e\u0d26\u0d3f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d06\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f \u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d4b\u0d1c\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d \u0d28\u0d1f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d3e\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d0e\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d1f\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d? ",
    "answer": "\u0d15\u0d1e\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4b\u0d1f\u0d4d",
    "status": "10"
  },
  {
    "id": "1252",
    "question": "\u0d15\u0d47\u0d30\u0d33\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4d \u0d0f\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d35\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d15\u0d42\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d24\u0d32\u0d4d \u0d2a\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d1c\u0d3e\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d41\u0d33\u0d4d\u0d33 \u0d1c\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4d\u0d32: ",
    "answer": "\u0d2a\u0d3e\u0d32\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d1f\u0d4d",
    "status": "10"
  },
  {
    "id": "1253",
    "question": "\u0d15\u0d4a\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4b\u0d33 \u0d35\u0d3f\u0d30\u0d41\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d27 \u0d38\u0d2e\u0d30\u0d02 \u0d28\u0d1f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d2a\u0d3e\u0d32\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d1f\u0d4d \u0d1c\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4d\u0d32\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d26\u0d47\u0d36\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d? ",
    "answer": "\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d32\u0d3e\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d3f\u0d2e\u0d1f",
    "status": "10"
  },
  {
    "id": "1254",
    "question": "\u0d15\u0d47\u0d30\u0d33\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4d \u0d0f\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d35\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d15\u0d42\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d24\u0d32\u0d4d \u0d1c\u0d28\u0d38\u0d02\u0d16\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d33\u0d4d\u0d33 \u0d1c\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4d\u0d32 \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d4d? ",
    "answer": "\u0d2e\u0d32\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d41\u0d31\u0d02",
    "status": "10"
  },
  {
    "id": "1255",
    "question": ". \u0d2e\u0d32\u0d2c\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d4d \u0d38\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d46\u0d37\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d32\u0d4d \u0d2a\u0d4b\u0d32\u0d40\u0d38\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d06\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d02 \u0d0e\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d1f\u0d46? ",
    "answer": "\u0d2e\u0d32\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d41\u0d31\u0d02",
    "status": "10"
  },
  {
    "id": "1256",
    "question": ". \u0d2a\u0d42\u0d30\u0d4d\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d23\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d15\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d42\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d30\u0d4d \u0d35\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d43\u0d24\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d2f \u0d06\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f \u0d2a\u0d1e\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d? ",
    "answer": "\u0d35\u0d46\u0d33\u0d4d\u0d33\u0d28\u0d3e\u0d1f\u0d4d",
    "status": "10"
  },
  {
    "id": "1257",
    "question": "\u0d07\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d06\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f \u0d15\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d42\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d30\u0d4d \u0d38\u0d3e\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d37\u0d30\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d17\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d2e\u0d02: ",
    "answer": "\u0d24\u0d2f\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d42\u0d30\u0d4d(\u0d24\u0d43\u0d36\u0d42\u0d30\u0d4d)",
    "status": "10"
  },
  {
    "id": "1258",
    "question": "\u0d15\u0d47\u0d30\u0d33\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4d \u0d0f\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d35\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d15\u0d42\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d24\u0d32\u0d4d \u0d15\u0d30\u0d4d\u0d37\u0d15 \u0d24\u0d4a\u0d34\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d3e\u0d33\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d33\u0d4d \u0d09\u0d33\u0d4d\u0d33 \u0d1c\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4d\u0d32: ",
    "answer": "\u0d2a\u0d3e\u0d32\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d1f\u0d4d",
    "status": "10"
  },
  {
    "id": "1259",
    "question": "\u0d2a\u0d42\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d02 \u0d28\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d42\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d07\u0d32\u0d4d\u0d32\u0d02 \u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d3f \u0d1a\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d30\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d24\u0d46\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d1f\u0d46? ",
    "answer": "\u0d15\u0d40\u0d34\u0d3e\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d42\u0d30\u0d4d (\u0d2a\u0d46\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d32\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d23\u0d2f\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d)",
    "status": "10"
  },
  {
    "id": "1260",
    "question": "\u0d15\u0d4b\u0d34\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4b\u0d1f\u0d4d \u0d35\u0d3f\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d35\u0d33\u0d02 \u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d0e\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d1f\u0d46? ",
    "answer": "\u0d15\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d42\u0d30\u0d4d(\u0d2e\u0d32\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d41\u0d31\u0d02 \u0d1c\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4d\u0d32)",
    "status": "10"
  },
  {
    "id": "1261",
    "question": "\u0d38\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d42\u0d30\u0d4d\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d23 \u0d15\u0d02\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d42\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d30\u0d4d \u0d38\u0d3e\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d37\u0d30\u0d24\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d41 \u0d35\u0d47\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d3f \u0d05\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d37\u0d2f \u0d15\u0d47\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d02 \u0d06\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d3f \u0d06\u0d30\u0d02\u0d2d\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a \u0d1c\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4d\u0d32 \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d4d? ",
    "answer": "\u0d2e\u0d32\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d41\u0d31\u0d02",
    "status": "10"
  },
  {
    "id": "1262",
    "question": "\u0d38\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d42\u0d30\u0d4d\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d23 \u0d15\u0d4b\u0d33 \u0d35\u0d3f\u0d2e\u0d41\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d24 \u0d1c\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4d\u0d32 \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d4d? ",
    "answer": "\u0d15\u0d4b\u0d34\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4b\u0d1f\u0d4d.",
    "status": "10"
  },
  {
    "id": "1263",
    "question": ". \u0d15\u0d47\u0d30\u0d33\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d0f\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d35\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d15\u0d41\u0d31\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d4d \u0d1c\u0d28\u0d38\u0d02\u0d16\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d33\u0d4d\u0d33 \u0d1c\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4d\u0d32 \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d4d? ",
    "answer": "\u0d35\u0d2f\u0d28\u0d3e\u0d1f\u0d4d",
    "status": "10"
  },
  {
    "id": "1264",
    "question": "\u0d15\u0d47\u0d30\u0d33\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d0f\u0d15 \u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d15\u0d43\u0d24\u0d3f \u0d26\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24 \u0d05\u0d23\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d46\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d4d \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d4d",
    "answer": "\u0d2c\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d3e\u0d38\u0d41\u0d30 \u0d38\u0d3e\u0d17\u0d30\u0d4d",
    "status": "10"
  },
  {
    "id": "1265",
    "question": "\u0d07\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d0f\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d35\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d35\u0d32\u0d3f\u0d2f \u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d15\u0d43\u0d24\u0d3f \u0d26\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24 \u0d2d\u0d42\u0d17\u0d30\u0d4d\u0d2d \u0d21\u0d3e\u0d02 \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d? ",
    "answer": "\u0d2c\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d3e\u0d38\u0d41\u0d30 \u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d4b\u0d1c\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d",
    "status": "10"
  },
  {
    "id": "1266",
    "question": "\u0d15\u0d47\u0d30\u0d33\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d28\u0d3e\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d15 \u0d05\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d26\u0d2e\u0d3f \u0d0e\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d3f \u0d1a\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d41? ",
    "answer": "\u0d0f\u0d34\u0d3f\u0d2e\u0d32",
    "status": "10"
  },
  {
    "id": "1267",
    "question": ". \u0d2e\u0d32\u0d2c\u0d3e\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d09\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d41 \u0d38\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d17\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d39\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d27\u0d3e\u0d28 \u0d35\u0d47\u0d26\u0d3f \u0d0e\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d1f\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d30\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d41? ",
    "answer": "\u0d2a\u0d2f\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d42\u0d30\u0d4d",
    "status": "10"
  },
  {
    "id": "1268",
    "question": "\u0d2e\u0d32\u0d2c\u0d3e\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d09\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d41 \u0d38\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d17\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d39\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d27\u0d3e\u0d28 \u0d35\u0d47\u0d26\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d30\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d2a\u0d2f\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d42\u0d30\u0d4d \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d1c\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4d\u0d32\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d? ",
    "answer": "\u0d15\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d23\u0d42\u0d30\u0d4d",
    "status": "10"
  },
  {
    "id": "1269",
    "question": "\u0d15\u0d47\u0d30\u0d33\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d2b\u0d4b\u0d31\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d \u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d3f\u0d02\u0d17\u0d4d \u0d38\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d42\u0d33\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d06\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d02 \u0d0e\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d1f\u0d46? ",
    "answer": "\u0d05\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a",
    "status": "10"
  },
  {
    "id": "1270",
    "question": ". \u0d15\u0d47\u0d30\u0d33\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d06\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d46 \u0d24\u0d41\u0d31\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d1c\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4d \u0d0e\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d3f \u0d1a\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d41? ",
    "answer": "\u0d28\u0d46\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d32\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d47\u0d30\u0d3f(\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d3e\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d1f)",
    "status": "10"
  },
  {
    "id": "1271",
    "question": "\u0d15\u0d47\u0d30\u0d33 \u0d38\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d47\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d \u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d4b\u0d30\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d4d \u0d15\u0d4b\u0d30\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d31\u0d47\u0d37\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d06\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d02 \u0d0e\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d1f\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d? ",
    "answer": "\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d30\u0d41\u0d35\u0d28\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d2a\u0d41\u0d30\u0d02",
    "status": "10"
  },
  {
    "id": "1272",
    "question": ". \u0d24\u0d3f\u0d30\u0d41\u0d35\u0d28\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d2a\u0d41\u0d30\u0d02 \u0d1c\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4d\u0d32\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d0f\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d35\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d09\u0d2f\u0d30\u0d02 \u0d15\u0d42\u0d1f\u0d3f\u0d2f \u0d15\u0d4a\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d2e\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d3f \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d4d? ",
    "answer": "\u0d05\u0d17\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d2e\u0d32",
    "status": "10"
  },
  {
    "id": "1273",
    "question": "\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d02 \u0d38\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d2d\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d3f \u0d38\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d47\u0d38\u0d4d \u0d38\u0d46\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d30\u0d4d \u0d0e\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d1f\u0d46?",
    "answer": " \u0d24\u0d41\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2a",
    "status": "10"
  },
  {
    "id": "1274",
    "question": "\u0d2a\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d28\u0d02\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d12\u0d30\u0d47\u0d2f\u0d4a\u0d30\u0d41 \u0d31\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4d\u0d35\u0d47\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d47\u0d37\u0d28\u0d4d \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d? ",
    "answer": "\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d30\u0d41\u0d35\u0d32\u0d4d\u0d32",
    "status": "10"
  },
  {
    "id": "1275",
    "question": ". \u0d15\u0d47\u0d30\u0d33\u0d3e \u0d07\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d42\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d4d \u0d13\u0d2b\u0d4d \u0d2b\u0d4b\u0d15\u0d4d \u0d32\u0d4b\u0d30\u0d4d \u0d06\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d \u0d2b\u0d4b\u0d15\u0d4d \u0d06\u0d30\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d38\u0d4d \u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d0e\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d1f\u0d46? ",
    "answer": "\u0d2e\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d23\u0d1f\u0d3f",
    "status": "10"
  },
  {
    "id": "1276",
    "question": ". \u0d36\u0d2c\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d17\u0d3f\u0d30\u0d3f \u0d1c\u0d32\u0d35\u0d48\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d24 \u0d2a\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d27\u0d24\u0d3f \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d1c\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4d\u0d32\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d? ",
    "answer": "\u0d2a\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d28\u0d02\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f",
    "status": "10"
  },
  {
    "id": "1277",
    "question": ". \u0d28\u0d46\u0d39\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d4b\u0d2b\u0d3f \u0d35\u0d33\u0d4d\u0d33\u0d02\u0d15\u0d33\u0d3f \u0d28\u0d1f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d38\u0d3e\u0d27\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d23\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d3f \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d38\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d? ",
    "answer": "\u0d06\u0d17\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d",
    "status": "10"
  },
  {
    "id": "1278",
    "question": "\u0d35\u0d48\u0d31\u0d4b\u0d33\u0d1c\u0d3f \u0d07\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d42\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d4d \u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d3f \u0d1a\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d1c\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4d\u0d32 \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d4d? ",
    "answer": "\u0d06\u0d32\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d41\u0d34",
    "status": "10"
  },
  {
    "id": "1279",
    "question": "\u0d15\u0d47\u0d30\u0d33\u0d3e \u0d38\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d47\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d \u0d21\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d17\u0d4d\u0d38\u0d4d \u0d06\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d \u0d2b\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d42\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d32\u0d4d\u0d38\u0d4d \u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d3f \u0d1a\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d24\u0d46\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d1f\u0d46? ",
    "answer": "\u0d15\u0d32\u0d35\u0d42\u0d30\u0d4d",
    "status": "10"
  },
  {
    "id": "1280",
    "question": "\u0d15\u0d4b\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d2f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d46 \u0d06\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f \u0d38\u0d3e\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d37\u0d30\u0d24\u0d3e \u0d2a\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d23\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d3f \u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d16\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d24\u0d46\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d4d? ",
    "answer": "1989 \u0d1c\u0d42\u0d23\u0d4d 25",
    "status": "10"
  },
  {
    "id": "1281",
    "question": "\u0d39\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d26\u0d41\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d4d \u0d2a\u0d47\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d30\u0d4d \u0d2e\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4d\u0d38\u0d4d \u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d0e\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d1f\u0d46? ",
    "answer": "\u0d35\u0d46\u0d33\u0d4d\u0d33\u0d42\u0d30\u0d4d",
    "status": "10"
  },
  {
    "id": "1282",
    "question": "\u0d39\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d26\u0d41\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d4d \u0d2a\u0d47\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d30\u0d4d \u0d2e\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4d\u0d38\u0d4d \u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d28\u0d26\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d24\u0d40\u0d30\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d? ",
    "answer": "\u0d2e\u0d42\u0d35\u0d3e\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d41\u0d2a\u0d41\u0d34",
    "status": "10"
  },
  {
    "id": "1283",
    "question": "\u0d15\u0d47\u0d30\u0d33\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d06\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d46 \u0d35\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d1c\u0d40\u0d35\u0d3f \u0d38\u0d02\u0d30\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d37\u0d23 \u0d15\u0d47\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d02: ",
    "answer": "\u0d24\u0d47\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d1f\u0d3f",
    "status": "10"
  },
  {
    "id": "1284",
    "question": "\u0d24\u0d47\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d1f\u0d3f \u0d35\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d1c\u0d40\u0d35\u0d3f \u0d38\u0d02\u0d30\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d37\u0d23 \u0d15\u0d47\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d02 \u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d3e\u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a \u0d24\u0d3f\u0d30\u0d41\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d02\u0d15\u0d42\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d30\u0d3e\u0d1c\u0d3e\u0d35\u0d4d \u0d06\u0d30\u0d4d? ",
    "answer": "\u0d36\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d40 \u0d1a\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d30\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d30\u0d41\u0d28\u0d3e\u0d33\u0d4d",
    "status": "10"
  },
  {
    "id": "1285",
    "question": "\u0d15\u0d47\u0d30\u0d33\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d0f\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d35\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d35\u0d32\u0d3f\u0d2f \u0d35\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d1c\u0d40\u0d35\u0d3f \u0d38\u0d02\u0d30\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d37\u0d23 \u0d15\u0d47\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d02: ",
    "answer": "\u0d24\u0d47\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d1f\u0d3f",
    "status": "10"
  },
  {
    "id": "1286",
    "question": ". \u0d35\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d47\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d26\u0d40\u0d15\u0d43\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d38\u0d42\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d23\u0d02 \u0d06\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d02 \u0d24\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d19\u0d3f\u0d2f \u0d2a\u0d1e\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d? ",
    "answer": "\u0d15\u0d32\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d36\u0d4d\u0d36\u0d47\u0d30\u0d3f",
    "status": "10"
  },
  {
    "id": "1287",
    "question": "\u0d07\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4d \u0d38\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d42\u0d30\u0d4d\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d23 \u0d38\u0d3e\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d37\u0d30\u0d24 \u0d28\u0d47\u0d1f\u0d3f\u0d2f \u0d06\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d46 \u0d1c\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4d\u0d32: ",
    "answer": "\u0d0e\u0d31\u0d23\u0d3e\u0d15\u0d41\u0d33\u0d02",
    "status": "10"
  },
  {
    "id": "1288",
    "question": ". \u0d0e\u0d31\u0d23\u0d3e\u0d15\u0d41\u0d33\u0d02 \u0d0e\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d4b\u0d34\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d \u0d38\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d42\u0d30\u0d4d\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d23 \u0d38\u0d3e\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d37\u0d30\u0d24 \u0d28\u0d47\u0d1f\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d24\u0d4d? ",
    "answer": "1990 \u0d2b\u0d46\u0d2c\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d41\u0d35\u0d30\u0d3f 4",
    "status": "10"
  },
  {
    "id": "1289",
    "question": "\u0d15\u0d47\u0d30\u0d33\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d35\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d35\u0d38\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d15 \u0d24\u0d32\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d02: ",
    "answer": "\u0d0e\u0d31\u0d23\u0d3e\u0d15\u0d41\u0d33\u0d02",
    "status": "10"
  },
  {
    "id": "1290",
    "question": "\u0d15\u0d47\u0d30\u0d33 \u0d15\u0d32\u0d3e\u0d2e\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d21\u0d32\u0d02 \u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d3e\u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d24\u0d46\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d4b\u0d33\u0d4d? ",
    "answer": "1930",
    "status": "10"
  },
  {
    "id": "1291",
    "question": "\u0d2a\u0d42\u0d30\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d19\u0d33\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d28\u0d3e\u0d1f\u0d4d \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d4d \u0d05\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d46\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d15\u0d47\u0d30\u0d33\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d1c\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4d\u0d32 \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d4d? ",
    "answer": "\u0d24\u0d43\u0d36\u0d42\u0d30\u0d4d",
    "status": "10"
  },
  {
    "id": "1292",
    "question": "\u0d15\u0d47\u0d30\u0d33\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d06\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f \u0d35\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d35\u0d39\u0d3e\u0d30 \u0d30\u0d39\u0d3f\u0d24 \u0d35\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4d\u0d32\u0d47\u0d1c\u0d4d \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d? ",
    "answer": "\u0d35\u0d30\u0d35\u0d42\u0d30\u0d4d",
    "status": "10"
  },
  {
    "id": "1293",
    "question": "\u0d15\u0d47\u0d30\u0d33\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4d \u0d0e\u0d32\u0d4d\u0d32\u0d3e\u0d35\u0d30\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d2c\u0d3e\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4d \u0d05\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d57\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d4d \u0d09\u0d33\u0d4d\u0d33 \u0d1c\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4d\u0d32: ",
    "answer": "\u0d2a\u0d3e\u0d32\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d1f\u0d4d",
    "status": "10"
  },
  {
    "id": "1294",
    "question": ". \u0d15\u0d47\u0d30\u0d33\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4d \u0d0f\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d35\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d15\u0d41\u0d31\u0d35\u0d4d \u0d35\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d35\u0d38\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d36\u0d3e\u0d32\u0d15\u0d33\u0d4d \u0d09\u0d33\u0d4d\u0d33 \u0d1c\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4d\u0d32 \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d4d? ",
    "answer": "\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d38\u0d30\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4b\u0d1f\u0d4d",
    "status": "10"
  },
  {
    "id": "1295",
    "question": ". \u0d15\u0d47\u0d30\u0d33\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d0f\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d35\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d35\u0d32\u0d3f\u0d2f \u0d31\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4d\u0d35\u0d47\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d47\u0d37\u0d28\u0d4d \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d? ",
    "answer": "\u0d37\u0d4b\u0d30\u0d4d\u0d23\u0d42\u0d30\u0d4d",
    "status": "10"
  },
  {
    "id": "1296",
    "question": "\u0d15\u0d47\u0d30\u0d33\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4d \u0d2a\u0d30\u0d41\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f \u0d09\u0d32\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d3e\u0d26\u0d3f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d0f\u0d15 \u0d1c\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4d\u0d32: ",
    "answer": "\u0d2a\u0d3e\u0d32\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d1f\u0d4d",
    "status": "10"
  },
  {
    "id": "1297",
    "question": "\u0d32\u0d4b\u0d15\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d0f\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d35\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d2a\u0d34\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d02 \u0d1a\u0d46\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d24\u0d47\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d \u0d24\u0d4b\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d02 \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d? ",
    "answer": "\u0d15\u0d28\u0d4b\u0d32\u0d3f \u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d32\u0d4b\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d4d",
    "status": "10"
  },
  {
    "id": "1298",
    "question": ". \u0d35\u0d3e\u0d17\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d1c\u0d21\u0d3f \u0d2e\u0d46\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d4b\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d32\u0d4d \u0d1f\u0d57\u0d23\u0d4d \u0d39\u0d3e\u0d33\u0d4d \u0d0e\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d1f\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d? ",
    "answer": "\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d30\u0d42\u0d30\u0d4d",
    "status": "10"
  },
  {
    "id": "1299",
    "question": "\u0d15\u0d47\u0d30\u0d33\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4d \u0d0f\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d35\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d15\u0d42\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d24\u0d32\u0d4d \u0d28\u0d3e\u0d33\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d47\u0d30\u0d02 \u0d09\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d3e\u0d26\u0d3f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d1c\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4d\u0d32 \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d4d? ",
    "answer": "\u0d15\u0d4b\u0d34\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4b\u0d1f\u0d4d",
    "status": "10"
  },
  {
    "id": "1300",
    "question": "\u0d32\u0d4b\u0d15\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d0f\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d35\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d2a\u0d34\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d02 \u0d1a\u0d46\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d24\u0d47\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d \u0d24\u0d4b\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d02 \u0d0e\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d1f\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d? ",
    "answer": "\u0d35\u0d46\u0d33\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d02 \u0d24\u0d4b\u0d1f\u0d4d (\u0d28\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d42\u0d30\u0d4d)",
    "status": "10"
  },
  {
    "id": "1301",
    "question": ". \u0d0f\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d35\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d15\u0d42\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d24\u0d32\u0d4d \u0d07\u0d30\u0d41\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d4d \u0d28\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d37\u0d47\u0d2a\u0d02 \u0d09\u0d33\u0d4d\u0d33 \u0d1c\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4d\u0d32 \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d4d? ",
    "answer": "\u0d15\u0d4b\u0d34\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4b\u0d1f\u0d4d",
    "status": "10"
  },
  {
    "id": "1302",
    "question": ". \u0d15\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d23\u0d42\u0d30\u0d4d \u0d1c\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4d\u0d32\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d05\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d1a\u0d40\u0d28\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d2f \u0d12\u0d30\u0d41 \u0d05\u0d28\u0d41\u0d37\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d15\u0d32: ",
    "answer": "\u0d24\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d02",
    "status": "10"
  },
  {
    "id": "1303",
    "question": "\u0d24\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d19\u0d33\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d28\u0d3e\u0d1f\u0d4d \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d46\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d1c\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4d\u0d32 \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d4d? ",
    "answer": "\u0d15\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d23\u0d42\u0d30\u0d4d",
    "status": "10"
  },
  {
    "id": "1304",
    "question": "\u0d15\u0d47\u0d30\u0d33\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4d \u0d0f\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d35\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d12\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4d \u0d30\u0d42\u0d2a\u0d02 \u0d15\u0d4a\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d1f \u0d2e\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d38\u0d3f\u0d2a\u0d3e\u0d32\u0d3f\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d3f \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d4d? ",
    "answer": "\u0d2e\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d42\u0d30\u0d4d",
    "status": "10"
  },
  {
    "id": "1305",
    "question": "\u0d30\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d3e\u0d02 \u0d2c\u0d30\u0d4d\u0d26\u0d4b\u0d33\u0d3f \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d46\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d32\u0d02: ",
    "answer": "\u0d2a\u0d2f\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d42\u0d30\u0d4d",
    "status": "10"
  },
  {
    "id": "1306",
    "question": "\u0d15\u0d47\u0d30\u0d33\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4d \u0d0f\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d35\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d15\u0d41\u0d31\u0d35\u0d4d \u0d24\u0d3e\u0d32\u0d42\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d41\u0d15\u0d33\u0d4d \u0d09\u0d33\u0d4d\u0d33 \u0d1c\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4d\u0d32 \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d4d? ",
    "answer": "\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d38\u0d30\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4b\u0d1f\u0d4d",
    "status": "10"
  },
  {
    "id": "1307",
    "question": ". \u0d15\u0d47\u0d30\u0d33\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d06\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f \u0d2e\u0d41\u0d16\u0d4d\u0d2f \u0d2e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d30\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d07 \u0d0e\u0d02 \u0d0e\u0d38\u0d4d \u0d12\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d3e\u0d02 \u0d15\u0d47\u0d30\u0d33\u0d3e \u0d28\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d2e \u0d38\u0d2d\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4d \u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d3f\u0d27\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d02 \u0d1a\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d30\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d05",
    "answer": "\u0d28\u0d40\u0d32\u0d47\u0d36\u0d4d\u0d35\u0d30\u0d02",
    "status": "10"
  },
  {
    "id": "1308",
    "question": "\u0d15\u0d47\u0d30\u0d33\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d35\u0d32\u0d3f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d02 \u0d15\u0d41\u0d31\u0d1e\u0d4d\u0d1e \u0d30\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d3e\u0d2e\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d46 \u0d1c\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4d\u0d32 \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d4d? ",
    "answer": "\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d38\u0d30\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4b\u0d1f\u0d4d",
    "status": "10"
  },
  {
    "id": "1309",
    "question": "\u0d15\u0d47\u0d30\u0d33\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4d \u0d0f\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d35\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d15\u0d42\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d24\u0d32\u0d4d \u0d15\u0d1f\u0d32\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d40\u0d30\u0d02 \u0d09\u0d33\u0d4d\u0d33 \u0d1c\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4d\u0d32 \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d4d? ",
    "answer": "\u0d15\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d23\u0d42\u0d30\u0d4d",
    "status": "10"
  },
  {
    "id": "1310",
    "question": "\u0d15\u0d47\u0d30\u0d33 \u0d38\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d47\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d \u0d2b\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d37\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d32\u0d4d \u0d15\u0d4b\u0d30\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d31\u0d47\u0d37\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d06\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d02 \u0d0e\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d1f\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d? ",
    "answer": "\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d30\u0d41\u0d35\u0d28\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d2a\u0d41\u0d30\u0d02",
    "status": "10"
  },
  {
    "id": "1311",
    "question": "\u0d2a\u0d3e\u0d32\u0d3f\u0d7d \u0d05\u0d1f\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d19\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d2a\u0d1e\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d38\u0d3e\u0d30 \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d4d ?",
    "answer": "\u0d32\u0d3e\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d4b\u0d38\u0d4d",
    "status": "11"
  },
  {
    "id": "1312",
    "question": "\u0d32\u0d35\u0d4d \u0d32\u0d4b\u0d38\u0d4d \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d46\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d24\u0d4d ? ",
    "answer": "\u0d2b\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d4b\u0d38\u0d4d ",
    "status": "11"
  },
  {
    "id": "1313",
    "question": "\u0d24\u0d47\u0d28\u0d3f\u0d7d \u0d05\u0d1f\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d19\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d27\u0d3e\u0d28 \u0d2a\u0d1e\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d38\u0d3e\u0d30 \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d4d ?",
    "answer": "\u0d2b\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d4b\u0d38\u0d4d ",
    "status": "11"
  },
  {
    "id": "1314",
    "question": "\u0d2e\u0d46\u0d34\u0d41\u0d15\u0d4d \u0d32\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d26\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d35\u0d15\u0d02 ?",
    "answer": "\u0d2c\u0d46\u0d7b\u0d38\u0d40\u0d7b",
    "status": "11"
  },
  {
    "id": "1315",
    "question": "\u0d38\u0d3f\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d1e\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d41\u0d15\u0d7e \u0d05\u0d23\u0d41\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d2e\u0d41\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d7b \u0d09\u0d2a\u0d2f\u0d4b\u0d17\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d2a\u0d26\u0d3e\u0d7c\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d02 \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d4d ?",
    "answer": "\u0d0e\u0d25\u0d28\u0d4b\u0d7e",
    "status": "11"
  },
  {
    "id": "1316",
    "question": "\u0d2e\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d23\u0d3f\u0d7b\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d05\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d32 \u0d35\u0d40\u0d30\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d02 \u0d15\u0d41\u0d31\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d7b \u0d09\u0d2a\u0d2f\u0d4b\u0d17\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d2a\u0d26\u0d3e\u0d7c\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d02 ?",
    "answer": "\u0d15\u0d41\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d02",
    "status": "11"
  },
  {
    "id": "1317",
    "question": "\u0d1c\u0d32\u0d02 \u0d36\u0d41\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d27\u0d40\u0d15\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d \u0d09\u0d2a\u0d2f\u0d4b\u0d17\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d12\u0d30\u0d41 \u0d32\u0d35\u0d23\u0d02 ?",
    "answer": "\u0d2a\u0d4a\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d3e\u0d37\u0d4d \u0d06\u0d32\u0d02",
    "status": "11"
  },
  {
    "id": "1318",
    "question": "\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d7c\u0d2c\u0d7a \u0d38\u0d02\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d19\u0d7e \u0d15\u0d41\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d4d \u0d2a\u0d20\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d30\u0d38\u0d24\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30 \u0d36\u0d3e\u0d16 ?",
    "answer": "\u0d13\u0d7c\u0d17\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d \u0d15\u0d46\u0d2e\u0d3f\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d3f",
    "status": "11"
  },
  {
    "id": "1319",
    "question": "\u0d2e\u0d37\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d31 \u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d7b \u0d09\u0d2a\u0d2f\u0d4b\u0d17\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d06\u0d38\u0d3f\u0d21\u0d4d ?",
    "answer": "\u0d13\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d38\u0d3e\u0d32\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d \u0d06\u0d38\u0d3f\u0d21\u0d4d",
    "status": "11"
  },
  {
    "id": "1320",
    "question": "\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d38\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d35\u0d7c\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d28 \u0d35\u0d47\u0d17\u0d02 \u0d35\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d38\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d46\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d7b \u0d1a\u0d47\u0d7c\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d30\u0d3e\u0d38\u0d35\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d41\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d7e \u0d05\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d46\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d24\u0d4d ?",
    "answer": "\u0d09\u0d7d\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d47\u0d30\u0d15\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d19\u0d7e ",
    "status": "11"
  },
  {
    "id": "1321",
    "question": "\u0d31\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d7b\u0d15\u0d4b\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d4d \u0d28\u0d3f\u0d7c\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d41\u0d35\u0d3e\u0d7b \u0d09\u0d2a\u0d2f\u0d4b\u0d17\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d30\u0d3e\u0d38\u0d35\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d41 ?",
    "answer": "\u0d2a\u0d4b\u0d33\u0d3f \u0d15\u0d4d\u0d32\u0d4b\u0d31\u0d4b \u0d08\u0d26\u0d3f\u0d7b",
    "status": "11"
  },
  {
    "id": "1322",
    "question": "\u0d2a\u0d1e\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d38\u0d3e\u0d30 \u0d1a\u0d42\u0d1f\u0d3e\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d41\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d4b\u0d7e \u0d32\u0d2d\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d07\u0d30\u0d41\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d1f \u0d24\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d41 \u0d28\u0d3f\u0d31\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d41\u0d33\u0d4d\u0d33 \u0d35\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d41 ?",
    "answer": "\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d2e\u0d7d",
    "status": "11"
  },
  {
    "id": "1323",
    "question": "\u0d05\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d30\u0d40\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d37\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d15\u0d3e\u0d7c\u0d2c\u0d7a \u0d21\u0d48 \u0d13\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d38\u0d48\u0d21\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d46 \u0d05\u0d33\u0d35\u0d4d \u0d0e\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30 ?",
    "answer": "0.03 %",
    "status": "11"
  },
  {
    "id": "1324",
    "question": "\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d7c\u0d2c\u0d7a \u0d21\u0d48 \u0d13\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d38\u0d48\u0d21\u0d4d \u0d15\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d41 \u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d1f\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d06\u0d30\u0d4d ?",
    "answer": "\u0d1c\u0d4b\u0d38\u0d2b\u0d4d \u0d2c\u0d4d\u0d32\u0d3e\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4d",
    "status": "11"
  },
  {
    "id": "1325",
    "question": "\u0d13\u0d38\u0d4b\u0d7a \u0d2a\u0d3e\u0d33\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d28\u0d3f\u0d31\u0d02 ?",
    "answer": "\u0d07\u0d33\u0d02\u0d28\u0d40\u0d32",
    "status": "11"
  },
  {
    "id": "1326",
    "question": "\u0d07\u0d7b\u0d38\u0d41\u0d32\u0d3f\u0d7b \u0d05\u0d1f\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d19\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d33\u0d4d\u0d33 \u0d32\u0d4b\u0d39\u0d02 ?",
    "answer": "\u0d38\u0d3f\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4d ",
    "status": "11"
  },
  {
    "id": "1327",
    "question": "\u0d24\u0d41\u0d30\u0d41\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24 \u0d38\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d40\u0d7d \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d4d ?",
    "answer": "\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d7b\u0d32\u0d46\u0d38\u0d4d \u0d38\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d40\u0d7d",
    "status": "11"
  },
  {
    "id": "1328",
    "question": "\u0d36\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d2f \u0d09\u0d2a\u0d15\u0d30\u0d23\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d19\u0d7e \u0d28\u0d3f\u0d7c\u0d2e\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d41\u0d2a\u0d2f\u0d4b\u0d17\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d38\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d40\u0d7d \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d4d ?",
    "answer": "\u0d39\u0d48 \u0d15\u0d3e\u0d7c\u0d2c\u0d7a \u0d38\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d40\u0d7d",
    "status": "11"
  },
  {
    "id": "1329",
    "question": "\u0d15\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d7e \u0d15\u0d41\u0d34\u0d32\u0d41\u0d15\u0d7e \u0d15\u0d43\u0d37\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d3e\u0d7d \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d3f\u0d35\u0d7c \u0d28\u0d3f\u0d7c\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d41\u0d35\u0d3e\u0d7b \u0d09\u0d2a\u0d2f\u0d4b\u0d17\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d38\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d40\u0d7d \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d4d ?",
    "answer": "\u0d2e\u0d48\u0d7d\u0d21\u0d4d \u0d38\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d40\u0d7d",
    "status": "11"
  },
  {
    "id": "1330",
    "question": "\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d7d \u0d0f\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d35\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d28\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d3f \u0d1a\u0d46\u0d31\u0d41\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d32\u0d4b\u0d39\u0d02 \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d4d ?",
    "answer": "\u0d07\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d21\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d02",
    "status": "11"
  },
  {
    "id": "1331",
    "question": "\u0d1a\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d28\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d2a\u0d3e\u0d31\u0d15\u0d33\u0d3f\u0d7d \u0d27\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d33\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d3f \u0d15\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d46\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d32\u0d4b\u0d39\u0d02 ?",
    "answer": "\u0d1f\u0d48\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d02",
    "status": "11"
  },
  {
    "id": "1332",
    "question": "\u0d17\u0d3e\u0d7d\u0d35\u0d28\u0d48\u0d38\u0d37\u0d7b \u0d1a\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d35\u0d3e\u0d7b \u0d09\u0d2a\u0d2f\u0d4b\u0d17\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d32\u0d4b\u0d39\u0d02 \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d4d ?",
    "answer": "\u0d38\u0d3f\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4d ",
    "status": "11"
  },
  {
    "id": "1333",
    "question": "\u0d15\u0d33\u0d3f\u0d2e\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d23\u0d3f\u0d7d \u0d38\u0d2e\u0d43\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d27\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d33\u0d4d\u0d33 \u0d32\u0d4b\u0d39\u0d02 \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d4d ?",
    "answer": "\u0d05\u0d32\u0d41\u0d2e\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d02",
    "status": "11"
  },
  {
    "id": "1334",
    "question": "\u0d2e\u0d30\u0d24\u0d15 \u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d7b\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d28\u0d3f\u0d31\u0d02 \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d ?",
    "answer": "\u0d2a\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a",
    "status": "11"
  },
  {
    "id": "1335",
    "question": "\u0d2f\u0d25\u0d3e\u0d7c\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d25 \u0d35\u0d1c\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d02 \u0d24\u0d3f\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d35\u0d3e\u0d7b \u0d09\u0d2a\u0d2f\u0d4b\u0d17\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d24\u0d4d ?",
    "answer": "\u0d05\u0d7e\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d35\u0d2f\u0d32\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d \u0d15\u0d3f\u0d30\u0d23\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d19\u0d7e",
    "status": "11"
  },
  {
    "id": "1336",
    "question": "\u0d17\u0d4d\u0d32\u0d3e\u0d38\u0d4d \u0d2e\u0d41\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d7b \u0d09\u0d2a\u0d2f\u0d4b\u0d17\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d35\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d41 ?",
    "answer": "\u0d35\u0d1c\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d02",
    "status": "11"
  },
  {
    "id": "1337",
    "question": "\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d32\u0d3e\u0d38\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d26\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d7b \u0d15\u0d34\u0d3f\u0d35\u0d41\u0d33\u0d4d\u0d33 \u0d06\u0d38\u0d3f\u0d21\u0d4d ?",
    "answer": "\u0d39\u0d48\u0d21\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d4b\u0d2b\u0d4d\u0d32\u0d42\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d \u0d06\u0d38\u0d3f\u0d21\u0d4d ",
    "status": "11"
  },
  {
    "id": "1338",
    "question": "\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d7c\u0d2c\u0d7a \u0d2e\u0d4b\u0d23\u0d4b\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d38\u0d48\u0d21\u0d4d \u0d30\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d39\u0d40\u0d2e\u0d4b\u0d17\u0d4d\u0d32\u0d4b\u0d2c\u0d3f\u0d7b \u0d05\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d3f \u0d15\u0d42\u0d1f\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d47\u0d30\u0d41\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d4b\u0d7e \u0d09\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d3e\u0d15\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d38\u0d02\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d02 ?",
    "answer": "\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d7c\u0d2c\u0d4b\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d38\u0d3f \u0d39\u0d40\u0d2e\u0d4b\u0d17\u0d4d\u0d32\u0d4b\u0d2c\u0d3f\u0d7b",
    "status": "11"
  },
  {
    "id": "1339",
    "question": "\u0d2d\u0d4b\u0d2a\u0d3e\u0d7d \u0d26\u0d41\u0d30\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d \u0d15\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d23\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d2f \u0d35\u0d3f\u0d37\u0d35\u0d3e\u0d24\u0d15\u0d02 ?",
    "answer": "\u0d2e\u0d40\u0d24\u0d48\u0d7d \u0d10\u0d38\u0d4b\u0d38\u0d2f\u0d28\u0d47\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d",
    "status": "11"
  },
  {
    "id": "1340",
    "question": "\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d1c\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d39\u0d32\u0d3f\u0d7d \u0d28\u0d3f\u0d31\u0d02 \u0d2e\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d19\u0d3e\u0d7b \u0d15\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d23\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d2f \u0d35\u0d3e\u0d24\u0d15\u0d02 ?",
    "answer": "\u0d38\u0d7e\u0d2b\u0d7c \u0d21\u0d2f\u0d4b\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d38\u0d48\u0d21\u0d4d",
    "status": "11"
  },
  {
    "id": "1341",
    "question": "\u0d1c\u0d32\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d7d \u0d32\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d17\u0d4d\u0d32\u0d3e\u0d38\u0d4d \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d ?",
    "answer": "\u0d38\u0d4b\u0d21\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d02 \u0d38\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d47\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d",
    "status": "11"
  },
  {
    "id": "1342",
    "question": "\u0d2e\u0d1e\u0d4d\u0d1e\u0d33\u0d3f\u0d7b\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d2e\u0d1e\u0d4d\u0d1e \u0d28\u0d3f\u0d31\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d \u0d15\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d23\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d2f \u0d30\u0d3e\u0d38\u0d35\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d41 ?",
    "answer": "\u0d15\u0d41\u0d7c\u0d15\u0d41\u0d2e\u0d3f\u0d7b",
    "status": "11"
  },
  {
    "id": "1343",
    "question": "\u0d1a\u0d41\u0d35\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d4d \u0d35\u0d3e\u0d24\u0d15\u0d02 \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d46\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d24\u0d4d ?",
    "answer": "\u0d2e\u0d40\u0d25\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d7b",
    "status": "11"
  },
  {
    "id": "1344",
    "question": "\u0d18\u0d28 \u0d39\u0d48\u0d21\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d1c\u0d7b \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d46\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d24\u0d4d ?",
    "answer": "\u0d21\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d42\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d40\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d02",
    "status": "11"
  },
  {
    "id": "1345",
    "question": "\u0d2e\u0d41\u0d32\u0d4d\u0d32\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d42\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d46 \u0d2e\u0d23\u0d2e\u0d41\u0d33\u0d4d\u0d33 \u0d30\u0d3e\u0d38\u0d35\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d41 ?",
    "answer": "\u0d2c\u0d46\u0d7b\u0d38\u0d48\u0d7d \u0d05\u0d38\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d47\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d ",
    "status": "11"
  },
  {
    "id": "1346",
    "question": "\u0d24\u0d47\u0d28\u0d3f\u0d7b\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d17\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d27\u0d2e\u0d41\u0d33\u0d4d\u0d33 \u0d30\u0d3e\u0d38\u0d35\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d41 ?",
    "answer": "\u0d2e\u0d40\u0d24\u0d48\u0d7d \u0d2b\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d48\u0d7d \u0d05\u0d38\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d47\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d ",
    "status": "11"
  },
  {
    "id": "1347",
    "question": "\u0d15\u0d41\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d36\u0d3f\u0d7b\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d30\u0d3e\u0d38\u0d28\u0d3e\u0d2e\u0d02 \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d ?",
    "answer": "\u0d15\u0d4b\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d7c \u0d38\u0d7e\u0d2b\u0d47\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d",
    "status": "11"
  },
  {
    "id": "1348",
    "question": "\u0d15\u0d41\u0d2e\u0d3f\u0d7e\u0d28\u0d3e\u0d36\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d3f \u0d06\u0d2f\u0d3f \u0d09\u0d2a\u0d2f\u0d4b\u0d17\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d30\u0d3e\u0d38\u0d35\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d41 \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d4d ?",
    "answer": "\u0d24\u0d41\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d36\u0d4d",
    "status": "11"
  },
  {
    "id": "1349",
    "question": "\u0d35\u0d48\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d \u0d35\u0d3f\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d4b\u0d7e \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d46\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d24\u0d4d ?",
    "answer": "\u0d38\u0d3f\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4d \u0d38\u0d7e\u0d2b\u0d47\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d",
    "status": "11"
  },
  {
    "id": "1350",
    "question": "\u0d0e\u0d32\u0d3f\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d37\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d30\u0d3e\u0d38\u0d28\u0d3e\u0d2e\u0d02 \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d ?",
    "answer": "\u0d38\u0d3f\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4d \u0d2b\u0d4b\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d2b\u0d48\u0d21\u0d4d",
    "status": "11"
  },
  {
    "id": "1351",
    "question": "\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d30\u0d3e\u0d38\u0d28\u0d3e\u0d2e\u0d02 \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d ?",
    "answer": "\u0d08\u0d24\u0d48\u0d7d \u0d06\u0d7d\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d39\u0d4b\u0d7e ",
    "status": "11"
  },
  {
    "id": "1352",
    "question": "\u0d2a\u0d3e\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31 \u0d17\u0d41\u0d33\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d30\u0d3e\u0d38\u0d28\u0d3e\u0d2e\u0d02 \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d ?",
    "answer": "\u0d28\u0d3e\u0d2b\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d32\u0d40\u0d7b ",
    "status": "11"
  },
  {
    "id": "1353",
    "question": "\u0d06\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d2c\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4b\u0d38\u0d4d \u0d30\u0d3e\u0d38\u0d28\u0d3e\u0d2e\u0d02 \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d ?",
    "answer": "\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d7d\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d02 \u0d2e\u0d17\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d40\u0d37\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d02 \u0d38\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d47\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d",
    "status": "11"
  },
  {
    "id": "1354",
    "question": "\u0d2c\u0d4d\u0d32\u0d40\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d3f\u0d19\u0d4d \u0d2a\u0d57\u0d21\u0d7c \u0d30\u0d3e\u0d38\u0d28\u0d3e\u0d2e\u0d02 ?",
    "answer": "\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d7d\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d02 \u0d39\u0d48\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d4b \u0d15\u0d4d\u0d32\u0d4b\u0d31\u0d48\u0d21\u0d4d",
    "status": "11"
  },
  {
    "id": "1355",
    "question": "\u0d35\u0d46\u0d1f\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d30\u0d3e\u0d38\u0d28\u0d3e\u0d2e\u0d02 ?",
    "answer": "\u0d2a\u0d4a\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d3e\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d02 \u0d28\u0d48\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d47\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d",
    "status": "11"
  },
  {
    "id": "1356",
    "question": "\u0d07\u0d1f\u0d3f\u0d2e\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d32\u0d41\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d3e\u0d15\u0d41\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d4b\u0d7e \u0d05\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d30\u0d40\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d37\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d41\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d3e\u0d15\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d38\u0d02\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d02 \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d4d ?",
    "answer": "\u0d28\u0d48\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d \u0d13\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d38\u0d48\u0d21\u0d4d",
    "status": "11"
  },
  {
    "id": "1357",
    "question": "\u0d35\u0d48\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d24\u0d3f \u0d15\u0d1f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d15\u0d3e\u0d7c\u0d2c\u0d23\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d46 \u0d15\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d7d \u0d30\u0d42\u0d2a\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d30\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d ?",
    "answer": "\u0d17\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d2b\u0d48\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d",
    "status": "11"
  },
  {
    "id": "1358",
    "question": "\u0d2e\u0d30\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d40\u0d28\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d7d \u0d05\u0d1f\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d19\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d06\u0d38\u0d3f\u0d21\u0d4d ?",
    "answer": "\u0d39\u0d48\u0d21\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d4b \u0d38\u0d2f\u0d28\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d \u0d06\u0d38\u0d3f\u0d21\u0d4d",
    "status": "11"
  },
  {
    "id": "1359",
    "question": "\u0d28\u0d48\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d1c\u0d7b \u0d15\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d1f\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a \u0d36\u0d3e\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d1c\u0d4d\u0d1e\u0d7b ?",
    "answer": "\u0d21\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d7d \u0d31\u0d42\u0d25\u0d7c\u0d2b\u0d4b\u0d7c\u0d21\u0d4d",
    "status": "11"
  },
  {
    "id": "1360",
    "question": "\u0d2e\u0d28\u0d41\u0d37\u0d4d\u0d2f \u0d30\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d0e\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d4d \u0d2e\u0d42\u0d32\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d02 \u0d0e\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30 ?",
    "answer": "7.40",
    "status": "11"
  },
  {
    "id": "1361",
    "question": "\u0d36\u0d41\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d27\u0d1c\u0d32\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d2a\u0d47\u0d1c\u0d4d \u0d2e\u0d42\u0d32\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d02 \u0d0e\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30 ?",
    "answer": "7.0",
    "status": "11"
  },
  {
    "id": "1362",
    "question": "\u0d06\u0d38\u0d3f\u0d21\u0d41\u0d15\u0d33\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d2c\u0d47\u0d38\u0d41\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d3f \u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d35\u0d7c\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d41\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d4b\u0d7e ____ \u0d09\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d3e\u0d15\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d41 .",
    "answer": "\u0d1c\u0d32\u0d35\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d32\u0d35\u0d23\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d19\u0d33\u0d41\u0d02",
    "status": "11"
  },
  {
    "id": "1363",
    "question": "\u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d0e\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d4d \u0d2e\u0d42\u0d32\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d02 7-\u0d7d \u0d15\u0d42\u0d1f\u0d3f\u0d2f \u0d30\u0d3e\u0d38\u0d35\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d41\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d7e ?",
    "answer": "\u0d2c\u0d47\u0d38\u0d41\u0d15\u0d7e ( \u0d06\u0d7d\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d32\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d7e )",
    "status": "11"
  },
  {
    "id": "1364",
    "question": "\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d0e\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d4d \u0d2e\u0d42\u0d32\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d02 ?",
    "answer": "5",
    "status": "11"
  },
  {
    "id": "1365",
    "question": "\u0d1a\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d0e\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d4d \u0d2e\u0d42\u0d32\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d02 ?",
    "answer": "5.5",
    "status": "11"
  },
  {
    "id": "1366",
    "question": "\u0d2e\u0d42\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d \u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d0e\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d4d \u0d2e\u0d42\u0d32\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d02 \u0d0e\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30 ?",
    "answer": "6",
    "status": "11"
  },
  {
    "id": "1367",
    "question": "\u0d2a\u0d3e\u0d32\u0d3f\u0d7b\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d0e\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d4d \u0d2e\u0d42\u0d32\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d02 \u0d0e\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30 ?",
    "answer": "6.5 - 6.7",
    "status": "11"
  },
  {
    "id": "1368",
    "question": "\u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d0e\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d4d \u0d2e\u0d42\u0d32\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d02 7-\u0d7d \u0d24\u0d3e\u0d34\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d33\u0d4d\u0d33\u0d35 ?",
    "answer": "\u0d06\u0d38\u0d3f\u0d21\u0d4d",
    "status": "11"
  },
  {
    "id": "1369",
    "question": "\u0d2a\u0d3f \u0d0e\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d4d \u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d2a\u0d42\u0d7c\u0d23 \u0d30\u0d42\u0d2a\u0d02 ?",
    "answer": "\u0d2a\u0d4a\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d7b\u0d37\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d7d \u0d13\u0d2b\u0d4d \u0d39\u0d48\u0d21\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d1c\u0d7b",
    "status": "11"
  },
  {
    "id": "1370",
    "question": "\u0d31\u0d2b\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d1c\u0d31\u0d47\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d31\u0d41\u0d15\u0d33\u0d3f\u0d7d \u0d15\u0d42\u0d33\u0d7c \u0d06\u0d2f\u0d3f \u0d09\u0d2a\u0d2f\u0d4b\u0d17\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d ?",
    "answer": "\u0d2b\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d4b\u0d7a ",
    "status": "11"
  },
  {
    "id": "1371",
    "question": "\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d02\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d7d \u0d05\u0d1f\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d19\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d06\u0d38\u0d3f\u0d21\u0d4d ?",
    "answer": "\u0d05\u0d2e\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4b \u0d06\u0d38\u0d3f\u0d21\u0d4d",
    "status": "11"
  },
  {
    "id": "1372",
    "question": "\u0d1c\u0d3f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d38\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d05\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d7b\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d30\u0d3e\u0d38\u0d28\u0d3e\u0d2e\u0d02 \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d ?",
    "answer": "\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d7d\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d02 \u0d38\u0d7e\u0d2b\u0d47\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d",
    "status": "11"
  },
  {
    "id": "1373",
    "question": "\u0d2e\u0d46\u0d34\u0d41\u0d15\u0d3f\u0d7d \u0d2a\u0d4a\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d1e\u0d4d\u0d1e\u0d41 \u0d38\u0d42\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d37\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d32\u0d4b\u0d39\u0d02 ?",
    "answer": "\u0d32\u0d3f\u0d25\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d02",
    "status": "11"
  },
  {
    "id": "1374",
    "question": "\u0d0f\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d35\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d2d\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d02 \u0d15\u0d42\u0d1f\u0d3f\u0d2f \u0d35\u0d3e\u0d24\u0d15\u0d02 ?",
    "answer": "\u0d31\u0d3e\u0d21\u0d4b\u0d7a ",
    "status": "11"
  },
  {
    "id": "1375",
    "question": "\u0d28\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d37\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d19\u0d33\u0d3f\u0d7d \u0d15\u0d42\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d24\u0d32\u0d41\u0d33\u0d4d\u0d33 \u0d2e\u0d42\u0d32\u0d15\u0d02 ?",
    "answer": "\u0d39\u0d48\u0d21\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d1c\u0d7b",
    "status": "11"
  },
  {
    "id": "1376",
    "question": "\u0d30\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d02 \u0d15\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d1f\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d32\u0d4b\u0d39\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d7b\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d38\u0d39\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d32\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d ?",
    "answer": "\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d7d\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d02",
    "status": "11"
  },
  {
    "id": "1377",
    "question": "\u0d0f\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d35\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d15\u0d42\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d24\u0d7d \u0d38\u0d02\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d02 \u0d09\u0d33\u0d4d\u0d33 \u0d2e\u0d42\u0d32\u0d15\u0d02 ?",
    "answer": "\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d7c\u0d2c\u0d7a",
    "status": "11"
  },
  {
    "id": "1378",
    "question": "\u0d15\u0d33\u0d3f\u0d2e\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d23\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d30\u0d3e\u0d38\u0d28\u0d3e\u0d2e\u0d02 \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d ?",
    "answer": "\u0d05\u0d32\u0d42\u0d2e\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d02 \u0d38\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d47\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d",
    "status": "11"
  },
  {
    "id": "1379",
    "question": "\u0d12\u0d30\u0d47 \u0d05\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4b\u0d2e\u0d3f\u0d15 \u0d28\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d31\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d35\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d24 \u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d38\u0d4d \u0d28\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d31\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d09\u0d33\u0d4d\u0d33 \u0d06\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d19\u0d7e \u0d05\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d46\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d24\u0d4d ?",
    "answer": "\u0d10\u0d38\u0d4b\u0d1f\u0d4b\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d4d",
    "status": "11"
  },
  {
    "id": "1380",
    "question": "\u0d1a\u0d4b\u0d33\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d7d \u0d28\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d41 \u0d35\u0d47\u0d7c\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d46\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d0e\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d23 \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d4d ?",
    "answer": "\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d7c\u0d17\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d7b ",
    "status": "11"
  },
  {
    "id": "1381",
    "question": "\u0d15\u0d41\u0d34\u0d7d \u0d35\u0d3e\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d19\u0d7e \u0d28\u0d3f\u0d7c\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d41\u0d35\u0d3e\u0d7b \u0d09\u0d2a\u0d2f\u0d4b\u0d17\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d32\u0d4b\u0d39\u0d38\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d30\u0d02 \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d4d ?",
    "answer": "\u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d33",
    "status": "11"
  },
  {
    "id": "1382",
    "question": "\u0d1a\u0d46\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4a\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d02 \u0d38\u0d3f\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4d \u0d1a\u0d47\u0d7c\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d41\u0d33\u0d4d\u0d33 \u0d32\u0d4b\u0d39\u0d38\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d30\u0d02 ?",
    "answer": "\u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d33",
    "status": "11"
  },
  {
    "id": "1383",
    "question": "\u0d13\u0d1f\u0d3f\u0d7d \u0d05\u0d1f\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d19\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d33\u0d4d\u0d33 \u0d32\u0d4b\u0d39\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d19\u0d7e \u0d0f\u0d35 ?",
    "answer": "\u0d1a\u0d46\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d4d ,\u0d1f\u0d3f\u0d7b",
    "status": "11"
  },
  {
    "id": "1384",
    "question": "\u0d2e\u0d28\u0d41\u0d37\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d7b \u0d0f\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d35\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d06\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d02 \u0d15\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d1f\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a \u0d32\u0d4b\u0d39\u0d38\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d30\u0d02",
    "answer": "\u0d13\u0d1f\u0d4d ( \u0d35\u0d46\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d32\u0d02 )",
    "status": "11"
  },
  {
    "id": "1385",
    "question": "\u0d07\u0d30\u0d41\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d41 \u0d15\u0d3e\u0d7c\u0d2c\u0d23\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d1a\u0d47\u0d7c\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d32\u0d4b\u0d39\u0d38\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d30\u0d02 ?",
    "answer": "\u0d09\u0d30\u0d41\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4d ",
    "status": "11"
  },
  {
    "id": "1386",
    "question": "\u0d30\u0d38\u0d02 \u0d1a\u0d47\u0d7c\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d32\u0d4b\u0d39\u0d38\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d30\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d19\u0d7e ____ \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d46\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d41 .",
    "answer": "\u0d05\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d7d\u0d17\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d19\u0d7e ",
    "status": "11"
  },
  {
    "id": "1387",
    "question": "\u0d15\u0d43\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d2e\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d3f \u0d28\u0d3f\u0d7c\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d46\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f \u0d06\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f \u0d2e\u0d42\u0d32\u0d15\u0d02 ?",
    "answer": "\u0d1f\u0d46\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d40\u0d37\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d02",
    "status": "11"
  },
  {
    "id": "1388",
    "question": "\u0d32\u0d4b\u0d39\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d19\u0d33\u0d46 \u0d15\u0d41\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d4d \u0d2a\u0d20\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d36\u0d3e\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30 \u0d36\u0d3e\u0d16 ?",
    "answer": "\u0d2e\u0d46\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d32\u0d7c\u0d1c\u0d3f",
    "status": "11"
  },
  {
    "id": "1389",
    "question": "\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d35\u0d24\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d35\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d7d \u0d15\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d46\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d32\u0d4b\u0d39\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d19\u0d7e ?",
    "answer": "\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d35\u0d7c\u0d23\u0d02 ,\u0d35\u0d46\u0d33\u0d4d\u0d33\u0d3f ,\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d32\u0d3e\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d02",
    "status": "11"
  },
  {
    "id": "1390",
    "question": "\u0d24\u0d46\u0d7c\u0d2e\u0d4b\u0d2e\u0d40\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d7d \u0d09\u0d2a\u0d2f\u0d4b\u0d17\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d32\u0d4b\u0d39\u0d02 ?",
    "answer": "\u0d30\u0d38\u0d02",
    "status": "11"
  },
  {
    "id": "1391",
    "question": "\u0d0f\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d35\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d15\u0d42\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d24\u0d7d \u0d2d\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d2e\u0d41\u0d33\u0d4d\u0d33 \u0d32\u0d4b\u0d39\u0d02 ?",
    "answer": "\u0d13\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d02",
    "status": "11"
  },
  {
    "id": "1392",
    "question": "\u0d0f\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d35\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d15\u0d3e\u0d20\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d2e\u0d41\u0d33\u0d4d\u0d33 \u0d32\u0d4b\u0d39\u0d2e\u0d47\u0d24\u0d4d ?",
    "answer": "\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d4b\u0d2e\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d02",
    "status": "11"
  },
  {
    "id": "1393",
    "question": "\u0d2a\u0d1e\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d32\u0d4b\u0d39 \u0d35\u0d3f\u0d17\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d39\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d19\u0d33\u0d3f\u0d7d \u0d0f\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d35\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d15\u0d42\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d24\u0d7d \u0d05\u0d1f\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d19\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d33\u0d4d\u0d33 \u0d32\u0d4b\u0d39\u0d02 ?",
    "answer": "\u0d1a\u0d46\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d4d",
    "status": "11"
  },
  {
    "id": "1394",
    "question": "\u0d2a\u0d1e\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d32\u0d4b\u0d39 \u0d35\u0d3f\u0d17\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d39\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d19\u0d33\u0d3f\u0d7d \u0d05\u0d1f\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d19\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d33\u0d4d\u0d33 \u0d32\u0d4b\u0d39\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d19\u0d7e \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d46\u0d32\u0d4d\u0d32\u0d3e\u0d02 ?",
    "answer": "\u0d1a\u0d46\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d4d ,\u0d08\u0d2f\u0d02 ,\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d35\u0d7c\u0d23\u0d02 ,\u0d35\u0d46\u0d33\u0d4d\u0d33\u0d3f ,\u0d07\u0d30\u0d41\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d4d",
    "status": "11"
  },
  {
    "id": "1395",
    "question": "\u0d2c\u0d7e\u0d2c\u0d41\u0d15\u0d33\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d2b\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d2e\u0d46\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d \u0d28\u0d3f\u0d7c\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d41\u0d2a\u0d2f\u0d4b\u0d17\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d32\u0d4b\u0d39\u0d02 ?",
    "answer": "\u0d1f\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d7a ",
    "status": "11"
  },
  {
    "id": "1396",
    "question": "\u0d30\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d39\u0d40\u0d2e\u0d4b\u0d17\u0d4d\u0d32\u0d4b\u0d2c\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d3f\u0d7d \u0d05\u0d1f\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d19\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d33\u0d4d\u0d33 \u0d32\u0d4b\u0d39\u0d02 ?",
    "answer": "\u0d07\u0d30\u0d41\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d4d",
    "status": "11"
  },
  {
    "id": "1397",
    "question": "\u0d2e\u0d28\u0d41\u0d37\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d36\u0d30\u0d40\u0d30\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d7d \u0d0f\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d35\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d15\u0d42\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d24\u0d32\u0d41\u0d33\u0d4d\u0d33 \u0d32\u0d4b\u0d39\u0d02 ?",
    "answer": "\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d7d\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d02",
    "status": "11"
  },
  {
    "id": "1398",
    "question": "\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d40\u0d7d \u0d05\u0d25\u0d35\u0d3e \u0d09\u0d30\u0d41\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3f\u0d7d \u0d05\u0d1f\u0d3f\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d3e\u0d28 \u0d18\u0d1f\u0d15\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d19\u0d7e \u0d0f\u0d35?",
    "answer": "\u0d07\u0d30\u0d41\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d4d ,\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d7c\u0d2c\u0d7a",
    "status": "11"
  },
  {
    "id": "1399",
    "question": "\u0d1a\u0d3f\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d35\u0d3e\u0d24\u0d15\u0d02 \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d46\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d35\u0d3e\u0d24\u0d15\u0d02 ?",
    "answer": "\u0d28\u0d48\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d38\u0d4d \u0d13\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d38\u0d48\u0d21\u0d4d ",
    "status": "11"
  },
  {
    "id": "1400",
    "question": "\u0d38\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d19\u0d33\u0d4d \u0d30\u0d3e\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d3f \u0d38\u0d2e\u0d2f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d2a\u0d41\u0d31\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d35\u0d3f\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d35\u0d3e\u0d24\u0d15\u0d02 ?",
    "answer": "\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d7c\u0d2c\u0d7a \u0d21\u0d48 \u0d13\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d38\u0d48\u0d21\u0d4d",
    "status": "11"
  },
  {
    "id": "1401",
    "question": "\u0d38\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d19\u0d7e \u0d2a\u0d15\u0d7d \u0d38\u0d2e\u0d2f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d36\u0d38\u0d02\u0d36\u0d4d\u0d32\u0d47\u0d37\u0d23\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d42\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d2a\u0d41\u0d31\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d35\u0d3f\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d35\u0d3e\u0d24\u0d15\u0d02 ?",
    "answer": "\u0d13\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d38\u0d3f\u0d1c\u0d7b",
    "status": "11"
  },
  {
    "id": "1402",
    "question": "\u0d2d\u0d42\u0d2e\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d05\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d30\u0d40\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d37\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d7d \u0d0f\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d35\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d15\u0d42\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d24\u0d32\u0d41\u0d33\u0d4d\u0d33 \u0d35\u0d3e\u0d24\u0d15\u0d02 ?",
    "answer": "\u0d28\u0d48\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d1c\u0d7b 78%",
    "status": "11"
  },
  {
    "id": "1403",
    "question": "\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d2a\u0d1e\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d7d \u0d0f\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d35\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d15\u0d42\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d24\u0d32\u0d41\u0d33\u0d4d\u0d33 \u0d35\u0d3e\u0d24\u0d15\u0d02 ?",
    "answer": "\u0d39\u0d48\u0d21\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d1c\u0d7b",
    "status": "11"
  },
  {
    "id": "1404",
    "question": "\u0d39\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d17\u0d43\u0d39\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d2d\u0d3e\u0d35\u0d02 \u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d27\u0d3e\u0d28 \u0d15\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d23\u0d02 \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d35\u0d3e\u0d24\u0d15\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d ?",
    "answer": "\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d7c\u0d2c\u0d7a\u0d21\u0d2f\u0d4b\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d38\u0d48\u0d21\u0d4d",
    "status": "11"
  },
  {
    "id": "1405",
    "question": "\u0d1a\u0d41\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d23\u0d3e\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d4d \u0d35\u0d46\u0d33\u0d4d\u0d33\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d46 \u0d2a\u0d3e\u0d7d \u0d28\u0d3f\u0d31\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d35\u0d3e\u0d24\u0d15\u0d02 ?",
    "answer": "\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d7c\u0d2c\u0d7a\u0d21\u0d2f\u0d4b\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d38\u0d48\u0d21\u0d4d",
    "status": "11"
  },
  {
    "id": "1406",
    "question": "\u0d28\u0d40\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d41 \u0d15\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d30\u0d3e\u0d38\u0d28\u0d3e\u0d2e\u0d02 \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d ?",
    "answer": "\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d7d\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d02 \u0d13\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d38\u0d48\u0d21\u0d4d",
    "status": "11"
  },
  {
    "id": "1407",
    "question": "\u0d1c\u0d32\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d \u0d0f\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d35\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d05\u0d27\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d02 \u0d38\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d24\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d33\u0d4d\u0d33\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d0e\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30 \u0d21\u0d3f\u0d17\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d3f \u0d38\u0d46\u0d7d\u0d37\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d38\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d ?",
    "answer": "4 \u0d21\u0d3f\u0d17\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d3f \u0d38\u0d46\u0d7d\u0d37\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d38\u0d4d",
    "status": "11"
  },
  {
    "id": "1408",
    "question": "\u0d35\u0d46\u0d33\u0d4d\u0d33\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d7d \u0d0f\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d35\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d15\u0d42\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d24\u0d32\u0d4d \u0d32\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d35\u0d3e\u0d24\u0d15\u0d02 \u0d06\u0d23\u0d4d ",
    "answer": "\u0d05\u0d2e\u0d4b\u0d23\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d02",
    "status": "11"
  },
  {
    "id": "1409",
    "question": "\u0d07\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d06\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f \u0d06\u0d23\u0d35 \u0d31\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d7c ?",
    "answer": "\u0d05\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d38\u0d30 ",
    "status": "11"
  },
  {
    "id": "1410",
    "question": "\u0d05\u0d28\u0d41\u0d2d\u0d35 \u0d35\u0d3f\u0d7b\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d35\u0d7c\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d28 \u0d24\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d35\u0d02 \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d ?",
    "answer": "\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d42\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d32\u0d40\u0d2f\u0d7c \u0d2b\u0d3f\u0d37\u0d7b ",
    "status": "11"
  },
  {
    "id": "1411",
    "question": "\u0d38\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d41\u0d37\u0d4d\u0d1f \u0d2f\u0d41\u0d31\u0d47\u0d28\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d02 \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d46\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d24\u0d4d ?",
    "answer": "\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d31\u0d47\u0d28\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d02 235",
    "status": "11"
  },
  {
    "id": "1412",
    "question": "\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d35\u0d3e\u0d2d\u0d3e\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d15 \u0d2f\u0d41\u0d31\u0d47\u0d28\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d10\u0d38\u0d4b\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d4b\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d41\u0d15\u0d7e \u0d0f\u0d35 ?",
    "answer": "\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d31\u0d47\u0d28\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d02 234 ,235 ,238",
    "status": "11"
  }
]